- Attention, everyone!
Jim and I, on behalf of...
- Too loud.
- The party planning committee,
- Too too loud, too loud.
- Have an annou--
But effective. Look.
On behalf
of jim and I,
Merry christmas.
All: Merry christmas.
- Good.
- My diabolical plot
is on hold for christmas.
My heart just melts with
the sound of children singing.
[snickers]
Not really.
I'm just tired.
The days are short.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm depressed.
It is time
to unveil the tree.
- Hey, rockefeller center.
- Yeah.
- Uh, I've actually
been to rock center,
And this is
nothing like that.
- This is all we have.
- Ugh.
- Nope, it's not "ugh."
It is office camaraderie.
- It is warm feelings.
- Why don't we talk more about
it instead of doing it?
- 30, 29, 28...
- Why would you start so high?
- 27...
- 3, 2, 1...
- 26...
- Ooh.
- Ah.
- You didn't decorate it.
- No, exactly.
- We didn't, because we think
It would be better
to do it together.
- Everyone.
- Why would you wrap it
in a sheet
If you're not covering
anything up?
- Is--is it fake?
- Pam.
- Yes!
We are unveiling
an artificial tree.
That will never die...
- Yes.
- Like the spirit
of christmas.
- And we're supposed
to applaud you
For you taking a giant diaper
off a fake tree?
- This was
a successful unveiling.
Go back to work!
Merry christmas.
- Hello. Sorry, guys.
Sorry, guys.
I'm not sure
I've earned the right
To make announcements yet,
But whoever is giving me
the twelve days of christmas
As my secret santa,
Please stop.
I can't take it anymore.
My cat killed
a turtledove.
The french hens have started
pulling out my hair
To make a nest.
Please stop.
- What psycho
would send that as a gift?
- I begged dwight and jim
To give me erin
for secret santa.
And I decided to give erin
the twelve days of christmas.
Bowtie time.
[birds honking]
Is it my fault
that the first eight days
There's basically
30 birds?
- Ho, ho, ho!
Merry christmas, boys and girls.
It's me, santa claus.
- Hey, santa.
- They finally let you do it.
- Congrats, phyl.
- It's so edgy.
- I have been wanting
to be santa for years.
I believe I have
the right temperament
And the figure
to do the job well.
I slipped a note to jim
11 weeks ago,
And he said I could do it.
[giggles]
[tearfully] oh...It's been
a long journey...
But...[sniffles]
I'm santa claus!
- So, santa, what can we
expect from this party?
- It's going to be
a very jolly time
If you've been good.
- What if you've been bad?
- Oh, then nothing but
a lump of coal for you.
- What if you've been
really, really bad?
More "evil"
than strictly "wrong."
- Hey, creed, we covered it.
Lump of coal.
- For the past several weeks,
My secret santa has been
giving me pieces of a machine
That I've been attempting
to assemble.
I'm suspicious of this,
Because I had
the exact same idea
For catching osama bin laden.
I would simply send him
a different piece each day.
He would assemble it
To find himself...
In jail!
- You know, oscar, every time
I make this lasagna,
People ask me
if it's a family recipe.
But really...I just get
the recipe from the box.
- That's funny.
- Is it funny?
I thought it was more...
Interesting than funny.
I think my water just broke.
- That's too funny.
- Oscar and the warehouse guy.
Go, oscar!
Go, gay warehouse guy!
- Here's...Santa!
Hey, little girl, what would
you like for christmas?
Ooh! You have been
a very naughty girl, I see.
- Michael, we already
have a santa--phyllis.
- What the hell is going on?
Phyllis, jim?
Phyllis is santa.
- Yeah.
- Phyllis.
- Yeah. I told her a long
time ago she could do it.
- Take it back.
That is absurd.
- No. I'm not gonna do that.
- No--no!
Jim, come on!
- I think she'll
do a good job.
- It's insane!
A woman santa?
Where does it stop?
No!
Jim, this may be the last
christmas that we have here.
Doesn't it make you
a tiny bit anxious
Me not playing santa?
Come on!
- I'm not gonna go tell phyllis
that she can't be santa.
- Fine. Then do it
anonymously.
Ransom note style.
You can...
You know what?
I have a bunch of letters
cut out of magazines in my desk.
You can use those.
If this were russia, yeah.
Sure, everybody
would go to one santa.
And there would be
a line around the block,
And once you sat on her lap
And she asked you
what you wanted,
You would say,
probably, "freedom"...
At which point the kgb
would arrest you
And send you to siberia.
It's a good thing russia
doesn't exist anymore.
Ho, ho, ho!
Why pay more to sit next
to old tranny claus over there
When you can sit on my lap?
Phyllis is only pretending
to be a man.
I'm the real thing!
Sit down on my lap,
and there will be no doubt!
[overlapping disgusted comments]
No, it's not,
like, penis-wise.
Hello, little boy!
What's your name?
- Michael, it's me, kevin.
Phyllis says
I'm too big for her lap.
- Oh, I am so sorry
that phyllis hates you
And hates your body.
But santa
remembers a reindeer
That was just a tiny bit
different as well.
- When can I sit on your lap?
- Right now!
Come on over here, big boy!
There we go!
[quietly] oh, my god.
[grunts]
- It's really comfortable.
- [gasping]
[strained] what would you
like for christmas, little boy?
[panting]
- I don't know.
I-I didn't know
you were gonna ask me that.
- Well, what did you think
was going to happen?
- I didn't know.
Nobody's ever let me sit
on their lap before.
- [wheezily] all right,
just say some toys, please.
- Can you give me
some choices?
'cause I really don't wanna
mess up on this list.
- [quietly] damn it, kevin.
Come on.
- What about if I tell you
the things I don't want?
- Okay--get off!
Get off!
Off!
[groans]
oh, jee--god!
- I didn't even get to tell you
what I wanted.
- Okay, you know what
you get?
You get a thousand
helium balloons attached to you
So santa doesn't have
to go through this again.
[moaning] oh!
- Awesome.
- Well?
- I'm trying, phyllis.
You're santa.
- The only santa.
- That's what I want.
- You promised me this.
Don't make me get bob
involved.
- What would bob do?
- Never mind.
I shouldn't have said that.
- Does it hurt?
- It stings a lot.
- Ehh.
- I keep trying to figure out
who's sending me these gifts.
- I know, right?
- So far,
no one will admit to it.
Is it you?
- [laughs] yeah!
[both chuckling]
Totally.
I admit it.
It's me.
- Oh. Seriously?
- Seriously?
[chuckling] are you serious?
- Is--what--you--
- Yeah.
Totally serious.
I'm your secret santa.
Busted!
- [laughing]
- There he is.
- Hey, man.
- Is matt around?
I've got his check.
- Uh, matt is on a delivery.
Just leave it here.
I'll take it.
- Ah. I'll just...
[laughs] wait for him.
- Matt's a pretty good-lookin'
dude, don't you think?
- I'll just leave it
here with ya.
[overlapping chatter]
- What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Come here!
- I'm doing something here.
- Come on! Ah...
Ho, ho, ho!
Come on, I need this.
Come over here!
- What are you talking--
- just sit down.
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Is everything okay?
- Yep. Yeah. Ryan and I
are just having some fun.
- Can I just talk to you
for a second?
- Whoop!
Okay, what?
- You can't yell out,
"I need this, I need this,"
As you pin down an employee
on your lap.
-  Okay. You know what, jim?
With two santas in the room,
things get ruthless.
- Yeah.
- Do you understand?
You forced my hand.
- Okay. Michael, it's phyllis.
We want phyllis as santa.
- Oh, do we? Do we?
Is that what we want?
Why don't we take a vote on it?
- Great.
- Hey! Okay, everybody.
The office
is being pulled apart.
I realize that.
There are traditions
at stake.
And there are women--
- who wants phyllis as santa?
- No, no, no!
Wait! No!
There are other choices.
There's information that we--
are you kidding me, kevin?
After you almost killed me?
- Michael, I had you.
I just wanna try phyllis.
- And if you want michael
as santa, raise your hand.
Can I get you some punch?
- I--no.
I'll get some punch.
- Oh!
- Michael!
- Excuse me.
Whoever has been sending me
the parts to this gun,
I think you sent me a gear
instead of a trigger.
- How do you know
it's a gun?
- What else
does it look like?
- Not a gun.
- Well, I don't have
all the pieces yet.
- Well, unless the missing
pieces is a gun,
You don't have a gun.
[thud]
Not a gun.
- In the north pole,
I spend many nights alone
Tinkering with toys.
So today,
let's put a twinkle
In old kris kringle's eye.
Let the party begin!
- Whoa!
- Yay!
- I don't ask for much
from christmas.
I really don't.
It's not like I am begging
people to...
Buy me diamonds and...
Brooch pendants.
Oh, buy me something
expensive,
Or I'm gonna kill myself.
That's not...
I don't care about that!
All I wanna be is santa.
And...You want to take
that away from me, fine.
Go ahead.
But when you need my help
because I am ruining everything,
Don't look at me!
- Behold...
Jesus christ.
And I bring to you...
Glad christmas tidings.
I want to remind everyone
The true meaning
of christmas.
Those of you
who wish to join me,
That's great,
I am excited by that.
And those of you who don't,
I forgive you.
But I never forget.
- Oh, wow, michael.
This must be obvious
how wrong this is.
- Oh...The antichrist.
- Okay, you can't--
- sss!
- Ow! Look--
you cannot push religion.
- Oh, but I can push drugs
in here.
Is that what you're saying?
- No! You--
- Well, you have to pick
one or the other.
Your choice.
Pick your poison.
Get back to me.
In the meantime...
I am going to spread
my goodness
All over this company!
- Hey, phyllis?
Could you not reveal to erin
that I'm her secret santa?
- All right, sweetie, I'll just
tell her it's michael.
- Okay.
Together:
♪ I saw three ships ♪
♪ come sailing in ♪
- have you talked to him?
- What...
- Matt.
- Is it that obvious?
[mumbles indistinctly]
Oh...Hey.
- Mm. Good pate, right?
Oscar made it.
Have you met oscar?
- I don't think so.
Hey, oscar, come here.
[singing continues
in background]
- ♪ on christmas day
in the morning ♪
Oscar, this is matt,
And, um, matt loves
your pate.
- I had some.
- Oscar's pate's great.
I could eat it all day,
every day.
Mm.
How come the good ones
are never straight, right?
- Okay, pam.
- Okay.
Yes. They're the only
two gay guys I know.
But they should be together.
- This just arrived
From the dunder mifflin
north pole branch.
- We don't have
a north pole branch.
Idiot!
- [sarcastic singsong]
uh-oh, what's dwight gonna get?
What is it?
- Yes!
- Oh, yes.
It's space garbage.
Dwight's gonna be able
to build himself a friend.
♪ deck the halls
with crappy...♪
- And stanley, ho, ho, ho!
You've been very good
this year.
- I have.
- Yeah, except for
cheating on your wife.
Adultery's a sin.
Look it up in the bible, people.
What'd he get?
- He got scented candles.
- Oh.
Well, that's appropriate.
A lotta fire where you're going.
Better get used to it.
You're going to h-e-l-l,
double hockey sticks.
Goin' to hell, stanley.
- Amen.
- And this brings us
to you, little one.
- I can't see from here,
people.
Somebody shout it out.
Don't make me get up.
- It's fabric.
I really wanted this.
- That's fantastic!
You can make another dress
that goes past your feet.
- Andy, was this you?
- It's a secret.
- No, andy had...Erin.
- That--
- michael!
- You--
- What, was I not
supposed to say?
[click]
what--turn it back on.
- No.
- Yes, michael.
What is so urgent?
- David, guess who I am
sitting here dressed as.
- I'm not going to guess.
You can tell me,
or I will hang up.
- I will give you a hint.
His last name is christ.
He has the power of flight.
He can heal leopards.
- Michael--
- I am jesus, david.
And you know why?
Because phyllis, a woman,
Has "uslurped"
my role as santa.
- Michael, this is
a very, very bad time.
- Really?
What's going on?
- Stephanie, can you hop off,
please?
- Sure, david.
- What the hell?
How rude!
Does she do that all the time?
- Do you want me off
this call too, michael?
- Hey--what?
Get off!
Get off the phone!
- [david sighs]
listen...
I shouldn't tell you this,
but the company has a buyer.
The board will have no choice
but to approve,
And they are going
to clean house.
- What does that mean?
- I'll be fired.
- Well...Can't alan
protect you?
- Alan will be out too.
All of us.
Good-bye, michael.
- [quietly]
oh, my god.
- Earlier today,
this office needed a santa.
And then it needed
a second santa.
And then it needed a jesus.
Now, it needs
a michael.
And that's one suit
phyllis cannot fit into.
[low conversations]
- hey...
How's everybody doing?
- Not great.
You heckled santa
for an hour and a half.
- That was a different guy.
That was jesus.
Jesus sort of ruined
the party.
Hurt, petulant jesus.
- Are you serious?
That is so offensive.
- You know what's
even more offensive...
Is bailing on this party
because some...
Jerk ruined
the first part of it.
Dwight, come here.
Here's my debit card.
I want you to go pick up
a bunch of pizzas
And meet me
in the conference room.
- What's your pin number?
- I...Don't want to say.
But it's fun to stay
at the...
♪ it's fun to stay at the ♪
- Where?
Holiday inn.
I don't--
- [humming]
- I-I thought that
you would like it.
- It was a little much,
andy.
- Well, it's the thought
that counts.
- What...Were you thinking?
- I suppose a gentleman
might throw in the towel
At this point.
Guess what.
Not gonna happen.
- You know what,
Christmas isn't
about santa or jesus.
It's about the workplace.
All of you...
Feel like my family.
Ryan, you are my son,
And...
Pam, you're my wife,
and jim...
And angela and phyllis,
you are my...Grandmas.
And stanley,
you're...Our mailman.
And I can't help but look
At all your wonderful,
beautiful faces
And think, "how could they
do this to us?"
- How could who do what to us?
- [overlapping questions]
- That's--not--nothing--
- why--
- It's just...
- We deserve to know.
[overlapping comments]
- We're going out of business!
- What?
- You are kidding me.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Who said that?
- David told me on the phone.
- When did he tell you, today?
- Earlier today, he said...
- Oh!
- We have been sold.
All: What?
- Aah!
- Dwight!
- Come on!
- Michael, wait.
So they said we are sold.
- David is gone, alan is gone.
We're all gone.
- Okay, but we haven't
gone under.
We've been sold, and that can
mean many different things.
- It's hard for me
to imagine a scenario
Where meredith palmer
keeps her job,
And david wallace does not--
no offense, meredith.
- No, I get it.
- I'll call him.
I'll call david.
- No, you won't, because
he's not picking up his phone.
- Yes, I will, because I always
know how to get through to him.
He told me where
his kids go to school.
I call the school.
I tell them
I'm the pediatrician.
They patch me through
to his secretary.
I use my little girl voice.
Badda-bing, badda-boom.
- Hey, sweetie, what is it?
- It's not sweetie.
It's michael scott.
- What the hell--
- Stephanie, could you
hop off, please?
- Michael--[huffs]
I have never--
- David--
- never, ever--
- David, you are on speakerphone
with the entire branch
And the warehouse.
- Hi, david.
- Hey, david.
[overlapping greetings]
- Hi, everyone.
- David,
they do not believe me
When you told me
that everyone was canned.
- You weren't supposed
to tell anyone, michael.
- Well, I think
we're past that now.
- I am not supposed--
Okay, guys, I was really
only talking about
Alan, myself, and a few
other execs you don't know.
- Oh, my god, david,
that's...Horrible.
- How about us?
It's meredith.
By the way, your wife
is a very lucky woman.
- Look, they're buying the
company for the distribution.
You guys are the only thing
about this company that works.
So congratulations.
- We're not fired?
- No.
No, congratulations.
- All right!
- Yeah!
[whooping]
- It's a christmas miracle!
- Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
[clamoring]
- ♪ walk a lonely road ♪
♪ only one
that I have ever known ♪
♪ don't know where it goes ♪
♪ but it's all to me
and I walk alone ♪
It's true.
We all walk alone
at some point.
♪ ♪
- Jim...
- Come on...Shall we?
- ♪ I walk alone ♪
- jim!
♪ I walk a ♪
Both: ♪ my shadow's ♪
♪ the only one
that walks beside me ♪
♪ my shallow heart's the only
thing that's beating ♪
- Wow.
- Yeah. That was--
that was the idea.
- Thank you.
- Awesome.
- Thanks, man.
- ♪ christmas tree ♪
- ♪ thou leaves are so... ♪
- wait a minute.
- Of course!
- Oh! You got it?
- Ha ha!
- What is that?
- I have no idea.
- Huh...
- Well...
Maybe those'll help.
- Michael, please.
Come on.
- Sorry.
- Sure.
- Nice to meet you, oscar.
- Nice to meet you, mark.
- It's matt.
- Right, matt.
I know what I'm doing, pam.
- Oh, man!
I can use this
for so many nuts--macadamias,
Brazil nuts, pecans,
almonds.
Clams. Snails.
- Hi, santa.
- Hi, michael.
[grunts]
Okay.
- [whispers]
I'd like to make a wish.
- [flatly] what?
- I would like an xbox
and...
A tv that's compatible
with an xbox.
And I'm sorry.
- [exhales]
An xbox it is,
Because I've decided
you're a good boy.
- Scott.
What in the hell
is going on here?
- No, no, no.
- You called bob?
Phyllis!
- I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
It's was earlier today.
- Okay.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- You okay, baby?
- I'm good, baby.
- Oh, god.
Get a room, santas.
- Thank you, santa.
It's a little slippery
out here.
[rhythmic sound approaches]
- Oh, my god.
- Twelve drummers drumming.
Merry Christmas, Aaron.
Sing it away, boys.
www.tvsubtitles.net