You know, sometimes I wake up
in the morning and I'm just like,
bleurgh! I don't want to go to work today.
And then I remember these guys.
Get excited.
Get that tingly feeling in my chest like,
ooh.
I think it's safe to say
that we all feel that.
Morning team.
That's good.
They're busy.
-Morning Lizzie.
-Ah!
Alisha just called to say that she's
running ten minutes late.
-For...?
-Your 10 a.m. meeting.
Which will now be at 10:10.
How many people
do we have signed in today?
Four. Johann's in the toilet.
The rest are working from home.
Johnny, how many guys
are on the floor today?
[indistinct chatter]
[Hannah] Come in.
Sorry, mate.
Just firing off a big report.
[Hannah chuckles] And sent.
What can I do you for?
As you know, Hannah, we've been looking
at attendance across the branches.
Well, you certainly don't need
to worry about numbers here.
-So, Johnny from the warehouse?
-No, What?
Umm, ah, you know what?
I can see the resemblance,
but no, that's not him.
You were saying?
Well, we've reviewed our flexible work
practices,
and given the low attendance rates,
Flinley Craddick can no longer
justify the cost of our office spaces.
[Hannah] Yeah,
We're going to close the regional
branches and everyone will go remote.
-What?
-Well, the warehouse will still stay open.
Everyone else will work from home.
[gulps]
I think that's a bad idea.
[blinds banging]
-[anxiously]
-So what are we talking?
Home detention, house arrest?
What are we--
What are we talking here Alisha?
[Alisha] Please calm down. Hannah.
Those people out there
are like family to me.
And I won't let you throw
them out on the street.
No one is going out on the street, Hannah.
They're just going home.
Do you think we can run Australia's
fourth largest packaging company
from the isolation of our own homes?
We can't.
Your lease expires
at the end of next month so--
What if we bring everyone in full time?
That'll boost productivity, right?
If we bring everyone in, I guarantee we
can make a year's worth of rent
by the end of next month.
-$300,000.
-300,000?
Yes. Too easy.
How are you even going to convince
your staff to come in full time?
I won't need to convince them.
I'll just ask them.
Please, Alisha.
Please, please, please.
-Fine. I'll talk to the board.
-Yes!
Yes!
But if any of your staff members
complain about being forced
to come in full time,
you are not to blame it on head office.
Why would I do that? [scoffs]
Won't even mention your name.
[phones ringing]
That is Johnny from the warehouse.
What? Johnny, shame on you.
If there's anyone here
that doesn't actually work up here,
can you please leave?
Thank you.
[Hannah] Honestly, I don't know
what's gotten into you guys.
Not cool.
[theme music playing]
[car alarm bleeps]
[Hannah] Welcome, welcome.
Come on in. Pile in.
Yeah. Oh, there he is, Marty HR. Look out!
So exciting to see everyone
in the building all at once.
Yeah.
Great. Is that everyone?
We're one short. Do you want to wait?
Who is it? Lloyd?
Nah.
Firstly, may I say thank you very much
for coming in at such short notice,
and what an absolute pleasure it is
to look out and see
a room full of smiling faces.
Secondly, for those of you who haven't
met Sebastian, this is Sebastian.
Come on up.
Come on. Yeah.
Sebastian started with us last week
on a three month unpaid internship on loan
from McClay Business College.
And I think I speak for everyone
when I say it's nice to have
some new blood in the office.
[laughs awkwardly]
Some fresh blood.
[hisses]
[Nick] I started as an intern.
I was Sebastian.
She's been doing that vampire shtick
for over seven years.
[in vampire accent]
I want to suck your blood.
[awkward laugh]
-Can I sit… down Thanks.
-Yeah. Yeah. By all means.
[Hannah] And thirdly, the big news.
-Oh.
Er, It's a lockout, Lloyd.
As specified on the phone call.
-Yeah, I get that.
-[Hannah] Yeah, just let him in.
-But it's a lockout.
-Yeah, just let him in.
Yeah, we can wait.
-G'day.
-Hi.
Sorry... just
had to drive in from Woy Woy.
-So, yeah.
-[Hannah] Yep. Lovely.
-So the big news.
-[Nick] Oh, don't tell us the quiz is off.
-Oh, no.
-No, Nick, the quiz is not off.
[Hannah] The good news is...
As of today, we are all back
in the office full time.
[Lizzie] Yes!
[Greta] Wait. What?
[Lloyd] That's not good news.
No, I know.
This isn't the good news.
This is the bad news
that I forgot to tell you earlier.
The bad news. And get this.
Alisha comes in this morning
and tells me that head office are forcing
us to come back to the office full time,
effective immediately.
[disgruntled mumbling]
[Hannah] I know.
And she set new productivity targets.
$300,000 by the end of next month.
[Deborah] What?
And I tried to talk her back around but...
do you know what, though?
At least we've got each other
and a fully stocked fridge.
[Lizzie] Oh, no. The card declined
and so the order--
[Hannah] It will be stocked.
So, wait, what? What was the good news?
The good news is that now we can do
TGI Friday trivia quiz IRL.
What's IRL?
This is IRL. In Real Life.
[Hannah] As much as everyone loves being
here at work,
the reality is, [chuckles ] we have lives.
You know, people have homes and pets
and children and partners
that we'd rather be spending time with.
So yeah, it's frustrating.
And also even people that don't have some
or any of those things
because they've
sacrificed all of it for their career,
It is still frustrating.
I imagine.
...220 by 320 but for your product,
I think our bubble pouches would
offer more protection and that's--.
[loud space invaders noises]
[Nick] Sorry. What was that?
[noises continue]
Yeah. Could you just give me one second?
Sorry. Thank you.
-[alarm noises]
-Hey, what's going on with all this?
I am trying to find a distinctive chime
for this week's quiz.
-[noises]
-Yeah, cool.
I'm just trying to do my job
and close the sale.
That sounds like a Nick problem
and not a Lizzie problem.
Couldn't just put some headphones in.
No, Nick, I couldn't, because how could
I concentrate with that [loud noise]
-in my ear?
-Yeah.
How could you concentrate
with that in your ear?
-[klaxon sounds]
-I hate how you make me do this.
[Lizzie] Nick,
give me back my Tassie devil.
I'll give your devil back when you
stop making those annoying noises.
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
[Lizzie] Nick is a joke.
He is a mess around clown.
Sorry about that.
So, as I was saying, the bubble pouches.
Hello?
[Greta] The perks of coming to work?
Riling up Lizzie.
Watching Nick rile up Lizzie.
Flirting. Who doesn't flirt at work?
And sales.
Obviously very,
very passionate about sales.
[coffee machine steams]
[Hannah] Whoa, whoa.
This one--Whoa. [laughs]
Hola. Como estas?
[knocking]
-Yep.
-You want to see me?
[whispers] Close the door.
I'm promoting you to Productivity Manager.
You're in charge of making that 300K
and I'm in charge of staff morale.
Sort of like good cop, bad cop.
Yeah, yeah. Which one am I?
-Bad cop. Yeah.
-Bad cop.
-I need you to ride that sales team.
-Oh. Giddy up.
Can I expect a raise?
-[electronic voice] No, no, no.
-No...
But I do want you to come and see this.
-[Lizzie] Oh!
-[both laugh]
-I'm on the toilet.
-That's very clever.
[Hannah] Yeah, that's very clever.
[straining noise]
There's not enough fibre in my diet.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, don't get a haemorrhoid.
Don't get a haemorrhoid.
All right, that's that's…
300K. Make it happen. Yeah?
Yes, sir.
Please don't call me that.
She / Her, you know.
[Lizzie] I'm going to need you
to relinquish your chair please.
[Lizzie] I love a challenge.
Being challenged makes me feel alive.
Like I've got something to fight for.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's going on? Hey.
Oh. I am increasing productivity
in the workplace.
-By taking away my chair.
-By introducing standing desks.
Do you know about this?
[Lizzie] Sitting is the new smoking Nick.
-I thought vaping was the new smoking.
-Five.
Four. Three. Two--
I have a question.
When are the standing desks arriving?
You will simply be standing
at your old desk, Greta.
[Greta] But they're the wrong height.
[Lizzie] If you have a problem with my
plan, take it to H.R..
[chair rattles]
[Nick] Can I get my jacket back.
You can collect it from lost property
at the end of the day.
My chair was cold anyway, so...
[frame rattles]
[Hannah] Okay, TGI Friday IRL.
Let's just throw around some key
words, see what sticks. Yeah?
-Right.
-[Hannah] Like, er, togetherness...
and fun.
Family.
It's a pity we can't do a funnier
zoom background.
I feel like that might have been and gone.
Fun doesn't date. Err...
You're young, you're hip.
What do you do to have fun?
Um. Well, I sometimes will, like, order
food.
Food? Put it up. What else?
I mean, I sometimes listen
to music, I guess.
Get it up there.
Food, music. Love that.
-[office chatter]
-That's cool.
-[worker] Thanks very much.
-[Martin] No worries
[Lloyd] Hey.
Am I really contracted
to be here full time?
Um, yeah, If you signed your contract
more than three years ago, probably.
Is there some kind of travel subsidy
that I could get?
[Martin] Um, if you signed your contract
more than three years ago,
probably not.
Can I actually have my contract
printed out, please?
I would, but, the printer is down.
Might probably get on to that.
-Yeah, it's an error 65, I think, yeah.
It's a tricky one. 65.
[Lloyd] I am the head of IT.
Well, it's a department of one.
I'm it.
[clears throat] It, I.T. [chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[paper rubbish rustles]
[Greta sighs] Oh my God. Hey!
-Check this out.
-What?
[Greta] Looks like someone
selling office chairs today.
-[Nick] Oh, my God, that's my chair.
-[Greta] Mm-hmm.
[Nick] Why has she called herself
Dirty Diana?
I think it's time to ask Dirty Diana
a couple of questions.
Ask her to take a photo.
No, no, no video.
-In the car park.
-[keyboard clacking]
[notification bleeps]
-[Nick] Yeah, yeah. So basically the…
-[Greta] Yeah.
[Nick and Greta mumble]
-Yeah. So the different size of the boxes.
-Okay. That's good.
[Zoom call rings]
[Man] Martin my man, are you all right?
-Hey.
-Looks like you're trying to take a shit.
Yeah. Sorry.
Yeah, there's something going on
with our chairs.
Look, I um,
I just wanted to touch base
and just see how you guys
were tracking up there in Brizzy.
Are you not at home?
No. We're still in the office.
Where are you?
Did Alisha come in
and send all you guys home?
What?
Right. So I've been in touch with
Brisbane,
-Mm-hmm.
-and they have gone remote.
And Melbourne is following suit.
Interesting.
I'm assuming that Alisha
offered you the same opportunity.
If by opportunity you mean
a life sentence of home detention.
Solitary confinement. Sure.
So she did suggest that we
could go remote as well, right?
-Oh, I don't want to get
into semantics Martin.
Yeah, but that was an option?
That is a legitimate option?
What does semantics actually mean?
[mutters]
I'm just going to have
a little look at the definition.
[keyboard clacking]
Right. So you'll need to tell the staff.
Okay.
So I'm just going to leave that with you.
[electronic voice] Yes.
[Greta] I noticed she didn't set
a reserve for the auction.
Oh, that's an oversight. [chuckles]
[Hannah] Hey, guys.
Um, Just a little heads up.
Meeting room, five minutes. Yeah?
[muffled phone conversations]
Five more minutes of this then.
Sorry I'm late,
I got caught up downstairs.
-Where are all the chairs?
-Downstairs.
I'm selling them.
-Who approved that?
-The Productivity Manager.
Who's the Productivity Manager?
-I am, you know, bad cop.
-Get the chairs back, Lizzy.
[Hannah] Um...
Right, about half an hour ago,
somebody who will remain nameless
walked into my office
and accused me of lying.
Wow. Am I a liar?
Nope.
I'm a truth bender.
I'm a truth masseuse, if you will.
-What truth did you bend exactly?
-[Hannah] Nice, Greta.
Straight to the point. Love that.
So this morning, Alisha actually came in,
threatening to close down the office
and send you all home.
But, I... fought for your rights
and negotiated a deal
-in which we all get to stay.
-[all murmur]
-[Tina] Why didn't you tell us?
-Because I love you.
And I was protecting you.
[Lloyd] From who?
[Hannah] From yourselves.
You know, some of you might be thinking,
"Oh, yeah, I'd love to be at home".
You wouldn't. You'd hate it.
Deborah would self-harm
if she was stuck at home with the kids.
Isn't that right, Deborah?
Could do. Yeah.
And look at what's happened to Lloyd
since he's moved to Woy Woy.
[Martin] So, to be clear, you're the one
making attendance mandatory.
[Hannah] Your words, not mine.
Yeah, that attendance is mandatory.
[all grumble]
[Greta] And if we don't make the money,
we all go remote?
[Hannah] Defeatist attitude Greta.
But yes. That's correct.
-Come on.
-Crazy idea.
Should we just skip to the bit where we
fail and we can all just go home now?
I don't think anyone
really wants that. Do you?
[Nick] I am definitely a homebody.
I love cooking, I love gardening,
but I wouldn't want to commit
to never coming into the office.
There are things that I'd definitely miss.
[Greta] Well, it's complicated because
working from home makes a lot of sense.
More flexibility, more time to watch
YouTube videos of baby pygmy hippos.
But by going to the office,
there are things to look forward to.
You have that feeling of like,
yeah, I get to see everyone today.
[Lizzie groans]
[indistinct phone chatter]
Hey, Lizzie. What's up?
-You wouldn't get it.
-Try me.
I need to buy the chairs back but
I've just sold them to some clown for $3.
Oh, yeah, that was Nick.
[Lizzie] Nick!
I need to buy them back.
[Nick] Tell you what.
I'll sell them back to you for four bucks.
But under one condition.
What's the condition?
I get to be quizmaster.
[Lizzie huffs]
[hisses venomously]
-[hisses]
-[Greta] Oh, gosh.
[road noise]
[Stevie] Yeah, I don't know the ins and
outs of it, but I heard the guys upstairs
-are going home.
-[thud]
Wouldn't be devastating for us.
[lift dings]
[upbeat music on radio playing]
[Hannah] Coming back full time
might not appeal to everyone at first.
It's like they've been invited to a party
they don't want to go to,
but then they get there and they're like,
"I'm having the best time".
"Thank God Hannah made me come
to this party".
[jovial chatter]
Okay, let's put them in the circle
so they can all see each other.
[upbeat music playing]
-Hey, Deb! Quiz is about to start.
-I'll zoom in.
[mumbles] But it's IRL.
I'll be IRL, right out there.
Great. Well, see you on the zoom.
But I thought we could do it all
together like a family, you know?
-Like all together.
-Yeah.
Traffic's building up on the M1, so.
But I'm keen to zoom.
Oh. Okay.
[in Italian accent]
But it's a pizza party.
Come on. All the pizza.
Want a pizza?
I guess the advantage of zoom is
that you can still run your
funniest zoom background competition.
That is true.
[zoom feedback echoes]
Can everyone please mute themselves? Yes.
[feedback continues]
Everybody on mute now. Thank you.
[feedback stops]
Now, this week, I have decided
to let Nick have a go at being quizmaster.
So now I'm going to make him the host.
And I absolve all
responsibility forthwith.
Thank you. Lizzie.
Good luck everyone.
To help our company's bottom line,
How much did Lizzie sell
all our office chairs for?
A, $3, B, $30, C, $300, or D, $3,000?
-Clock's ticking.
-[buzzer noise]
[bright noise]
Oh, well done, Greta.
Thank you Quizmaster.
Which member of the office
goes by the online alias Dirty Diana?
Nick. They need to be questions
that everyone knows the answers to.
That wouldn't be a quiz.
-[Lizzie] You know what I'm talking
about, Nick.
-[quiz buzzers ding]
-Hey, baby girl.
Mason. Hey.
-I thought you were coming at five.
-I finished early.
[buzzers continue]
Okay. What best describes the new smoking?
Is it A, sitting or B, vaping?
-[Hannah making dance music sounds]
-Sorry, Nick, can you repeat the question?
It's just a bit loud in here.
-[Hannah laughs]
-[buzzers ding]
[singing badly]
[Hannah] What matters to me the most?
Is it the money?
Nope. Is it the power?
Nope. Most important?
The people.
I love my staff.
And I told them that today.
And to see their faces. "Hannah loves me".
And then to hear them say,
"We love you, Hannah".
Not with words, but…
Wow.