[Lizzie] Artificial intelligence
is changing the business landscape.
As productivity manager, I have invested
in a high tech, cutting edge AI product
that will save us thousands.
Unlike humans,
our AI bots don't question authority,
need the toilet, or have emotions.
So yes...
I am firing the cleaners.
[title music plays]
But listen, if you can up it by 200,
I'll throw in a pallet of 48 mils
-and some dividers at no additional cost.
-[lift dings]
[man] Things change. Circumstances change.
Right now, their sick,
we've got to get moving.
Mason, your sick nan isn't a reason
to rush in and have a baby.
[Mason] I don't get it, babe.
This is what you wanted.
[Greta] What I want is maybe to
do all the things I haven't done yet.
Like going to Santorini,
or getting a back tattoo,
or taking LSD. You know, I haven't.
I haven't been in a threesome.
I haven't been skydiving.
-And what about my work?
-[Mason] Okay, I love you.
I want what you want.
So let's just keep talking yeah?
[Greta] Yeah, later. Time and place.
[Alisha] I don't like your chances
of saving the office
with these numbers Hannah.
[Hannah] They are looking good.
Sales are steady Eddie.
Making cuts all over the place.
Snippety-snip.
Really? How so?
Turning off lights,
not cranking the old air-con...
-And layoffs of course
-You've made redundancies?
Yeah.
We are getting rid of two cleaners today.
Yeah, I don't think laying off
your part time cleaners
is going to help you meet
your targets Hannah.
Yeah, I agree,
and that is why I have...
fired Brian.
-Brian.
-Yep.
Brian last week laid him off.
Laid him right off.
-Brian is from warehouse accounts.
-[Hannah] Yep.
He sat over there.
So why?
He just sort of come
to the end of the road.
Wasn't doing his job.
Often tardy, just dead weight.
We're going to go down to the warehouse.
Make sure their accounting
needs are taken care of.
Ah, do you know? We've got it covered?
Deb's taking care of all accounts now.
-Yeah, but still, I mean, it's--
-Yeah, no, we'd better go down,
Have a little girls trip! Yeah.
-After you.
[vacuum bot hums]
-[Hannah] Um Lizzie,
We're just going to head down
to the warehouse, Alisha and I,
because I fired Brian last week.
-Wha-- Brian?
-Yeah.
So maybe you can give Stevie a call,
tell him that we're heading down...
to talk to him because I fired Brian,
I fired him.
[Hannah] Thanks, Lizzie.
[Lizzie] Brian died last Wednesday.
3:34 a.m. Cardiac arrest.
[Hannah] Ah, okay.
Oh, God. It's all happening down here.
You know what? We can come back.
-[Stevie] No. You're right, I can talk.
-[Hannah] Yep.
[Alisha] Oh, great.
I wanted to check in re Brian,
make sure
your accountancy needs taken care of.
Yeah, we're all good.
Deb said you could sort something, so...
Just like I said. So we can…
-Such a shame. He's such a nice guy.
-Yeah, look, redundancies are hard--
-Well said. Let's go.
Brian wasn't made redundant.
He passed away.
-What?
Oh, my God, he must have taken it
so badly when I fired him.
You said that he'd come
to the end of the road.
Yeah, I did, God,
I suppose it was two roads, wasn't it?
At the same time.
Like, what are the chances,
like getting fired and dying same day?
You know what?
Minute's silence for Brian?
[Hannah sniffs]
-Sorry about this Stevie.
[whispers] Is she gone?
[vacuum bot hums]
[Deb] I can't pick him up from judo.
Fuck off.
No, no. Not you. They've got this...
You know those
robot vacuum cleaner things?
[Lizzie] Mason, can you please sign in?
Well, then I shall have to do it
for you, again.
Hey. What's up?
[Mason] I was just feeling bad
about our conversation.
I've been thinking about what you said.
And you're right.
You're completely right.
You know, I, of course
I want you to feel like you've lived
a full life before becoming a mum.
So...
I'm happy for you to bring in
a friend of your choice.
Sorry. What?
Yes.
[gleefully]
I'm giving you your threesome.
That's what you took
from our conversation?
Yeah. Babe. I don't want
you to have any regrets.
[Mason] Listen, start thinking about who
you want to bring in,
because it's your treat.
It's your call. All right?
I love you.
I love you, too.
[Mason giggles] You're in shock.
Who doesn't listen now, huh?
[Alisha] And so I trust
that the mental health
of your staff has been taken care of.
Oh, I've created a culture
of resilience here so--
[Martin] I'll be conducting
a grief counselling session today
for those who wish to attend.
-That's great. Thank you Martin.
-Yeah.
It's really good to know
that everyone's in your safe hands.
-No worries.
[Hannah] Yeah, it's so good.
And I, to add to that springboard,
I'm going to throw... a wake.
[Hannah] Yeah, that's what families do.
And we're a Flinley Craddick family.
-And this wake's happening today?
-Yeah.
[Alisha] Okay.
Well obviously I would love to attend.
-Huh? It's it's very last minute.
-What time is it happening?
It's loose.
Uhm… I'--
I'll check with Lizzie,
but I think we said 2:00 p.m. Yeah.
The grief counselling is
running from 1 to 3--
3:00 p.m… It's 3:00 p.m... Yeah,
I got it mixed up.
Okay, 3:00 p.m.
I will see you all at 3:00 p.m.
-Can't wait.
-Thank you Martin.
-Martin. All good.
-Thank you. Hannah.
[Hannah] Thank you Alicia.
Thank you for your support today.
[door closes]
So we're throwing a wake now.
Yeah, I always was... Martin.
United front yeah?
Hey guys, I just want to have
a moment of your time.
As you know,
we lost one of our own last week,
-Brian… Hodge.
-Hodge.
Yeah, that's Brian Hodge.
Which one was Brian?
Ah, he was the one who sat next to...
-[Josh] Josh.
-[Hannah] Josh. Thank you.
And Josh is just...
-Me.
-Yeah, I know, obviously.
-He worked from home mostly.
-[Hannah mutters in agreement]
And was retired,
but, recently, he unretired.
Probably should have stayed retired.
[Martin] And I'll be in the meeting room
from about one o' clock,
for anyone who wants to come through
and process anything for grief counselling
just to get some support
or just talk things through.
[Hannah] Or in less depressing news,
I'll be celebrating Brian's life
at 3:00p.m. with a wake.
And I know he'd want you all
to be there because we were so close.
I just can't picture him.
I can. 'Cause he's always in my heart.
What he look like?
What did he look like?
It's hard to put into words.
-You made him a cup of tea last week.
-Did I?
-Oh, is he the tall, sad one?
-Yeah.
[Tina]
No, he was the short and smiley one.
-Yeah, that's what I meant.
-[Nick] What nationality is he.
Err, What sexual identity is he?
-Doesn't feel relevant does it?
-What did his voice sound like?
[Hannah] His voice?
[deep voice] I'm Bryan Hodge,
and I sit next to...
-Jack. Josh.
-Josh.
[Lizzie] I can send you a copy
of his driver's license
-if you need a visual ID.
-I don't need it.
-I don't need his license.
-Yeah.
But send it to me so I can sign off on it.
Sign off
on the late Brian's driver's license.
Yeah. So then I can distribute it...
to people
who don't remember what he looks like.
Could I please be on that email?
You're the only person
who's on that email, Lloyd. Yeah.
[Martin] There are some bosses
who respect the grieving process,
and there are some who throw an impromptu
wake for a dead staff member,
they can't remember,
just to prove a point.
Right. As you know, I love a party
and I know how to throw one.
But because I've got to focus
on my death speech.
-Eulogy.
-Yep.
I've decided to put together
a party planning committee.
And congratulations. You're it.
Why us?
Why not you?
So let's think headlines, bullet points.
What I'm thinking is it's got
to be moving, emotional and also "fun".
Quite the vibe.
They're all quite different vibes.
Yes, but why don't you think
about Four Weddings and a funeral?
It's got romance, comedy,
weddings, funeral, gay people.
So let's give Brian the send off
with all the things he loves the most.
I don't want to be on the party committee.
I understand that, but you're also the
oldest and closest to the end,
so I would
really love your buy in on this event.
Okay? Come on, guys!
I want you to be in charge of things.
Music, slideshow, decorations, food.
Yeah, it's a, it's a wake,
but I want people to feel a-wake.
[chuckles]
I want them to feel a-live.
At this point, I wish I was Brian.
I wish I could help out,
but obviously I'm not cool enough
to be on the party planning committee.
Remind me,
what's the criteria to be on it?
Is it, saddest life,
[phone dings]
...connections in the balloon industry?
[phone dings again]
[Greta] Oh, my--
-Have you found a third person yet?
-What?
No. I'm not-- No.
[Greta] Mason started sending through
options.
Nick Fletcher, Flinley Craddick
Oh. That's Claudia. She's our dentist.
[mouse clicks]
Hey Deb?
How do you make one photo melt
into another photo.
Melt?
You know, like when a photo bleeds into
another one
to create a kind of emotional...
Never mind.
-[papers rustle]
-[Lizzie] Lloyd.
-Deb.
-What's this?
The cleaning roster for the toilets.
I'm firing the cleaners,
so... we all need to chip in.
Umm, Lizzie, I see that you've rostered me
on for three afternoons in a row.
Can we even get out
with a couple of morning shifts
-before people have had lunch?
-No.
This will be enforced, Deb.
Or you’ll
soon find that they...
Will be doing your job too.
Hello, everyone. Hmm, Sadder.
[voice cracks] Hello, everyone.
-[Hannah voice cracking] Hello, Lizzie.
-Have you had a stroke?
No. I'm practising my feelings.
And the cleaning rosters
have been circulated.
Oh. Have you fired the cleaners then?
No, I'm just about to send them a text
and then block their number.
Okay. Don't.
I need a full house.
Let's invite them to the wake,
and then we can fire them after.
Nice.
Actually, it might be a good opportunity
for Alisha to see my ruthless side.
But-- but that's my job.
I'm bad cop.
Well, I'm chief of bad cops,
so this what's happenin'.
I really need this.
It's really ugly when you beg.
Don't do that.
[water cooler bubbles]
Oh, hi.
Um… My wife Kelly might be up for it.
-Sorry. What?
-You know, you're three way.
To be honest you'd be doing me a favour.
Since menopause,
I'm dead from the neck down.
[awkwardly] Oh, okay. Um...
Use it before you lose it.
[Sebastian] Yeah, it turns out Brian
ordered Mexican almost every single day.
He's a big fan of the chips
and cheesy pork tacos.
It's possibly what killed him.
[Hannah]
You know, Brian retired then unretired
and some people might say
it was because of the cost of living
and the pension not being liveable.
But for me, I think it's that he had to be
here in the office,
-[phone dings]
-...that he loved it.
-[Greta] Ugh!
-[Hannah] And my speech needs to...
honour his legacy.
[muffled] Brian was a man...
[Hannah] If I can't save this office,
then Brian died for nothing.
[loudly]
It's good. Needs a few more LOL's.
[Hannah] I have a dream.
[excitedly]
I have a team! I had a team.
[keyboard clacks]
Um...excuse me? We've got--
-Lizzie.
-Yeah.
[Hannah whispers] Come here.
Don't let the delivery drivers leave
because we want to keep the numbers up.
-Roger that.
-For the wakety wake.
Hey, I've also written your script.
Oh, no. I finished my speech.
-It's actually really good.
-No, no.
Your script for firing the cleaners.
You need to give them
specific reasons for their dismissal.
Hunchbacks. Too old…
-Poor English skills?
-Mm-hmm.
I can't say that.
You can't? Or you won't?
Both.
And I'm actually really good
at firing people, so I don't need it.
Okay, well, if you need back up...
-We're here.
-[vacuum bots hum]
Yep I don't.
Umm...
-I'm sure you've heard all about the...
-About what?
Oh, the…Mason...
What are you talking about?
[Hannah] Hey, Greta, you know what?
I was thinking a really, like,
respectful way to open the wake
would be if you did a Welcome to Country?
Oh. Umm, Yeah. No.
-Me?
-[Hannah quietly] Yeah.
Umm...I'll get back to you on that.
This is why progress is so hard.
[footsteps recede]
[both chuckle]
-I'll see you later.
-[Greta] See ya.
-Ow! There's a wall there.
-[Greta chuckles]
-[Nick] Watch out for that.
-Thank you.
Sorry, no one turned up.
[sympathetically]
Oh, God.
Brian.
He just loved Mexican food, didn't he?
-Um, I don't really--
-Yeah, we don't really know him
Yeah. So I was thinking maybe you guys
could stick around,
say a few words at the top of the wake.
Maybe, you know, like a warm up act,
maybe a Mexican wave.
Well, I'm Turkish German so I don't know--
-[lift dings]
- [Hannah] Yeah, That makes sense.
-Yeah, we probably gotta--
-'Scuse me. [Hannah mumbles]
[delivery man]…Just go.
Alisha.
-Hello.
-Thank you for coming.
Would have meant a lot
to Brian that you're here.
Come take a seat. We're about to begin.
These are the Lopez brothers.
The delivery peop--
-[Hannah] Do something with them.
And we've got a seat for you
down the front.
Um, everyone. Could we-- Oh.
[high pitched feedback]
Oh, Lloyd, can you fix this?
Can everyone just gather around?
Because we're about to begin.
Hello? Hello.
-[feedback continues and echoes]
-[Hannah] Worse.
It's on lead guitar setting.
Okay. Can you make it not on that?
Before we kick off,
I'd just like to thank you--
-[vacuum bot hums]
-Lizzie. Can we...
-[Lizzie] Yep.
-…stop these immediately, please?
I'd like to thank Alisha
for coming down to support the local
Rydalmere Flinley Craddick family.
Also, I'd like to kick it off with two
very special guests who knew Brian
almost as well as any of us.
The local delivery guys from
Lopez y Lopez.
[polite clapping]
[Hannah] Come on down.
Say a few words. Yeah?
-This ought to be good.
-Mm-hmm.
Brian was a loyal customer, um...
He he always used the app to pay,
and he left good reviews.
Anything you want to add?
No. You pretty much said it.
Welcome to Australia.
[polite clapping]
-Yeah. Absolutely beautiful.
-[lift dings]
[Hannah] What a touching tribute that was.
Thank you. And so well said.
-Hey
-[Greta] Hey.
[Hannah] Here we are at this sad
but celebratory occasion...
-[Greta] What are you doing here?
-[Mason] Did you get the pics?
-Yeah, can we not talk about this now?
-[Mason] I'm leaning towards the dentist.
[Hannah] What to say about Brian?
Um, he was short, but that smile, ooh boy!
Could light up a room.
Am I right, Tina?
Born on the 13th of July, 1957.
He was a giver, a donor,
some might say of organs.
[Stevie] If I die while I'm still working
here, please don't let this happen.
Free tacos, man. I'm into it.
[Hannah] Brian enjoyed driving.
All sorts of vehicles, cars, mopeds
and other learner approved motorcycles.
But the truth is,
we had the privilege of knowing Brian
because he had the opportunity
to come to work,
to this beautiful office.
I actually made him a cup of tea
last week, apparently.
Well said.
And now to think of a future without
this office, without our community.
I think this office gave Brian a purpose
and a reason to get up in the morning.
A reason for him to do his hair and...
put on his heels and his lipstick.
Yeah. R.I.P Brian, thank you.
[Applause]
[stereo clicks]
[♪ Boyz II Men: "End of the Road"]
♪ Although we've come
to the end of the road ♪
♪ Still I can't let go ♪
♪ It's unnatural
You belong...
[Mason] I'm just saying,
It's gonna be way less awkward
with someone you know.
So that's all I'm trying to say.
Just pick a friend,
Okay, you want a friend?
Then I choose Nick
because Nick is my friend.
[Mason scoffs] Nick?
I'm not gonna root your work husband,
-That's ridiculous.
-No, Mason, that's not what I'm saying.
I'm not gonna have sex
with beanpole Nick babe.
A threesome's two girls and a guy.
-[Greta] Oh, well
-What are you talkin' about?
...can we talking about
combination of genders?
Hey, Nick.
I'm not having sex with you yeah?
-[Greta] Mason…
-All right? So forget about it.
Us three. It's not going to happen.
[Hannah]
It's a wake, mate. It's a wake.
Hope you're happy, man.
You've ruined our threesome.
-I didn't think I--
-You're not even that hot.
[Nick] He's just joking around.
Just a joke.
We should-- We should probably go.
-We've got other customers--
-[Hannah] Show some respect,
-the man died.
-Yeah. We'll stay.
["End of the Road" continues]
♪ Although we've come
To the end…
I'm glad that you got to see
how close-knit our family really is.
[whispers] Psst. Hannah. It's firing time.
And you're right, Alisha,
if I want to keep this family together,
then I've got to make the tough calls.
-I don't think today is the best day.
-No, no.
Lizzie said you wanted to see us.
Uh huh, I did.
-It's so sad about Brian.
-Yes.
He was such a lovely man.
He remembered our son's birthday.
Did he?
Even bought him presents
because he knew we didn't have much money.
That is why I brought you here today.
[mouths] Do it.
To tell you…
that I have...
a little gift, a token of my appreciation.
-I know that you're old.
-[Lizzie] No, Hannah.
-You have to do this!
-And I know that carrying around those
heavy vacuum cleaners,
I mean, they can't be good for your
hunched backs, can they?
-Hannah, Thank you.
-So that is from me to you, that is. Yeah.
You are the best boss.
Oh, no, I don't.
I mean, it's been said, obviously.
Well.
You hear that?
That was "best boss". Best boss.
You are a terrible bad cop.
-Bye Hannah.
-Bye.
-See you Lizzie.
-Yeah.
[Hannah] Am I afraid
to make the tough calls? Absolutely not.
We already lost Brian.
That's one less wage to pay.
But was today the day
to start going on a sacking spree?
No, it's too soon.
Tragedy plus time equals comedy.
So in a few days' time,
when we're all laughing about today,
that's when I'll start firing people.
One for the road?
Thank you.
-C'mon, today was a crazy day.
-Yeah.
So the work husband thing?
Yeah, I said it once.
-I know,
-And he's never let it go, as a joke.
Don't worry about it.
I do. When's the wedding?
-Bye Nick.
-We gotta set a date.
Destination wedding. Santorini.
-What are we thinking?
-See ya.
Tina can come. She was up for it.
Yeah, I'm fully aware of that.
Should we invite Deborah's wife?
[laughter]
[Nick]
On a scale of one to freaking weird.
I'd say today was up there.
Definitely up there. [scoffs]
To Brian.
May your name never be forgotten...
again.
[title music plays]