Okay. Bye.
Everyone stop
what you're doing.
I have terrible news.
Dwight is no longer with us.
What?
He's gone, damn it!
He's been promoted
to VP of Sabre retail,
and he's staying
in Florida forever.
So... He's alive.
Yeah.
That was him on the phone.
He sounds wonderful.
Well, the way you said it
made it sound like he was dead.
How could I have been
more clear?
He had a massive stroke
of good fortune
and he is now
in a better place.
If Dwight's not coming back,
does that mean we can open
his treasure?
Uh...
You guys, we've gone over this.
There is no treasure.
When the team left
for Tallahassee,
Dwight told everyone
not to touch his treasure.
Don't touch my treasure.
Okay? You understand?
Obviously, he wants us
to obsess about it.
There's nothing in there.
Which is obviously what
he would want us to think,
making it the perfect place
to hide a treasure!
Oh, God, I'm Wallace Shawn
The Princess Bride!
I think that Dwight
wanted us to realize
that this conversation
among friends
is the true treasure.
That's not Dwight.
No.
I am dying to know
what's in there.
Yeah, I know, Oscar.
We all are.
But nobody's gonna open it.
You'd have to be insane.
Hi, hello.
Now carefully open the box.
It's a photo of all of us.
Oh, that's so sweet.
A dart?
Are you kidding me?
Who would put a poison dart--
Well, I mean, I don't know
that it's poison.
I mean, I just have to imagine.
God, I'm glad he's okay though.
Kinda sounds like
he deserved it,
opening another man's
treasure and all.
Wow!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Well, Mr. Ball,
it's been a pleasure.
Now give my regards to hell!
Dah!
All right!
Well swung, my VIP VP.
I am loving the chemistry
between you two.
I am so happy.
Dwight is gonna be working
alongside me.
We are a regular Archibald
and his man George.
I bet.
I'm excited.
Trick!
There's no such thing.
It's not even
a real English duo.
Ahh!
I just made you look
like the Goat of Dover.
And that doesn't exist either.
You think you're excited?
You should feel my nipples.
Boing!
Oh, that reminds me.
Little something from all of us.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you, Jim.
That's so thoughtful.
Fore!
- Oh, yeah!
- He doesn't even care.
Don't even care!
This is the last time
I'll ever see Dwight.
It's a weird feeling.
It's, um...
What's the word?
It's not bittersweet.
It's, uh...
Sweet.
Yeah.
Hey, man.
Selling cookies for Jada.
Want the same as last year?
Would if I could
and I can, so I will.
Put me down for one box.
Don't care what it is,
dealer's choice.
I'll put you down
for shortbreads.
Damn it!
Knock, knock.
Hey, it's Sasha's first year
in the troupe,
so I'm selling cookies for her.
- Anyway, would you like some?
- No!
- No.
- What?
I've been selling here
for five years.
This is my spot.
You can't claim territories.
This is the only place
I interact with people.
Can't you sell at...
Your church or barbershop?
Or... Chess club?
You know what?
It's your first time.
Let's split the office.
You can have sales,
the annex, creed.
And I don't know,
I'll just take, uh...
- Accounting.
- That's it?
Yeah, well, okay.
Thanks, Darryl.
Okay.
Great.
All I need is Kevin.
Dude buys more cookies
than everyone combined,
and then some.
When I first started
selling cookies,
he was a relatively thin man.
Not a thin man, mind you.
Relatively thin.
Hey, Lucy, I'm home!
Bobaloo!
- Oh, here, let me help.
- I got it.
It was so busy
at the store today.
Really good cheese samples.
I had, like, a hundred.
Irene hired me
as her live-in helper.
We met at the store launch.
I told her I was moving here
and I needed a place.
And it just sort of made sense.
I basically do
everything for her.
I run errands,
I do chores around the house,
I cook and clean.
Honestly, I don't know how
she survived without me.
When can I introduce you
to my grandson?
He's a wonderful swimmer.
Shallow end, deep end.
He does it all.
Well, today might be
kind of tough, Irene.
I have to talk
to my old boss Andy
and tell him I'm staying
in Florida.
Oh, what kind of tea is this?
Oh, I boiled some Gatorade.
- Oh.
- Ah!
In england, they put the holes
a little bit to the right,
you see?
We'll just chalk it up
to cultural bias.
If I may...
Try holding the putter...
Here.
With your wrists here,
your thumbs here.
- Oh.
- That's right.
Your little finger.
Would you like to buy
some cookies?
- Cookies, eh?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ oh, the springtime thinks ♪
♪ that it's the best ♪
♪ fall time thinks
that it's the best ♪
♪ cold time has
kind of a strut ♪
♪ and Valentine's thinks
that it's the best ♪
♪ but gather round, peeps,
I'll tell you the truth ♪
♪ nothing beats
the cookie season ♪
♪ that's the truth ♪
It's not
a scratch and sniff, Kev.
I know.
But sometimes you still
get a little something.
Hey, you tricked me.
You just wanted Kevin.
You're new to the game.
You learned a lesson today.
- See you next year, sport.
- No, no, no. It's not fair.
What if Kevin wants to buy
cookies from me?
- I do.
- See?
That doesn't mean anything.
Kevin, do you wanna
buy cookies from me?
Oh, I definitely do.
Huh.
Hit the road, Jack.
No, you hit the road, Jack.
Hey, guys, come on.
Don't fight over me.
Why don't we split the order?
It's only fair.
No, wait, no.
I'm buying, I make the rules.
I actually do want you
to fight over me.
I wanna be wined and dined
and... sixty-nined.
Ugh.
Metaphorically
sixty-nined.
Ew! Perverts.
No offense, Oscar.
Hop in.
We have places to be.
No rest for the wicked.
Ha ha.
All right.
So...
I guess this is it.
Well, Jim, I just wanna say
that we haven't always
gotten along.
And at times,
I've even hated your guts.
But...
Bye-bye.
I win.
- Good-bye, Dwight.
Robert! Race you
to the clubhouse.
Gentlemen's bet.
Whoo-hoo!
Well, he's Florida's
problem now.
Oh, let Dwight have his fun.
- Today will not be his day.
- What's that?
I'm gonna tank the Sabre store
at the presentation
to the board.
I thought you liked the store.
The store is lovely.
You created a wonderful space
to showcase our product line.
Great job!
Cheers.
Thank you.
But there's a reason
we sell our products online
and over the phone.
Have you ever used Sabre
electronics, Jim?
They're cheap.
They're unintuitive.
The Sabre store would work
if we adopted the carnival model
of leaving town
once everyone's wise to us.
Wow, when you put it that way,
I guess it does sound
pretty terrible.
I couldn't just kill
the project from the start.
Jo Bennett endorsed it.
Shame, though--
I did like Dwight.
Robert!
I'm gonna win!
Ha ha, I'm the gentleman!
Suck it!
Bravo, Dwight.
Very good.
Shame.
The math is simple, folks.
Deeper market penetration,
plus greater visibility,
- will raise Sabre...
- To the power of two.
How did that look?
I'm not just saying this.
That was the best thing
I've ever seen.
Told you.
When you guys do that whole
"power of two" shebang,
how about I pop up also?
I guess we'd have to say
"power of three."
Hmm, actually, you know what?
Yeah! That actually works.
You'd spin-off right,
I'd spin off--
You know what?
That is a great idea.
Cathy, write that down
and print it out.
It's gonna make some really
good toilet paper.
All right.
There he is.
What are you doing here?
I thought I got rid of you.
Can I just talk to you
for one quick second?
What, your stylist ran out
of messy spray?
Um, actually
it's for your own good.
I think we should--
You wanna do something
for my own good?
Turn around,
walk out that door,
do not stop till you get
to Scranton,
find my cell phone charger,
mail it back to me,
and then go to hell!
Nice!
Hey, Halpert,
anyone ever tell you
you look like Wooly Willie?
Silence.
I'm just trying--
I know what you're
trying to do.
I don't want it.
But your face does look like
the guy from "Operation."
It's the same guy.
- That's the joke I made.
- That's not--
- Different guy.
- You know what?
I just think
you should know--
That you look like
the world's tallest hobbit.
Well, I tried.
You saw it.
So it's on the record.
I have a plane to catch.
Can you help me?
I'm trying to make
a video chat with Andy.
Just open the program
and type in his username.
Can you just do it?
Here, type in your password.
Erin123.
That's a terrible password.
And you don't "make a video
chat"-- You "video chat."
All right!
Hello!
That's so weird.
There's something wrong
with my laptop.
Oh! I fixed it.
Oh! Now mine's broken.
Hang on.
Oh, there we go.
Aghh!
He said "I did like Dwight"?
He's gonna fire him.
No, no, I think it was more
like, you know,
"I liked him,
but I don't any more,
'cause he did a bad job.
So I'm definitely
gonna yell at him."
Robert doesn't talk like that.
You have to stop Dwight
from doing this.
I tried.
He will not listen.
Did you actually
try your hardest?
Yes.
My pretty hardest.
Look, you haven't dealt with him
in a while, all right?
He's like Super Dwight.
It's like he's been bitten
by a radioactive Dwight or som--
- Stanley, back me up.
- Don't talk to me.
Stanley's very upset
that we're leaving Florida.
But he would back me up.
If Dwight's about to get fired,
you have to tell him.
Just get the words out,
that's all you can do.
Okay.
All right.
What's a skinny guy
like Toby know about cookies?
You can't trust him to
understand the wants and needs
of the thick man.
Maybe Toby from two years ago.
- Yeah.
- That's true.
If I have a question
about my cookies at midnight,
who am I gonna call?
Darryl.
Toby's probably in bed
with some model.
Thank you.
I'm not gonna comment
on my personal life.
Look, I need this.
Your daughter is
a pretty little girl.
Let her go door to door.
You think people are gonna
buy cookies from my...
Chubby daughter?
Baby, if you're watching this,
you're not chubby.
You're beautiful.
Daddy's just gotta sell
some cookies.
And we're also gonna
exercise more.
It's gonna be fun.
Oh, you know what you have
to do to decide?
You need to make them
do things for you.
And, like, buy you things.
Or have them sing that song
that the frog does
in Looney Tunes.
Make them kiss each other.
Make them kiss me!
Eww.
Yes! This is too tan.
This right here.
- No!
- This is a tan spot.
I don't buy it.
That is a freckle.
That is not a tan.
I'm gonna have to inspect it in
person when you get back here.
I want you looking
totally puertoriquena
when I see you.
Well, Andy,
I'm not coming back.
- What?
- I have a job here.
I work for an old lady.
Hello!
Andy?
Yeah, that's awesome.
That's great.
♪ oh, baby, telephone ♪
♪ and tell me I'm your own ♪
This is tough.
'Cause Darryl, you sang better
and you dance better.
But Toby has
that indescribable quality
that makes a star.
I think I've reached
my decision.
I have decided...
That you guys are gonna
keep doing things for me.
No, no, no.
It's not worth it.
- No.
- No, it's not worth it?
That's too bad.
'Cause I was feeling
particularly hungry this year.
Yeah, okay, so what--
You'll buy 40 boxes?
Hungrier.
50?
You're not talking...
Triple digits.
Oh, yeah, I'm talking
triple digits.
Again.
♪ hello, my baby,
hello, my honey ♪
♪ hello, my ragtime gal ♪
Showtime.
- Dwight.
- You again?
Gosh, I keep throwing you away,
you keep flying back.
You're like
an amish return-stick.
Okay, great, listen to me.
No, no, I know.
Will you just let me tell you
one thing, please?
Yes, you may tell me one thing.
Great!
Wait, do you wanna
borrow money?
Listen to me.
Robert is going to veto
the Sabre store.
Jim, come on.
Dwight, he's gonna kill
the store.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then I'm pretty sure
he's gonna fire you for it.
Wait, he's gonna kill
the store,
- and he's gonna fire me.
- Yes.
- That's two things.
- Dwight, please.
Nice try, Jim.
Your pranks have never worked
in the past,
and they're not gonna work
today.
Okay, first of all,
they've mostly worked.
You know what, you might
wanna get to the airport.
It's gonna take you a long time
to get through security
with all those beauty products.
- Bye!
- Dwight, come--
Nothing is gonna stop me.
That is the mark
of a great man--
Unstoppability.
Dunder Mifflin...
the farm, Mose.
All those things.
Vanish in my rearview mirror.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a date with destiny.
And from what I hear,
she's a-- Oh!
- Help!
- Shut up.
Oh, gross!
Don't lick my hand!
God, why is there
so much saliva?
All I had to do
was think about pie,
and my salivary glands
did the rest.
- Nah!
- What, what, what, what?
- Oh, my appendix.
- I'm sorry.
- My wound hasn't healed yet.
- Oh, man.
- I'm so sorry, I forgot.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Dwight!
Where the hell is he?
I cannot do this without him.
I don't know.
He's not picking up.
Oh, look like shnoot's
a no-show.
Guess he wasn't Vice President
material after all.
But I am.
Put me in, babe.
I've got the info down
backwards, forwards,
and doggy-style.
I'm your man.
Right, let's begin then.
Ladies and gentlemen,
allow me to introduce the Vice
President of Sabre retail--
Mr. Todd Packer.
'Sup?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just dealing
with Erin's stuff
since apparently
she's not coming back
and she didn't bother
to tell anyone.
We knew.
Ryan told us.
Ryan, why didn't you tell me?
Thought you checked my Tumblr.
You never update it.
Well, I updated it.
Does anyone else
think this is weird?
And, like,
kind of uncool, actually?
To leave us
without a receptionist?
We'll find another
receptionist.
I mean, that's easy.
We'll be fine.
Hup, hup, hup!
What are you doing?
- I was trying to go--
- Get up, get up.
Okay, okay!
All right?
I'm not gonna let you by.
Then you know what?
I'm gonna just have to run
right through you.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Are you really revving up?
You know that doesn't work.
Jackie chan!
Go.
Hi, this is Alex.
And this is Sam.
Kevin can't come
to the phone right now
because he's busy...
With us.
Perfect!
Now people will think
I'm doing hot girls all day.
I don't know, man, they might
think we're drag queens.
Yeah, I don't know why
you picked names
that are also guys' names.
Okay, now who do I ride
to the kitchen like a pony?
Don't make me be your pony,
Kevin.
- Forget it, man.
- What do you mean?
I'm out.
So is Toby.
This may be wrong,
but there's a limit
to what I would do for my child.
Yeah, I have my dignity too.
I refuse to be
another man's horsey.
No, guys! Stop!
You have to sell me cookies.
I'll do anything!
♪ Hello, my baby,
hello, my honey ♪
I'm even gonna kiss Meredith.
That's what--
That is--
Hmm.
That's... so good.
What are you doing?
No!
- No, no, no!
- This will end now.
- No! This is dangerous.
- Thunderslam!
- Arrgh!
- Oh!
Anything else you need
to talk about?
Nope.
That was it.
Once again, it's showtime.
What baffles me
is how you could
take a perfectly good idea,
which the great Jo Bennett
rightfully signed off on,
and then utterly botch it
in execution.
If I may speak to that,
I have only been Vice President
of this project
for the last half hour.
So the man you want
is Dwight Schrute.
I don't see Dwight.
He clearly had
the infinite wisdom
to stay as far away from
this clown show as possible.
Whatever you do...
Do not blame Todd packer.
It is not his fault.
Blame his upbringing,
his parents.
The society that would mold
this idiotic creature.
Fire the employee, yes.
But not the man.
You may not cancel his soul.
That was never on the table.
Are you kidding?
She's the queen of the whole
friggin' magilla!
And yet, Todd,
it's you who's fired.
What--
I can't get fired.
I'm an institution.
I have been at this company
for 20 years.
How many of you have been here
that long, huh?
Hey, hey!
They're back.
Hey! Wait, Dwight,
what are you doing here?
I thought you were supposed
to be in Florida.
Yeah, the crazy thing
about that
is, um--
Wow, you look great.
- Did you lose some weight?
- Thank you.
For someone who actually
notices this.
No, I didn't lose weight,
but I started using my make up
to contour my face
to look skinnier.
Actually...
- Hey, good to have you back.
- Good to be back.
- Hey, stranger!
- Hey!
- Oh, I missed you.
- I missed you.
I'm going to Florida to get Erin.
I forgot to check my email.
It's crazy, right? It's just,
when she said she was leaving...
I thought...
You're about to close four tabs,
are you sure you want to continue? Yes.
I am sure.
Ahh! Slow computer!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net