So you'll have those reports
on your desk by 3 p.m.
They were meant to be on my desk by 9 a.m.
And it still can be...
9 a.m. Standard Pacific time.
Just get it to me ASAP okay?
No problem. Alisha. Okay. See you later--
-I've got one more thing.
-Yeah.
-We both know what day it is today.
-Do we?
-It's Melbourne Cup day.
-Today?
Yeah, you know it is.
Oh, actually yeah I was,
I was forgetting but now I'm...
It is coming back to me.
Yeah it is today isn't it?
Well as you know, head office has a strict
policy not to celebrate Melbourne Cup.
Yeah, it's a quite a new policy isn't it?
It's important policy for obvious reasons.
That is why we won't be celebrating
Melbourne Cup day.
-Good, just making it clear.
-Okay. Bye Alisha, see ya later!
She knows.
She has to say that every year.
I have to agree every year.
You know, we do the corporate dance,
blah, blah, blah.
And I know we've got targets, but when
it comes down to it,
it's the "Race that stops the nation"!
Who is ready?
-Me.
-He's ready.
-Anyone else?
-[phone rings]
I'll get you later.
[theme music playing]
[Lloyd] I love Melbourne Cup day.
I organise a sweep every year.
Obviously gambling is a very serious
and complex issue, but,
you know, Cup day
is just a fun day for the whole family.
-Hey, can I have King's Landing?
-Oh, that's one of the favourites.
-I know.
-What are you doing?
-It's luck of the draw.
-Bingo. King's landing. How lucky is that?
How would you feel if I reached in
and grabbed some of your cake?
Don't touch the cake.
Nobody touch the fucking cake.
[Deborah] I got put on cake duty.
So I palmed it off to the wife and kids.
And they spent three
hours on it last night.
-Greta.
-[Greta] Ah, just a moment.
Greta, Greta.
Sorry. I'm going to have to call you back.
[Hannah] Oh, you weren't
in the middle of something were you?
Big day today.
Everybody loves Cup day,
-Do they?
-Yeah.
And with Danny coming down actually,
and "F on the F"...
-"F on the F"?
-...Fashion on the field.
Quite a big day for me.
So I want to empower you
with a business opportunity.
And that opportunity is finishing
the business strategy report.
-When you say finishing…
-It's a WIP…
An early stage WIP.
-And when it due?
-3:00 PM
-When was it due?
-Irrelevant.
But if you achieve this task,
you will earn an almost full bottle
of, was it prosecco or champagne?
No, that's,
that's Australian sparkling wine.
And some brie.
[phones ringing]
[Hannah] Today is very special because my
best mate Danny,
down from the Brizzy office,
is coming to celebrate Cup Day.
He does it every year.
The office bloody loves him.
Okay, I'm just going to tell you.
Umm, ten years ago, we made the pact
that if we were still single at age 40,
then we'd get married and settle down.
And he turned 40 two weeks ago, and...
I just happened to have two
tickets to a moonlit cruise.
So, yeah, maybe I'll bring
the conversation up tonight.
No, ninety's the best I can do.
We only punt on Melbourne Cup day
Not on the prices…
[muffled shouting] The gates are back
and they’re racing in the Cup!
-[lift dings]
-[Nick] I could send you those by...
[excitedly] Legs Akimbo
has the early lead.
Wonder Boy two lengths back
as they approach the bend.
Oh no.
It's Golden Shower in front. 400 to go.
But ladies and gentlemen,
here comes Wonder Boy.
[excitedly]
Esky drops back as the pace picks up.
Weirdo Woman drops a shoe
and her race is done.
But who's this? There's 200 to go.
Last stretch. It's Sticky Fingers.
[Danny] Oh, no!
She's overtaken by Wonder Boy now.
[Hannah] But I think Sticky Fingers
is making a late break!
No. no, no, Wonder Boy's ahead.
-But it's Sticky Fingers by a nose!
-[both laughing]
-How the fuck are you mate?
-[poshly] Ah, a little parched!
[Danny] Where's the beats?
-[Hannah] Good question. Actually.
-[Danny] That's bad form on your end.
Hey, can you chuck this crab
in the fridge for me Elizabeth
when you get a sec?
[Hannah] Ah! So good to see you, mate.
Here is to F on the F,
best suited and best dressed.
Jeez, I hope we win.
Come on. Never stood a chance, did they?
What is the prize this year?
Oh, it's not a big deal.
Just a moonlit cruise.
-What, on the Harbour?
-Parramatta river.
-Oh, nice.
-Yeah.
And I've also organised
a special little bottle of something.
Of course she has.
What, what, what variety of beverage
are we talking?
-A little tequila.
-Senorita, Si, sil vous plaît!
Merci, de nada.
[intense laughter]
-[Danny splutters]
-[Hannah] You right?
[Greta] It's not the worst thing to be
locked away from the chaos of Cup day.
It's nice to have some separation
from Hannah...
and Danny.
Especially Danny.
-[Hannah] We should take a selfie.
-Yeah, up higher, That's good.
-Okay.
Oh, Lizzie, you're just in the back.
Can you...
Can you just duck down?
I'm at my workstation. Working.
Yep. Can you work and duck down?
[mumbles]
Okay.
Yeah, we're still getting
the top of your helmet.
-Come on.
-Yep.
-Just married.
-Huh?
What? No. I'm kidding.
Okay, do a hot one.
-[camera snaps]
[Hannah] Stay still...
[Lizzie] Hannah is not herself today.
Or any other day
that she begins drinking at 9 a.m.
-[loud dance music playing]
-Yeah, absolutely. We'll get--
Yep. Thank you.
[Hannah and Danny laughing]
[Danny] All right, guys, musical chairs.
Come on.
Get involved. Who's keen?
[Hannah singing]
♪ I could teach you but I'd... [mumbles]
No. Go on.
♪ And they're like
it's better than yours ♪
[Danny] Hey, Nicky.
I know you want to play. Come on, mate
[Nick] Can I join you?
[Greta] What?
Not loving the entertainment?
It's like footy teams gone maggot
and wrote a rom com.
-[Greta] Oh cute.
-[Nick chuckles]
[Greta] Okay, What time do you think
Hannah loses her shoes this year?
[Nick] Oh 4:15
when she takes them off to play limbo.
-[music stops suddenly]
-[Greta] Oh, okay.
I'm gonna go earlier pre-race 2:35 p.m.
[loud music continues]
What we talking? 20 on the nose?
[Greta] Or we could specify shoe location
for the quinella and an extra 20.
We feeling confident are we?
Yeah, I'm gonna take a safe punt
and go toilet cubicle.
I'm thinking car park next to the bins.
-Outside bet?
-Yeah.
-Bold call.
-Right call.
[Greta chuckles] Okay, we'll see,
-Who are you dressed as?
-I'm Bart Cummings.
Whose Bart Cummings?
You know he's, the horse trainer.
-[Martin] G'day mate.
-[Lloyd] G'day Martin,
-You want to get in on the sweeps?
-Oh, nah.
-No one's meant to be gambling at work,
-[phone chimes]
I know it's kind of a tradition...
[Hannah] Danny,
which of these selfies should I post?
That one? Nope.
-Nope.
-[Danny] Hey Hannso mate,
I've got some work to do.
Can I borrow a little desk and a computer?
Work! Come on mate, It's cup day.
No it's just a little report,
a couple of emails and I'll be done.
You know how it is.
-Righto Mark Zuckerberg.
What have we got?
God, it all looks a bit busy.
-You wanna just hang in with me?
-No, Lizzie's desk is free.
[Hannah] Oh, yeah. Didn't even see it.
-That's sweet? Thank you.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-Hello.
-How's work going?
[laughs]
Oh, I can't get anything done
with you around.
That's the plan.
All right,
can I get off this phone call now?
-But we can stay on the line.
-I gotta get this bloody work done.
-All right, you go, you go.
-Love you, love you.
-See you soon.
-Yeah.
Love you. Yeah.
[Lizzie] Umm… What are you doing?
Huh?
-Oh, working,
-Yes, at my workstation.
-Yeah. I got the boss's permish.
What?
Yeah. Go and take it up with her.
[Danny] Your mouse sensitivity
is way too sensitive too, by the way.
You won't be having my keyboard
or my screen,
so good luck
doing any high definition work.
Okay.
You need to chill out.
I'll be like, ten minutes Lizzie.
-That's ten minutes too long.
-Jesus.
[Lloyd] Danny.
-Great to see a man at reception hey.
-What?
Shattering the glass ceiling.
Hey, do you want in on the sweeps?
-Ah, yes, I do actually.
-Pick a horse, any horse.
Oh, give us Tutankhamun mate.
Oh, yeah. Good choice. Yeah.
Late money. You could pick that.
Come on, I'll buy you a beer.
-Would you drink it with me, though?
-Yes. Yeah, of course I will.
You mean we'd sit
and drink the beer together?
Yes, mate.
Here. Grab it. Get it for me.
[Lizzie] I know when I'm not being
appreciated.
So I have decided to apply my
skill set elsewhere for the day.
[Lizzie coughs]
-Lizzie?
-Is, umm, is this normal?
Your men over there
slacking off on the job?
-Oh, they're just having a break.
-How long have they been on break?
I don't know.
Well, as productivity manager,
I'm more than happy to step in
and say something, if that's--
Oh, yeah, we're all good.
Here if you need me.
[Danny] You haven't eaten anything.
You've just been smashing booze.
-[Hannah in a posh accent] …bit of crab!
-_[Danny Ready?
-Here you go, oh.
-[both chuckle]
Do you think tonight's the night?
-I don't want to think about it.
-He's into her right?
…two seconds, alright, come here then!
[Hannah squeals with delight]
Come on.
-Noogie, noogie, noogie, noogie!
-No, no! Get off, get off!
If you want to hook up with someone,
I don't think you put them in a headlock.
[Hannah] Hang on.
The quicker I finish this,
then we can play limbo.
No, no, no, keep the shoes on.
-Keep it on, keep it on, keep it on.
-Come on Hannah!
-[Nick shouts] Hannah!
-Oh, just...why would you do that?
-It was nearly 20 bucks richer.
-[Nick] Sorry, different Hannah.
-Here if you need.
[commentator] We're up to race four at
Flemington,
as we settle in to the biggest day
in the Australian racing calendar.
-Seven minutes thirty.
-Sorry?
That's how long this little coffee break
has been going on for.
-It's morning tea.
-Yeah, well, it's after midday, mate.
So nice try, pal. Not on my watch.
Everything all right?
Well, I think it's time for these boys
to break up the Tea Party, don't you?
-Come on, everyone back to work.
-Lizzie, mate.
Yeah?
Not your job to tell my staff what to do.
Look, Stevie. I get it.
You want to be a good cop.
But if you want this place
to run efficient--
If you want this place to run efficiently,
you're going to need a bad cop.
And that is a role
that I'm more than happy to play.
Don't you worry.
-[phones ring]
-Tina.
-Holy hell.
-Uh oh, look out!
Hottest bird in the office.
[laughs loudly]
-[Danny] Lloyd gets it.
-[Lloyd laughs] Yeah.
[Deborah] Talented niece
you've got there, Tina.
Isn't she just?
-What's this do?
-Push the button and find out.
-[Danny] Holy shit.
-[Sebastian] That's awesome!
You know what? I got a feeling
it's going to be me and you on that
little moonlight cruise tonight, m'lady.
-[Sebastian] Wow.
-[Danny] Look out!
[Danny] She's winning.
[Lloyd] Yeah!
[Danny] Now that's a fascinator!
[Tina]
…and thanks so much for your business.
Have a great week.
Okay. Bye.
[singing] Tina. Cha, cha, cha.
Tina. cha, cha, cha.
Tina, can we just have
a quick online sales meeting?
-Yeah, sure.
-Look, number one, amazing hat.
-Thanks.
-Love it. Incredible.
Number two, this is so hard for me to say,
but I don't think you can wear it
on fashions in the field.
Okay? Why?
Well, because you didn't come
to work wearing it.
It's like a technical disqualification.
Like, absolutely heartbroken for you.
But yeah, it sucks, but them's the rules.
Who complained?
-It was anonymous.
-Was it anonymously Tina?
Point is, there's no established rules
for fashion on the field.
We can't just disqualify Tina
because she's got an amazing hat.
It's an okay hat at best.
At worst, it's a toy bird from a $2 shop
stapled to a headband.
[Danny] Three, two, one. Lift off!
[Hannah laughs loudly]
[Danny shouts gleefully]
God, he's a crack up isn't he?
[slurs] Oh! Isn't he just the best?
Hey, maybe you should stop drinking.
-I'm not drinking.
-I just saw you take a drink.
Oh my God.
-The state of Hannah's paperwork.
[voice] Yoo hoo.
Oh, is that a floating tequila bottle?
I wonder what comes next.
-Me!
-[both] Ah.
-Hi. Oh, my feet are killing me.
-Do you want a seat?
Yeah, I will.
[drunkenly] I just wanted to ask
a little bit of advice here.
Let me put this down.
Umm, obviously Danny and I
are really into each other.
-[Nick] Yeah.
-Okay. Massive.
So I was just wondering, like, do you
think I should try to make a move now,
or, like, pash him later in the toilets?
Oh, options, erm...
Hey, maybe, maybe you should take
some time, sober up a bit,
have a little think before doing anything.
-Yeah, I like that.
Ah… cake!
Oh yum! Yeah. Thank you Deb.
[pallet truck whirs]
Whoa! Lizzie, what are you doing?
Listen, Jimmy
-It's Johnny
-Whatever.
Look, you may think you have what it takes
to help Stevie run this joint,
but from what I have witnessed,
you are a joke.
All right.
Consider yourself warned.
-Changes afoot.
-Whose foot?
Mine.
Oi, Stevie...
[Lloyd] Okay, ladies and germs,
it's time for fashions on the field.
-[staff whoop]
-[Lloyd] Yeah!
Now, just a heads up.
Our contestants will be competing for two
awards, best suited and best dressed.
And both will be receiving tickets
to the Parramatta River cruise.
Oh! Late entry.
Welcome back Hannah.
Very good.
-You're blind.
[Lloyd] So, by way of applause,
let's find our winners.
First up, Deborah!
[Staff cheer]
[light applause]
[Lloyd] Very nice.
Very nice. Next up is Danny.
[Hannah cheers loudly]
-It's embarrassing. It's embarrassing.
[Hannah] Take it off!
-[more applause]
-[Lloyd] Yes!
[Danny] Just havin' a laugh, couldn't give
a shit!
I would.
[Lloyd] Ah, who's next?
[Hannah] Martin.
Martin, do you want to have a go?
Come on. You've got a nice suit on.
-Take it off.
-[Martin] No, thanks.
[All] Take it off. Take it off.
-No, no, Lloyd...
-[Danny] Get your old boy out!
-Take it off.
-[Danny] Get it out!
-No!
[chanting stops rapidly]
[Lloyd] Okay. Next up, it's Tina.
-Here she is!
-Yay Tina!
[all applaud]
[all cheer loudly]
That is bloody good!
A hat that moves.
And then. Hannah.
[polite applause]
[drunkenly] Sorry not, not Tina.
I haven't got a dead bird on my head.
Sorry, I didn't kill anything.
Just the vibe! [chuckles]
[Lloyd] Okay, well...
so I think we know who our winners are,
obviously.
It's Danny and Tina.
-[applause]
-Thank you everyone. Thank you.
Come on bring it in.
[Lloyd] You've won a cruise on the
gorgeous Parramatta river!
-Congrats
-Another one under the belt.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, where should we go
for that drink tonight?
Yep. Lizzie, I reckon it's time
you headed back upstairs.
Why did someone ask me
to come back with something?
-Yep.
-Yeah?
Yep. They did, they did.
It's all gone to hell up there
without you, mate.
All the same,
I've got a job to complete down here
so they can just sit in chaos and wait.
Yes, except you don't have a job
to complete down here,
so step away from the forklift.
-Let it go.
-Fine
-[forklift starts up]
-[Jonny] Hey wait!
[Lizzie] Oh, boy. Excuse me.
-Coming through.
-[Stevie] Lizzie, what are you doing?
-[Lizzie] I know what I'm doing!
-[Stevie] Jesus, Lizzie!
-[forklift engine roars]
-Stay back. Are you all right?
-[Stevie] Get out of the forklift!
-[Lizzie] Get out the way!
-[Jonny] Chill out, chill out, chill out.
-[Stevie] Lizzie stop!
Stop! Keys, now!
What is wrong with you mate?
[Lizzie] Your accelerator pedal is way too
sensitive by the way!
[Stevie] Jesus Christ!
[Danny] Oh mate, I'm nervous.
[radio] What an absolute honour
and privilege it is to say…
-[Hannah] I'm nervous.
-[Deb] Fucks sake!
[radio] …is race number seven.
The Melbourne Cup.
[Hannah] So I bought Tina's
river cruise ticket
so we could still go together tonight.
Oh, Hey. You can have mine.
Yeah. I don't need it anymore.
I got, I got a dinner date on tonight.
You can have that.
[disappointedly] Oh.
Okay. Oh. Who, who with?
Oh, just this this
this chick I met online.
She's super cool. Early days.
I mean, we're not getting married
or anything.
-No.
-But if we do. Best man?
-Yeah.
-[Danny laughs]
Ha. Wow. What, um...
She Sydney based?
-Yeah.
-What's her name?
-Maryanne.
-The full name?
[Hannah] Maryanne Connors.
What have we got?
Ah!
Sales assistant. Embarrassing.
You know who doesn't do Pilates?
People that don't piss their pants.
-[TV] …and the gates are back!
-[Danny] Here we go!
-[shouting, cheering]
-[Danny] Out the way, Coming through!
[shouting, cheering]
[muffled shouting]
Relationship? Heartbroken, but eyes open.
Honestly. Diagnosis not a threat.
[TV] …Here trackside, high emotion at
Flemington, a day of racing…
-[Nick] That sucks.
-[Greta] Yeah.
[TV] …A cracking day.
The race is over for another year...
Did I miss it? Oh no, who won?
[Sebastian] At least the horse died
doing something it loved.
That's true. It's still a bit sad, though.
[TV] A sad end for Tutankhamen.
But let's not let it take away
from Hello Kitty.
-A great win…
-Wait a minute. Did they say Hello Kitty?
That's my horse. I've never won anything.
[gleefully]
Oh my God. Have I won all of that money?
[sadly]
Oh. Oh, that's so sad, though, isn't it?
-Bring it in, mate.
-Oh, bye Danny.
-Hey, I'm off everyone.
[Lloyd] See you Danny!
Thanks for the best day ever.
-[Lloyd] See you next year mate.
-[Danny] See you next year.
Hey, how are you guys going?
-What's happening?
-Your report's almost done.
Hmm? Oh, yeah… Great.
[Lizzie] Well Hannah, I found them.
Lizzie. My saviour.
[Nick] Where Did you find those?
Oh, umm...
-The bathroom
-[Greta] Yes!
Oh nothing well done for finding them.
That's awesome.
[uncomfortably] Ah...
I do not feel good.
-I'll take you to the loo.
-Yeah.
Can you just hold my hair back.
I just washed it.
Yeah, of course I can.
[Hannah] Oh, too much cake
[Lizzie] And tequila.
[Nick] It's weirdly sweet.
[Greta] I know.
Okay. Pay up.
[sighs]
Thank you. Loser!
[Hannah] Run, Lizzie! Run!
[Lizzie] Lose the shoes.
[Hannah] I'm not losing the shoes.
I already lost them once today.
-Oh, no.
-[loud music and partying]
Lizzie, we missed it.
The party ship has sailed.
Worry not. How does karaoke sound?
Well, it sounds [vocalizing] great. Yeah.
Go on.
-I'll book your favourite room.
-Yes, please.
-Hey, can we do "Stumblin’ In"?
-No. No duets tonight.
I think this is my time to shine,
you know?
Okay, let me get a couple of solos out,
and then we'll do Stumbling In. Okay.
[Lizzie giggles]
-[singing] ♪ Our love is alive. ♪ Yeah?
-Yeah, yeah.
[vocalizing together]
[theme music playing]