[Nick] Oh, morning, Lizzie.
Installing a security camera
in the kitchen, are we?
What I'm doing, Nick,
is none of your concern.
Someone been stealing your Tasmanian stew?
Stew is not from Tasmania,
it is from everywhere.
[Lizzie] The most important factor
in catching a perpetrator
is video evidence of wrongdoing.
The perpetrator in this instance
is the disgusting individual
who has been using the jaffle maker
and not cleaning it afterwards.
I bet it's Lloyd.
[theme music playing]
[roadway noise]
[elevator dings]
Good morning, Flinley Craddick!
What excitement awaits us today,
young Elizabeth?
Um… nothing in the calendar.
No meetings?
No.
Any messages?
-[Lizzie] From…?
-Anyone?
No.
[tapping]
"Must have coffee."
-[Tina] I'm just not enjoying it.
-So, you're resigning?
I'm thinking about it, yes.
[Tina] My friend Mel resigned last month.
She's with another company now.
She's much happier.
I have their details if you want them.
They're recruiting.
[Deborah] Yeah, put them on through.
They had an away day last Friday.
Ziplining.
[Deborah] Oh, sweet!
[notification chimes]
That's it.
Oh Lloyd, you little rat.
[Lizzie imitates a rat] Ah!
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Hannah.
-We have a problem.
Come into my office, please.
Come into my office.
[Lizzie] Yeah, okay.
What's the sitchenario?
That's my word.
Yep. Sorry.
The sitchenario is this.
I was in the kitchen,
and I overheard Tina.
-And she's going to resign.
-Traitor.
And she's gonna take
half the staff with her.
Okay, let her resign,
but I'll do the exit interview.
She'll be crying like a baby
when I'm done.
[Hannah] Um…Yeah.
Yeah, I was actually thinking about
doing something fun
to prevent a mass exodus.
How much is ziplining?
You will not find a ziplining experience
for less than $75 per person.
Well, that's too expensive. Okay.
All right, I need you to plan
a fun away day activity,
including lunch and transport,
$500 max.
Give me a date.
Today.
Too easy.
-And Lizzie?
-Yeah?
Nothing with guns this time.
Copy that.
[Mason] Come on, baby,
just take a day off.
I don't understand. It's like
you're literally obsessed with this place.
[Greta] I work here, Mason.
This is my job. I get paid to be here.
[Mason] Babe! Baby girl!
Guys! Big announcement.
Can I have a drumroll, please?
That's not a drumroll, Lloyd.
That's how I drumroll.
Sebastian, can you do a drumroll, please?
-Yeah, on your legs.
-[Greta sniffling]
On your legs, everyone.
[Hannah] Mm? Mm? Mm? Mm? Mm? Mm?
[softly] Are you okay?
[the "drumroll" continues]
[mimics firework noises]
We are going on a surprise away day!
What? Yep!
Impromptu excursion where we will
self-develop, bond, and have fun!
Where are we going?
Um…?
That is for me to know
and for you to find out.
-When?
-[Hannah] When we get there.
-Get where?
-Look, all you need to know is,
it's happening outside of this building.
Okay, well, we're gonna need
a health and safety plan.
Well, then, plan it, Martin.
I will be taking my first aid kit
and my taser.
We will be fine.
-How'd you get a taser?
-We're not having a taser.
I wouldn't mind having a crack
at axe throwing.
[Hannah] Yep,
we're not doing axe throwing.
-It's not an escape room, is it?
-It is not an escape room.
Thank you, Sebastian.
Ziplining?
Ziplining? Did I hear ziplining?
Tina!
You're backing me into a corner here.
I'm not allowed to say anything,
but… [coughs] …maybe.
[indistinct chatter]
Do you think Tina's having a good time?
-She, she's standing by herself.
-[Lizzie] I mean, I don't know.
-We haven't left the car park yet, so.
-[Greta sighs heavily]
-You want to talk about it?
-Not really.
-That's cool.
I too myself am a big fan
of the repress-don't-express method.
I feel pain, I just push it
down, down, down.
Mason's Nan is sick, so we spent
all weekend at the hospital.
Which, of course we would.
But then this morning,
Mason wanted me to stay home
to help him tile the bathroom
because he didn't get time to do it
over the weekend.
Okay, everyone!
Attention, please!
The bus has now arrived.
Please take note of the seating chart.
Any questions?
Yeah, why do we have a seating chart plan?
To ensure equal weight distribution
on the vehicle.
Next question!
Isn't that just for light planes?
Trust me, I've done the research.
Oh, we trust you. Question.
Were you in The Matrix?
-Next question!
-Okay, no more questions.
Yeah? Um…
Breaking news, folks.
There's a new award up for grabs.
Best Away Day Employee.
And I don't want to say who's gonna win,
but there's an early frontrunner.
Her name's Tina.
[Hannah] Ooh!
-[Lizzie] Okay, everyone on the bus.
-Yes!
[indistinct, unenthusiastic chatter]
Where are we going?
-Not telling.
-Zorbing?
I don't think you understand
the concept of surprise.
-Biscuit factory.
-[Lizzie] Please get on the bus, Lloyd.
[softly] I need you to find me
a destination.
-[Lizzie] On it.
-Stat.
Got your little suncream,
have you, Martin?
[Martin] Look, I know it's very exciting.
We are on a trip.
But please stay in your seats
and just keep your belts on.
I got plenty of sunscreen here,
so don't be afraid to come on up.
And when we cross the road,
let's do it in a group, okay?
Thank you.
[Hannah] Thanks, Marty!
-Just gonna go and have a chat to Tina.
-Yeah.
[Hannah grunts]
Seatbelt.
-Hey, Sebastian.
-Mm?
Um, there's a spare seat up the front.
It's pretty cool.
You can see where we're going.
Uh… no, I'm good,
I've been on a bus before.
Thanks.
Right. Yep.
[sighs]
Teens, where do you see yourself
in five years?
Maybe if you work hard enough,
you can take my job.
No, thanks.
Okay.
[snores]
[Greta chuckles]
[phone dings]
[laughs]
Cone of silence. How's it going?
Well, naturally, I assumed
the jaffle culprit was one of our own,
but, turns out it's Grubby Mitts Jonny
from the warehouse.
What are you talking about?
I mean the away day destination.
Oh. Well, there's only two places
that we can afford.
One, an interactive reptile experience,
or a bakery tour called "Gluten Tootin".
That's it?
For five hundred bucks
including lunch? Yes.
[sighs heavily] Okay.
Testing.
Um, hi, everyone!
Uh, it's time for the big announcement.
We are going to an interactive
reptile experience
with a fully catered lunch!
Yay!
When I say "reptile",
you say "experience"!
-Reptile!
-[Lloyd and Lizzie] Experience.
[Hannah] Okay.
Let's go, everybody.
Hey! G'day!
-[Hannah] Hi.
-I'm Phil.
[Phil] How's it going?
-Yep.
-[Phil] All right.
This is my dog, Shane.
-Everyone say, "Hello, Shane."
-[Shane barks]
-Hello, Shane.
-[Phil] Shane's saying hello to you.
Now, Shane's not dangerous,
but if you go through
that gate over there,
then it's a completely different
fuckin' story, all right?
Could Shane be on a lead while we're here?
Nah, I don't believe
in tying animals up, mate.
It's all right,
just don't go through the gate.
Okay, and where are the toilets?
Ah, just around the side of the house.
-Through the gate.
-[Phil] Yeah.
All right, just head 'round this way.
[Hannah] Okay, yeah.
-"Shane".
-[hushed] Lizzie, what is this place?
It's… it's Phil's Reptile Park.
[upbeat exciting music playing]
[Phil] Welcome to…
Phil's snake and reptile experience!
Experience… experience…
Okay, inside this garage
are some of Australia's
most dangerous animals.
Excuse me.
[music stops]
Yeah, mate?
Do you have, ah, funnel web spiders?
-No. No.
-[Lloyd] No?
Do you have, ah, box jellyfish?
Is a box jellyfish a reptile, mate?
-No, but you said--
-[Hannah] Lloyd?
You're actually ruining it for Tina and I.
We're just trying to have fun.
Aren't we?
[Lloyd] You can't say, "I've got
Australia's most dangerous animals",
and then not actually have any
of Australia's most dangerous animals.
Do you have a taipan? No.
Do you have a saltwater croc? No.
Do you have a redback? No.
Doesn't even have a cassowary.
[Phil] Okay, everybody, this is Tammy.
-Hello!
-She's an albino carpet python.
AKA, Morelia spilota.
Now, who wants to have a hold?
I do!
Oh, that's what I like to see.
Keen as mustard.
-Yes! [laughs]
-[Phil] Very nice.
[in Dobby's accent] "The Chamber
of Secrets has been opened."
[in normal voice] What was that?
You want to go around Nick's neck?
-Okay.
-Oh, just like… just here's fine, Lizzie.
-[Phil] Go for it, She's a sweetheart.
-Do you want to touch?
-It's like a dog. You just pat it.
-Okay. Thank you.
-There we go, thanks very much.
-[Hannah] I'll have a turn.
-[Nick] Yeah? Okay.
-[Hannah] Yeah, here we go.
-Yeah, around my neck.
-Oh, neck? Okay.
Oh, wow. Yep.
Ooh. Yep.
I feel… fertile.
I think that's the best way
to describe it.
Tina, you are gonna love this, honestly.
You get it?
You getting it?
-Yeah. Oh, get a photo.
-Yeah? Okay.
-Hashtag snake sisters.
-[Lizzie] Yeah, okay.
Go like this! [hisses]
[hisses]
[upbeat rock music playing]
Okay, strap in, folks. This is Jacob,
an Eastern Brown snake,
aka Pseudonaja textilis,
the most deadliest snake in the world.
More like top ten.
One bite from Jacob and it's fuckin'
goodnight nurse, all right?
So, I'll just put him down here
so you guys can have
a good look at him, all right?
Careful, Jacob. Where you goin', mate?
That's it.
-Oh…
-[Phil] Enjoy yourselves.
[Martin] We might need that hook.
-[Hannah] Look at this.
-[Nick] Um, Phil…?
-Sorry mate, he's on the move.
-[all exclaiming]
[Phil] It's all right, it's all right.
Just stand still and relax.
It's all good.
Snakes have got terrible eyesight.
Not true.
[all exclaiming]
[Nick yelps]
You okay?
[Lizzie] If only I had my taser.
-You can't taser a snake.
-You can if it's threatening your liberty.
Remember, he's more scared of you
than you are of him.
[Hannah]
I bet this doesn't happen every day.
All right, no, he's heading to
the neighbours' chook house for a feed.
[Phil] Come back here, you little bugger.
-[Phil] Look out!
-Memories.
[Phil] Everybody, get back.
[Martin] Maybe just let him go, Phil.
[Hannah] I think he knows
what he's doing, Martin.
[Phil groans]
Get the anti-venom! It's by the CD player.
Okay. Move. Move.
Move! Out the way. Move!
Hey, Phil, can I just check,
is this part of the show
or have you actually been bitten?
Either way, incredible performance.
Don't you think, Tina?
-[Phil] Where's the anti-venom?
-[Lizzie] On my way! On my way!
On my way!
[Phil] Jesus.
-In the neck? Straight…
-No, give it here.
[Phil grunts]
[grunts]
Very good.
Man, everything but a first aid kit.
[Greta rummages]
Got these?
I'm okay, I'm saving myself for lunch.
Ha, ha. Sit up here.
[sighs]
[Nick] Mmm!
-Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Do you think Tina's having fun?
[Lizzie] Um… I don't think so,
but it's also Tina, so it's hard to tell.
[Hannah] Okay.
-[phone ringing]
-Hungry?
No thanks, I have to take this.
[Hannah sighs]
[hushed] Okay. Everyone, come here.
Come here, quickly.
[Hannah] Okay.
I'm worried about Tina, okay?
I think she's very unwell.
I think she's been caught up
in a pyramid scheme
and she's gonna try and recruit you.
Of course, she's gonna dress it up
as a job opportunity.
Do not take it under any circumstances.
It's very sad,
but we just have to ignore it.
Just gotta, you know…
[brightly] Tina!
That was a quick call. How was it?
-Okay.
-[Phil] Ah, guys?
I hope you're enjoying the sambos.
Now, look, forgot to mention,
the bedroom on the left down the hall
is the gift shop.
Come and get a keyring, a stubby holder.
In fact, everything in the house is
for sale, so make an offer!
-[Hannah] Whoo!
-What about these tongs?
[Phil] Eight bucks.
-What about the oven mitt?
-Four bucks.
Honestly, everything's for sale.
Make me an offer. Come find me.
[Hannah sighs]
Do you think they missed us?
-[laughing] No.
-[laughs]
We could be dead on the floor,
riddled with venom.
-Yeah.
-And nobody would know.
[Greta laughs]
Um…
Gonna change my arm.
Keep my biceps even.
No, I can do it. I can do it. I can do it.
[plastic crinkling]
[Nick] Mm…
Do you like peas?
Is that where we're at?
Chatting about peas?
Mm.
[Lloyd] Oop, g'day, guys.
-[Nick] Oh, hey, Lloyd.
-[Lloyd] Yes! There it is. Yes.
He only wants ten bucks for that.
That is incredibly cheap meat.
[Nick laughs] Yeah.
You gonna, um…?
-No, they're all yours.
-You know?
Sweet!
[Nick] Mm.
-Lloyd's dinner is already set, isn't it?
-Yes, yeah.
-Sunday… Sunday night roast, yes.
-Saturday night roast, yeah.
Whoa.
[tablet chimes]
Oh, you sneaky little man.
Oh my…
[phone ringing]
Pick up, Jonny, I dare you.
Pick up, you little chicken.
[Jonny speaking indistinctly]
[Lizzie] That's it.
[Jonny] Goodbye.
[scoffs]
Oh, really unimpressed, Jonny.
Really unimpressed now.
-[slurping]
-You said I was unwell.
-Did I?
-Yes.
Well, at least I'm not a traitor.
Oh, come on.
She's threatening a mutiny.
What are you talking about?
She is gonna quit
and take the whole staff with her,
and she just wants to go and find someone
who'll take her ziplining.
Well, you know what, Tina?
Goodbye, and good luck
finding a boss like this
again.
-[Tina] I'm not quitting.
-Mm?
I work part-time
for a Chinese-language newspaper.
That's the job I'm thinking of quitting.
Okay, so…
so you're not leaving Flinley Craddick?
No.
Oh…
Okay.
Well.
Sounds like someone made a dummy.
Someone made a boo-boo.
Hey, shall we have a little sorry hug?
-No, thanks.
-[Hannah] No.
-Martin?
-No.
[sighs]
[Sebastian]
You've never had a pair of tongs before?
[Lloyd] No, I never use tongs.
What do you normally use for tongs?
Either my fingers or a spatula.
-You use a spatula to pick things up?
-[Lloyd] Yeah.
Got you a memento.
[Greta laughs] Okay.
-And it was only eight bucks.
-[Greta] Ooh.
-That's a… bargain.
-Mm-hmm.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[Hannah] Ah, guys? Guys?
Um, I forgot to present
the Best Away Day Employee.
Ah, this gift is for Tina.
-[all clapping]
-[indistinct chatter]
[Hannah] Yeah?
Ooh, don't touch the bottom.
It's Tammy!
I have a Dwarf bunny rabbit at home.
Not compatible.
What is your refund policy?
Don't have one.
I'll buy it off you for fifty bucks.
Fifty bucks?
Can we hurry up, please?
The meat's starting to thaw.
[Phil] All right, well.
Come again.
Make sure you tell your friends.
Yep. We won't.
Thank you.
[Hannah] Has it been
a successful away day?
I'd say yes.
It wasn't ziplining,
who would have remembered that?
No one.
You know what people remember?
A grown man
being bitten by a venomous snake.
That's…
That's going in there forever.
Tina.
She'll remember.
See ya, Sebastian.
-See ya, Deb. Lloyd.
-See ya.
Love ya shank.
-Bye, Greta. Nick.
-[Greta] Bye.
[Hannah] See ya, James.
[Josh mutters] Josh.
See ya, Tina.
-Long distance high five.
-[Tina scoffs]
[grunts, pretends to whimper in pain]
[indistinct chatter]
[clears throat]
I've got a little surprise for Jonny.
Can I give you a ride somewhere?
Yeah, like Milos?
Yeah, we could go to Milos.
But I think Parramatta is,
like, more achievable.
We could go for dinner.
Yeah. That could be fun.
Yeah.
-[phone ringing]
-Ooh.
-Sorry, I should, um…
-Yeah, of course.
-[Greta] Hey.
-[Mason indistinct on phone]
Oh no!
Oh, babe, I'm so sorry.
[Mason] I'll pick you up
if you're still at work.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll be here.
[Nick] Everything okay?
Um…
Mason's Teta has died.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Can we just pretend this…
whole thing didn't… didn't happen?
Yeah, of course. Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Um, Mason's picking me up, so.
Oh.
[Greta sighs]
I'll drop it back off at Phil's then.
[roadway noise]
[yelps]
Bloody hell!
[theme music]