This is Pam.
Oh, my God, are you sure?
Uh, okay.
Okay, we'll be right there.
Everybody,
the balloon is falling.
Nice.
There's this balloon
that has been floating
in the rafters of the warehouse
for, like, ever.
And, okay, it's not--
it doesn't sound cool.
You just have to see it.
Well, I guess it doesn't
look that cool either.
But it's been up there a long time,
so it's become a pretty big deal.
Wow.
It's the end of an era.
Did a good job, buddy.
Now it's time to come home.
I remember
when that balloon went up there.
I was still with gil.
We were so happy.
When that went up there,
I had hair like Rapunzel.
How long do you think
it's been up there, Kevin?
I just remember
pushing aside my silky bangs
to say, "Look, a balloon."
My Warcraft clan
was still on speaking terms.
My kid didn't have a face tattoo.
I was still thinking
of going back to school.
And I was still just a paper salesman.
Well, this has been fun, Pam.
Thanks for calling us all down here.
Kill the balloon.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com.
Hey.
So they accidentally gave us
an extra egg sandwich this morning.
- Who wants it?
- Ooh.
- Right here, right here.
- Yes.
Allow me to solve your problem then.
- Nellie.
- Mmm.
Oh, that is disgusting.
Do you call that
a King James breakfast pie?
What brings you to town?
Certainly not
the Harry Houdini Museum.
What a nobody.
Oh, look, some Hungarian just
found their way out of a sack.
Let's build a shrine.
No, I've come to work here.
What?
How could Robert transfer Nellie here
after the Sabre store debacle?
She stinks of failure.
The fact that she could show her face
around here is an embarrassment.
I should know.
I'm in an identical situation.
Robert did say you'd be joining us.
Welcome.
I'm Tony.
- Mm.
- What?
I-I said,
I'm Tony.
Okay, I made a mistake.
I thought it might go unnoticed.
But, uh, I'm Toby.
You messed up saying your name?
It happens, okay?
So let's just find
an empty desk for you,
and I'm sure Robert will be
with you as soon as he gets in.
- That one looks empty.
- No, it's Andy's office.
Oh, is it?
I have one simple philosophy
in business:
If the seat is open, the job is open.
It's how I came to briefly race
a formula one car.
The three slowest laps ever recorded.
Another beautiful day in Tallahassee.
Ooh.
Good morning, Alonzo.
Good morning, Erin.
How are you?
How's your family doing?
Bye.
Look at this place!
Five rooms, and I get
to clean them all.
That's right,
I'm a maid for an old lady.
Her grandson's staying with us too,
because he ran out of money.
Listen to me, bragging away.
- Nellie.
- Robert.
How are you adjusting to life
in Scranton so far?
- So far, so good.
- Good.
Water pressure in the hotel
is marvelous.
Ah, well, it is astounding
what a difference
that can make, isn't it?
Mmhm.
Now let's find you something
fun to do here, shall we?
Oh, I've already found it.
I am manager,
a natural next step.
It fits like a glove.
We have a manager.
Do you really?
Because it is 10:00,
I've been in this chair for an hour,
and no other manager
has come and sat in my lap.
Excuse me, has anyone
seen Andy this morning?
Huh, yeah, that's weird.
He's usually here by now.
Right, guys?
Hello?
Andy, it's Robert.
Why aren't you at work?
Hey, Robert.
Ah, I really wish I could
come into work today,
but I'm super sick.
I don't care, I don't care.
Please come to work immediately.
Okay, I'll try to come in,
even though
I'm really sick with the...
Florida flu.
He just hung up on me
mid-sentence.
I'm in Florida to get Erin.
As soon as I heard she wasn't
coming back to Scranton,
I jumped straight in my car
and drove straight down
till I hit the ocean.
My heart is my map.
Turns out Tallahassee
is about 200 miles inland,
so I overshot a good amount.
But still, not bad
for a heart map, right?
Oh, no.
Thanks a lot, B.P.
Not much we can do about this
until he gets here.
Can't you do something about this?
Sometimes the flowers
arrange themselves, Jim.
Right.
What is going on?
And where's Andy?
And what is going on?
- Erin, you got a package.
- I'm in the bathroom.
Where's the postage?
I mean, there's no shipping label.
- Did you wash your hands?
- Yes.
♪ Here I am
♪ signed, sealed, delivered ♪
♪ I'm yours
Andy, what are you doing here?
It's great to see you.
Uh, I am here
to take you back to Scranton,
because I love you
and I want to be with you.
Where's the ring?
- Hm?
- Where's the ring, Lancelot?
Would you guys mind if we
talked privately for a second?
Sorry, Glenn.
Um, Andy...
I am so happy to see you.
But I'm not coming back with you.
Why won't she go with him?
I don't know.
Maybe it's 'cause
he's not that handsome.
Hey...
Don't listen.
So, what is going on?
That does seem to be
the question, doesn't it?
Hey, this is messed up, bro.
Who is this weird lady?
I know.
It's a lot.
So who knows what's going on?
Anyone?
You, yes.
Wait, I am very good
at intuiting names.
Is it...Chumbo?
I think it's a cross
between "Dumbo" and "Jumbo,"
with a hint of "chubby."
It's not a name.
So no one can tell me what's going on.
Well, let me illuminate
things for you.
We are getting to know each other.
But why, m'lady?
Because I am your new manager.
Robert, is Nellie our new manager?
This is an odd situation.
But it's very interesting
how it's playing out.
We live in this world
of routines and rhythms.
Kevin ate someone's lunch,
Phyllis has a new necklace.
Who is this woman?
I came in here simply
trying to get to know you,
learn your names,
maybe have someone teach me
the company song.
And what I got in return
was nothing but disrespect.
You leave me no choice
but to get to know you
in a more intimate way.
Hot tub party?
Performance reviews.
How can you give us
performance reviews
if you don't know us?
On first impressions,
so I recommend smiling.
It goes a long way with me.
Erin, you really nailed
the hot dogs today.
Oh, thanks.
I've been reusing the hot dog water
so it gets more flavor.
It's only going
to keep getting better.
So, Andrew, how does
your skinny brunette girlfriend
Jessica feel about you visiting
your ex-girlfriend?
Well, we're not
really dating anymore, so...
Basically, I mean,
I just have to cross a few "T"s
and dot a few "I"s, you know.
So you came to get me,
but you still have a girlfriend.
I think you should leave, young man.
All right, technically, yes,
I am still technically dating Jessica.
But when I realized
that I wanted you back,
I just jumped in the car,
and I drove down here,
and I didn't want to stop
until I saw you.
You didn't even stop to pee?
Gross.
- Any luck?
- No.
He just keeps letting
all the calls go to voicemail.
♪ Please leave
♪ a message for Andy Bernard ♪
♪ include your na--
Oh, you're doing so good.
Oh, my God,
you're Superman over there.
You should take it.
It's probably your girlfriend,
wondering where you are.
Nope, it's just work.
Not important.
You know, I can
really feel this in my quads.
I can tell I'm getting stronger.
You really wouldn't
feel those kinds of results
- after one session.
- I don't know.
Just let it vibrate.
It's fine.
- You could put it on silent.
- I don't think it does that.
Just go to preferences,
then click--
Proctology.
Andy?
- Jim?
- Andy, where are you?
I'm home in bed.
I've been in bed all day.
I got the--I got
the serious poops, man.
He's here in Tallahassee,
trying to turn my life upside down.
What?
You're in Florida?
Andy, Nellie Bertram's
trying to take your job.
What do you mean, take my job?
Like, set up camp in your office
and is calling herself the manager.
Okay...
Jim, I really appreciate you
looking out for me,
but I'm not coming home without Erin.
So I'll talk to you later.
Guys, we cannot do
these performance reviews, okay?
If we go into them,
you're basically accepting
Nellie as your manager,
and trust me, you do not
want her as your manager.
Trust you?
The way Pam trusted you
to provide for her
so she wouldn't have to work?
I like working here.
Dwight, should she be our manager?
I wouldn't let her
manage a celery farm.
Those who can't farm farm celery.
And when was the last time
Dwight and I agreed
on anything ever?
All right, let's get going.
First up, it is the woman
with the beautiful fingernails
and the tiny feet,
Phyllis.
Nellie, I'm sorry,
but I don't feel comfortable
being evaluated
by someone I don't know.
Oh, oh, okay, I understand.
Let me show you
how these are going to go.
Dwight.
I refuse to be judged by
someone that I do not respect.
I lost respect for you in Florida.
If it was up to me,
you would be in jail forever.
Dwight, I have completed
your evaluation.
- You're getting a raise.
- What?
Dwight, you carry this company
on your massive shoulders.
You are our Atlas,
and for that, do you not
think you deserve a raise?
There's no limit
to what I think I deserve.
- Then you accept it?
- 5%, no less.
Absolutely not.
7%.
6%.
I know my worth.
Raise isn't real.
Money isn't real ever since
we got off the gold standard.
So, Phyllis, now you know
the rules of the game.
Would you care to have a go?
I'm fairly certain
you're going to like it.
- Phyllis.
- Pam.
So, Phyllis, I have been
very impressed with you.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
The way you conquered your fear
and came in here,
and now the way you sit there...
All very impressive.
Um...
Are you aware that
Nellie is giving out raises?
I am not.
Huh.
Yeah.
She gave one to Dwight, Phyllis.
Let me guess, you want one too?
Take the family to Disneytown?
Land. World.
Uh, it's not
that I don't want a--
Well, yes, I guess I'd take a raise.
That's not what I'm saying.
That's not--sorry.
Jim, I told Andy to come in,
and yet, he is still not in.
By contrast, Nellie Bertram
saw a vacuum and filled it.
To make no mention
of her business experience
or her relationship
with Jo Bennett, my boss.
- Yes.
- Jim, would you prefer
a nature metaphor
or a sexual metaphor?
Oh, God, nature, please.
When two animals are having sex,
one of them...
Is communicating a message
to the other.
Nothing is mutua--
this isn't very helpful.
You're going to want
to hear the sexual metaphor.
Was that not the--
All life is sex.
And all sex is competition.
Mmhm.
And there are no rules to that game.
That wasn't so perverted, now was it?
Was that it?
No, that wasn't bad.
My point is,
there is one person in charge
of every office in America,
and that person is Charles Darwin.
In the end, doesn't he decide
who the manager is?
No.
I would've said no.
Let's see ***.
Yes, good stuff.
Here you go, have a raise.
Oh, great.
I mean, if we go in there
and take these raises,
what are we saying?
That it's okay for someone
to just take someone else's job?
Shouldn't work like that.
No, you know what?
Nellie's right.
That is exactly how it should work.
Darryl, this office is mine now.
- No.
- Yes.
Sorry, too late.
I'm here.
This is mine.
Back off.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Well fought.
I accept the outcome.
Touch me and I'll sue.
I've heard that's amazing
when it works.
- Yeah, if I had my own--
- Andy, I care about you and--
- Sorry, you go.
- No, go ahead.
Well, I was just going to say that,
if I had my own fountain,
it would be two frogs
that are spitting
into each other's mouth.
It's just stupid.
What were you going to say?
Andy, you broke my heart.
Do you know what it feels like
to be constantly rejected by you
and to have to watch you
date someone else?
You broke my heart too.
You broke my heart
more recently and more often.
And I think,
at some point, in my head,
it just sort of clicked
that we're not meant to be.
I'm so sorry that
we have not loved each other
- at the same time.
- I know.
So, Pamela, I'm going
to start this review,
not by telling you what you lack,
but rather, asking you
what it is you want.
Really?
Okay, well, I like consistency
in the manager's position,
no weird silent coups.
Stuff like that.
I'm easy.
That's not really what you want.
What you want is a good night's sleep,
working mother of two.
Whoa, that's kind of condescending.
Would you say
something like that to Jim?
Does Jim have to breastfeed?
Did Jim carry around
those babies for--
What is it?
12 months?
Be honest, does Jim
really get up in the night?
Well, I mean,
the only reason he doesn't
is because I'm breastfeeding,
and Phillip doesn't like a bottle.
You must be exhausted.
Fancy a nap?
No.
Go on.
Have a nap.
Lie down right here.
There's a blanket in here.
I used it earlier myself.
Dreamt I could breath underwater
like Jacques Cousteau.
No one will know.
I'll wake you up.
And when you wake up,
you will earn more money.
I think...
you're a witch.
I think you're amazing.
You know that, right?
Go on, say it:
"I'm amazing."
I'm amazing.
Erin, I think you're making
a big mistake right now.
Andy is a nice boy.
Really?
'Cause you've been kind of
a "B" to him all afternoon.
I was protecting you,
because I thought he was no good.
But I can tell you really like him.
And he's willing
to lose his job for you
in this economy
with Europe on the brink--
Irene, what would you do without me?
We're not your concern, sweetheart.
Besides, Glenn's going
to sue home depot.
Why?
He got his foreskin caught
in some lawn furniture.
Jim, time for your review.
No, it's not, because
you don't really work here.
Why are you so staunchly defending
your friend, who has abandoned you?
Wouldn't you rather come talk with me?
Maybe definitely get a raise?
Yeah, that's the thing.
I don't know
if you can even give raises.
Jim, have you ever heard
of a character named Tinkerbell?
- Yes.
- I'm Tinkerbell.
- No.
- Mm-hm.
I'm a magical fairy
who floated into your office
to bring a little bit
of magic into your lives,
to give you all raises.
And we are grateful.
But here's the thing
about Tinkerbell, Jim.
Everyone has to believe in her
or she doesn't exist.
- She dies.
- She dies!
Now who here believes in Tinkerbell?
Let's see it.
Show of hands.
- I do.
- Oh!
Come on, everyone.
All right, guys, stop.
- I already spent the money.
- How?
Come on, Jim, you're killing her.
We believe!
Look at this wonderful recognition
of Nellie's leadership.
I believe.
That did not go how I wanted it to.
Ugh.
I have a whole ton
of Erin's favorite food
for the drive back, eggplant parm.
It's biodegradable.
Animals will eat it.
Andy, wait!
Andy!
Andy, wait.
Andy, don't go.
Andy, I love you!
Stop!
Oh, this is the wrong Prius.
I don't love you.
- Erin!
- I'm sorry.
Andy.
Let's get out of here.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Wait, we have to go back
and get your stuff.
No, I don't have any stuff.
Like, your toothbrush and stuff.
- I don't have one.
- You don't have a toothbrush?
No.
How do you not have a toothbrush?
I just--
there's always one around.
You just use
whichever one's sitting there?
I always find one.
Have you ever heard
of buying a toothbrush?
Of course.
I own my toothbrush.
I grew up poor.
I had little formal education.
No real skills.
I don't work especially hard...
And most of my ideas are either unoriginal
or total crap and yet
I walked right into a job for which
I was ill prepared,
ill seated,
and somebody else already had
and I got it.
If you ask me, that's the American dream
right there,
anything can happen to anyone.
It's just random.
www.tvsubtitles.net