-[Lloyd] Hey, Sebastian.
-What?
Hey, do you have any adventurers
in your family?
-What?
-Any… any heroes?
Ah… no, I don't think so.
-I do.
-Right.
Well, TBC, you know.
-To be confirmed.
-[printer beeps]
But I'm pretty sure
it's gonna be confirmed.
-Yeah, uh…
-Yeah.
-Cool, man. Uh…
-Keep you updated.
You don't… you don't have to.
I bought myself a genealogy test
for my birthday.
Oh, hey, Carlie.
Hey, do you have any adventurers
in your family?
My mate Craig Dodd got a test.
Turns out he's 2% Hispanic.
Total game-changer.
Met a nice lady at a flamenco class.
Now, he's moving in with her,
and her, um,
her adult son.
I'll keep you updated.
Hey. Hey, Nick.
[theme music playing]
[roadway noise]
-[lift pings]
-[indistinct office chatter]
What is going on?
[mumbles] Good morning.
-I need you to sign in, please.
-[Lizzie] Sorry.
Who are you
and why are you sitting at my desk?
I'm Dylan, the receptionist.
Uh, you're not.
So, move,
before I call security,
which also happens to be me
so they'll be here instantly, yeah?
[tablet beeping]
[Lizzie] Actually, you know what?
I won't sign in,
-and if I find you here--
-[Hannah] Lizzie. Lizzie.
Can I… borrow you for a second?
Got a… got a surprise for you.
Last night, Alisha asked me
to submit an application
for Western Sydney
Businesswoman of the Year,
and, pfft.
I don't really care about awards.
I've always found the award
is in the reward
of having a happy staff that love you.
I am not happy about this, Hannah.
Well, you might be happy about this.
I'm promoting you.
You are?
Yep. Promoting women
into positions of power.
That's my mantra, really.
I've never heard you say that.
I say it all the time.
And, ooh, my back hurts
from carrying all my sisters
all the time.
Ow. Pulled a muscle in my feminism.
I'm making you
my production manager.
[Lizzie] Wow.
Yep, okay.
What am I Production Managering?
[Hannah] My award application.
Just a sexy little upbeat video
highlighting all my best attributes.
They want a sex video?
No, they just want a video.
[Lizzie] Done.
Sebastian's gonna make the video.
Why Sebastian?
[Hannah] 'Cause he's a cool guy
with a cool phone.
And we need a video that highlights me
as women supporting women, check,
and a passionate commitment to diversity.
[Lizzie laughing] Okay.
So that's why he's here.
-Who?
-The security risk.
Dylan is here
because he's an excellent receptionist.
[Lizzie] So, who do you want
in your video?
Oh, who do I want in my video?
I haven't really thought about it.
Um, top of my head, let's say,
Martin, Greta, Tina,
Dylan, Big D,
Sebastian,
and, I don't know,
Stevie from the warehouse?
So yeah, Hannah just pretty much listed
every diverse person in the office.
Just off the top of her head, though.
[Lizzie] Who else have we got? We've got…
Deborah, Lloyd, um…
Me.
Yeah, I reckon we just stick to the list
that I gave you initially.
Yeah.
And I'll have a ham and cheese
tomato sandwich. [laughs]
[muttering]
Come on.
Ugh!
[Deborah] Okay, attention, everybody.
We've got a problem.
Does anyone know
why the coffee machine is not working?
Anybody?
[silence]
[Deborah] Marty?
No, no. No. No.
-[Deborah] Greta?
-Uh-uh.
Excuse me.
[Nick] Why are you doubting me?
I reckon I could pull off a kilt.
-So confident.
-My legs are long.
-[Greta] I mean, they are--
-Hey, guys.
[Hannah] Oh, Greta!
You know what I was thinking?
It's illegal how many good hair days
you get a week.
Yeah, I've issued her a number of fines.
Call my lawyer.
[laughs]
[Greta laughs, forced]
Do you need something…?
No. Ac-- well, you know what?
Now that you've brought it up, um,
Alisha wants me to apply for this
women in business thing,
and she was wondering
if you could write a little testimonial
about how inspiring I am as a boss?
Her words, not mine.
So, if you could, I don't know,
maybe have that by this afternoon?
[Hannah] Hey, Teens.
How ya going?
You all excited
for your big, starring role
in my video this afternoon?
Um, not really.
-[indistinct office chatter]
-[keyboards clacking]
-[Deborah] What's up with you?
-Nothing.
Just excited about
what the day might bring.
You've had coffee, haven't you?
-[Lloyd] No.
-Where'd you get it?
Today, I get to find out who I really am.
Uh, no.
[Deborah] Not today Lloyd, not today.
[Lloyd] Yeah, it's pretty exciting.
I could be descended from adventurers
or heroic Spanish conquistadors
or kings, even.
Imagine that.
"Hi! I…" No, that's too…
Hi-- [clears throat]
-[in lower voice] Hi. Hi.
-"Hi."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, yeah, that says…
that says "woman".
Should I say,
[in low voice] "Hi, I'm Hannah Howard,"
or should I say,
[in low voice] "Hi. Hannah Howard here."
"Hi. Hannah Howard here,"
has too many H's in a row.
That's a good point.
Is the suit a bit much?
-Yes.
-[Hannah] Good. Good, good, good.
[clattering loudly]
-Now you've really broken it.
-It was broken.
So am I, son.
[mutters] So am I.
[Deborah] I've got
an addictive personality,
which stems back to my childhood.
My dad used to give me a lollipop
every time I went to the store
to get a pack of cigarettes.
For him, not for me.
I didn't smoke until I was…
eight?
[coffee machine clattering]
Have you tried turning it off
and turning it on again?
Yeah, it's not a computer, Tina.
Sorry, this…
We should try…
Try turning it off and on at the wall.
[Yohan] I didn't do anything.
But did you make it worse? Like,
is… is it totally stuffed now?
-I mean, it was already broken.
-[Deborah] Ugh!
[Deborah] Fuck!
[Deborah] But I heard it was you that
pulled the hose out.
-[Lizzie] Hannah?
-[Hannah] Ah, Lizzie.
-What's all that noise?
-[Lizzie] We have a problem.
The coffee machine is broken.
This is an office of addicts.
[Hannah] Helloha, everybody!
[dead silence]
Yeah, I-- I get it.
"Where's my goddamn coffee?"
Am I right?
Um, well,
I want you to know that
I am personally managing this crisis.
[Deborah] How?
By identifying options.
What are they?
Good question.
Lizzie, why don't you…?
I… uh…
Option one is the truck stop café
down the road.
Nah, that's worse than servo coffee.
What's option two?
The servo.
[all sign despondently]
Okay, I-- I want you to know
that I'm listening
and I hear you
and you need a third option.
We're going to have that
solved in the next hour.
-Aren't-- Am I right, Lizzie?
-Tick-tock!
[discontented muttering]
It's coming, guys. Don't worry.
And don't forget,
we're filming the video later!
Lizzie?
[softly] You need to sort this crisis
in the next hour, okay?
Whatever the cost.
[telephones ringing]
[notification chimes]
[Lloyd] 67% Anglo Saxon,
24% Celtic…
Oh.
…8% Germanic.
Just boring farmers,
not a hero or a Spanish conquistador
amongst them.
[female voice over laptop]
When on camera,
use physical actions
to punctuate your message.
[video stops playing]
Please tell me
the coffee crisis is sorted.
The coffee crisis is sorted.
-Oh. But is it actually?
-Yes.
-Oh, great.
-Do you want to know how I did it?
Oh, not at all. Thank you.
[machinery whirring]
-[man 1] Take it down.
[Stevie] Just need to ask him.
Oi, Jonny!
Wait a sec.
-What?
-These guys wanna use your coffee machine.
No way.
Told you. He doesn't let anyone
touch his coffee machine.
Yeah, I agreed to sort out
the coffee situation
in exchange for Lizzie
writing Hannah's testimonial.
-Pretty happy about that.
-Mm.
And I agreed to help because I was bored.
I mean supportive.
Okay, what if it's him touching it
but making coffees for us?
Maybe.
You guys would cover costs?
-So says Hannah.
-Yeah, I can vouch for that.
What do you reckon?
-Cash?
-Yeah.
-Café prices?
Sure.
He said sure.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you very much.
-[Jonny] Have a good day.
-[Greta] Thank you.
[Jonny] No, mate,
I've got to unpack these.
[indistinct chatter]
Could I get a triple shot flat white?
Uh, now. As in, like, right now.
Coming up.
-How much?
-No, they're free.
-I'm just gonna wait over here.
-All right.
-[Jonny] I'll bring it over.
-Great.
[Lloyd] Martin? Martin?
Martin?
Can I have a word?
It's a little bit sensitive.
Ah… is it work-related?
Ah, well, it's affecting my work, so yeah.
I need to apply
for some compassionate leave.
Oh, is someone in your family sick?
No, no. No, my family aren't anything.
-That's the problem.
-Right.
-My mate Craig's 2% Hispanic.
-Yeah?
And in real life,
I am way more interesting than he is.
-Yeah?
-And it's just not fair.
So can I just get
a little bit of time off?
-Um…
-Just to process it?
-No.
-[Lizzie] Okay everyone.
Coffee break over.
-Everybody upstairs now.
-[discontented murmuring]
What? I haven't got mine yet.
[Lizzie] Come on,
it's time to shoot Hannah's video.
-We'll be five minutes, Lizzie.
Hi. I'm Hannah Howard,
Managing Director at the Sydney branch
of packaging company Flinley Craddick.
And I'm a woman.
I've created a relaxed environment
where fun and productivity are
at the top of the agenda.
Call Stevie.
You know, I've been
at Flinley Craddick a long time,
but not nearly as long as Greta's people.
Here's to another 40,000 years.
Seventy.
Hmm?
I've created an inclusive environment
where every size, colour, gender,
and abilities are welcome.
[mumbling] You have
an eleven o'clock meeting.
Thanks, Dylan.
-[laughs cheerily]
-[lift dings]
[Stevie clears throat]
[Hannah] Oh. Hi, Stevie.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. I hope you don't mind that
we borrowed your flag.
That's not my flag.
Well, not yours, but your community's.
That's a lesbian flag.
It is.
Thank you.
I thought he was a lesbian.
[Lizzie] I thought so too
but maybe he's not.
[Sebastian] Do you want me to cut?
Yes, c-- Yes, cut!
I'm not doing The Voice.
[Hannah in video on phone] …a relaxed
environment where fun and productivity
are at the top of the agenda.
-[Dylan] Hi, Hannah.
-Hi.
Just checking that
you're happy with everything.
Mwah! Absolutely.
Oh, great.
If you decide to use my image
in the video,
you'll need a release form.
It's an extra thousand.
[splutters] We've--
we've already paid you $500, Dylan.
That's more like a call-out fee.
[forced laugh] Um…
[Hannah] Dylan, I've been very charitable,
and I don't want to
have to call your mother.
Um, and so what happened next, Dylan?
Miss Howard raised her voice.
Oh, it was just above
speaking level. That's…
Well, it-- it wasn't.
I could hear it in here all the way
on the other side of the office.
I project.
Well, it was a raised voice.
She entered my personal space
and started to threaten me.
That is just a lie. That's what that is.
It's just, like, a lie.
[tsks]
How would you like to proceed, Dylan?
I guess you could pixelate my face.
It's not so much the job
that's challenging.
It's the people.
The people…
being Hannah.
She's the people.
-It's just Hannah.
-[phone ringing]
And there's Hannah.
Great.
You only usually have one.
-There's too many for any--
-Is that bad?
"Is that bad?"
Cheers. What a rollercoaster of a day.
Is it?
Yeah. Yeah.
Started off thinking
I was gonna meet the love of my life
-at a flamenco class…
-Mm.
…only to discover my ancestors
are all cabbage farmers.
[laughs] Oh…
-From Wales.
-Crazy.
Probably can't even dance.
[Nick laughs sympathetically]
So obviously…
That's… yeah.
I mean…
Hey, do you know,
I should probably get back to my desk.
-But you can come tell me later.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, okay.
-[Nick] Yeah.
Geez, what a rollercoaster of a day.
Yeah.
Okay. That sounds good.
-Sorry I'm just on the phone, sorry.
-[Lloyd] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I will, I will do that. Yeah.
[softly] Oh, sorry,
could you close the door?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
[Hannah] Yeah. I love this one.
Yeah, but you, um…
You stumble over your line in this take.
Yeah, but I look hotter.
-Mm?
-Yeah…
Can you check with Greta
and see how the testimonial's going?
Actually, I wrote your testimonial.
What?
Well, when I delegated to her
the coffee problem,
she delegated to me
the testimonial problem.
Oh no.
No, no. It's good.
It's really good.
Hannah Howard is an exceptional leader,
made stronger by the amazing team
she has gathered around herself.
In particular,
the backbone of her operation,
Lizzie Moyle.
None of that's not true.
[Hannah in video] Good news.
-Good news. Yeah.
-Good news.
-It's good, isn't it? Ah…
-[computer notification chimes]
[Hannah] Ooh, it's Alisha!
[Hannah grunts]
Hello, Alisha!
Coming to you live from an ant farm.
Oh, hey, Hannah. I'm, um…
I'm just calling to check how
the application's going.
Oh, amazingly. I bet--
You should see this video,
honestly. I'll do--
I'll share my screen. That thing.
You can't share the screen.
It's on my computer.
[Hannah] Oh. Ah…
Well, uh, yeah, hold it up.
He's gonna show you.
[Hannah on video]
Here at Flinley Craddick,
I like to create a relaxed environment
where fun and productivity
are at the top of the agenda.
What… what's… what's…
What's this?
Um, it's, that's the video for my app.
Your application?
[in French accent] Oui, ma application.
Um, Hannah, I think you might have
got the wrong end of the stick.
I was suggesting that we nominate Greta.
[silence]
Um…
No, no, your…
your email--
I've printed it up. [forced laugh]
And it says, "This came across my desk."
"You should consider. Greta?"
"Will need to write a testimonial."
[Alisha] You should consider Greta
for the award
and you will need to write
a testimonial for her.
Well, that… that's not what that means.
[Alisha] Hope you haven't spent
too much time on this, Hannah.
Nope.
No. [forced laugh]
Nah. God, like, what? Five minutes?
Max?
-Max.
-Great.
Well, I need it on my desk by 5:00 p.m.
Okay.
[Alisha] I have to go.
-Sure.
Yeah, no, I've got to go too.
-Just, um…
-I've got a busy day, all right?
Yeah I'm--
Yeah, no, I've got--
I'm swamped!
So, can I, um, stop?
Yeah. Thank you.
[telephone ringing]
[Tina] Flinley Craddick, Tina speaking.
Um… hey, everyone.
Just a bit of an update on
the old awards hoo-ha.
I have decided to step aside
and, um, nominate Greta.
-Whoo! Yeah!
-[scattered clapping]
Uh, why?
[Hannah] Um…
'Cause I've had
considerable success in my career,
and there's…
there's no more room
in the trophy cabinet.
So, um, yeah.
Congratulations, Greta,
and if anyone needs me,
I'll be in the office
writing her a glowing testimonial.
I don't want to be Western Sydney
Businesswoman of the Year.
I don't want to be
the businesswoman of any year.
I don't want to be a businesswoman.
-[Nick sings] Business Woman of the Year.
-Stop it.
[Dylan] Hey, everyone.
Jonny's doing iced coffees
and Portuguese tarts.
-[indistinct eager chatter]
-Coffee?
-Did he say coffee?
-[Lloyd] Yeah, yeah.
[eager chatter]
I'm not applying.
Why not? You could be
the next Hannah Howard.
And that's why I'm not applying.
You'd actually be a pretty good boss.
-"Pretty good"?
-Mm.
Passable.
You'd be a great boss.
-I know.
-[slurps]
[Lizzie] So next Tuesday
at 11:30 a.m.,
you have a supplier meeting
to negotiate contracts.
-Move it.
-Okay.
Knock-knock. G'day.
That's for you, Hannah.
[Hannah clears throat]
$890? What's this?
Oh, that's the invoice for today.
Who's… covering this?
You are, apparently.
Is that what you told Greta?
You said "whatever the cost".
I--
[softly] Well, I didn't mean literally.
Well, how did you mean it not literally?
Metaphorically.
I'm gonna let you handle this one.
Hey, good on you, Hannah.
[Stevie] See you later.
[Hannah] $890?!
You need to return that money to Hannah
now that there's no video.
Doesn't work like that.
Your mum will be very disappointed
when she finds out that you exploited her.
Don't hate the player.
Hate the game.
What does that even mean?
Far out.
That was the coolest thing I've ever seen.
You still need to sign out.
[lift dings]
[Lloyd] $890.
What did you want me to do with this?
Be the hero your ancestors weren't.
By paying for coffee?
It's bold.
It's brave.
You'd be a hero.
You'd be my hero.
I'll even hang a framed photo
of the occasion
in my office on the wall.
-Okay.
-[Hannah] Yeah.
-Great.
-[Hannah] Yeah?
[Lloyd] I'll probably have to
pay in instalments.
Not a problem.
Just have to move some money
around or something.
Yeah…
Okay. Hey, thanks.
[Hannah] Who's my hero?
-Me.
-You are.
Okay.
[theme music playing]