Could you please sign
my expense report?
No way, no how.
Expense reports are a day-to-day
item. That is jim's now.
I am exclusively
big picture, epic.
- Sign this.
- Ah, ah, ah.
Where's the "please"?
We're not animals.
Sign it.
No, not without a "please. "
Idiot.
I have a complaint about jim.
That is not big picture.
I would like to file a huge,
enormous, massive complaint
about the tallest guy
in our office.
Okay.
Jim won't sign
my expense report.
That is not... Okay...
- That is day-to-day.
- No, that his huge.
- You're trying to trick me.
Get out, get out, get out.
- This has to do...
Get out, get out.
I'd like to lodge a complaint.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
Who is this about?
- You!
- Okay.
Just want to let you know
I take complaints very seriously.
So... When did this happen?
- One minute ago.
- Okay.
And how do you feel?
- Angry.
- - All right. Did he hit you?
- No.
- Did you cry?
- Did you feel like crying?
- No.
- I'm just gonna write,
"held back tears. "
Wait, stop writing that.
That is not true.
If you stop crying,
i'll stop writing it.
I'm not cr...
Uhh!
I deserved that promotion,
not jim.
Oh, man.
Makes me want to put him
in a triangle choke hold and
force him down to the ground and
just keep pressing and pressing.
And then flip him over and then
put him in a hammer lock.
And he's gasping, he's panting.
Every last breath.
And the crowd is going crazy.
And boom!
I emerge victorious!
Aha!
$18,000 and a chance
at the title.
Ooh hah!
Dwight, jim wants you
to keep it down.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:mzinfo@FRS
the Office s06e03
Everyone, now would be
a good time to freshen up,
because I'd like everyone to meet in
the conference room in five minutes.
And I suggest that you bring a snack,
because we may be in there for a while.
- Michael...
- Yes?
- Can I talk to you
in my office for a second?
- Mmm,
sure, but could I first
talk to you in my office?
Can I also be a boss?
Look, it doesn't take a genius to know that
any organization thrives when it has two leaders.
Go ahead, name a country that
doesn't have two presidents.
A boat that sets sail
without two captains.
Where would catholicism be
without the popes?
I have noticed that we...
Welcome.
Thank you.
I've noticed we've been having
a lot of conference room meetings.
And I'm wondering if perhaps
those are a bit, um...
- Disruptive.
- Yes.
No, I don't think they are.
I think the meetings
are very important.
Okay, maybe we should
talk specifics.
- Let's do.
- Okay.
Yesterday, we had a meeting
about planets.
N... Well, to be fair, jim...
James...
Jimothy...
To be fair, jimothy, the...
Ah, that sounds weird.
Are you okay
with being called jim?
- I am.
- All right.
Jim, to be fair,
- the conversation wasn't
about planets...
- Right.
At first. We were talking about
introducing a line of toilet paper.
And what part of the human body
does one use toilet paper upon?
So you draw a line from there
to the other planets,
and I think by the end, we all learned
a little bit about how small we are.
- Yes, I agree.
- Because it's a big universe,
and we're all just little,
tiny specks of dust.
I just think that maybe they're eating
large amounts of the day.
You know what eats a large
amount of the day are naps.
You go to sleep, it's light out, you
wake up, it's dark. That's the whole day.
Where did that day go?
I have no idea.
You mean on a weekend.
Yes.
How about this?
I think our goal should be
we don't have meetings unless
they're absolutely essential.
All right.
No more meetings this week.
Really?
You just agree to that?
I can be very surprising.
What's going on?
I need to fit into
my wedding dress.
However, I'm also pregnant.
You know, it's a myth that women have to
gain more than nine pounds in a pregnancy?
Look at these actresses.
Some of them lose weight.
Hey, did you guys
register for wedding gifts?
We did, but mostly
because people expect us to.
We're also accepting
other gifts not on the registry...
However much.
It's awkward
asking people for money,
but we could really use it.
Why doesn't crate & barrel let you
register for a toaster full of cash?
Perfect.
I hate registries.
Oh, good.
My cousin makes the most amazing
romantic birdhouse mailboxes.
I know I shouldn't tell you, but you'll
still be surprised when you see it.
You're not registered
for a birdhouse, are you?
No, we're not.
Good. Good.
Mm-hmm?
Okay, I thought
I saw people missing.
Yeah, just focus-grouping a product
expansion idea to these folks.
- Got one of each.
- Really?
Hey, stanley, what was the last thing michael
said before I came through the door?
- Stanley, you don't need
to answer that.
- Stanley?
"If you don't smell this,
you're fired. "
Okay, michael, I thought we agreed to not
take up people's time with meetings like these.
What do you mean
by "these people"?
Michael, this is
a conference room meeting.
Oh, hey, everybody, I think
that jim has gone insane,
because he thinks that my office
is a conference room.
- That's not what I meant.
- Listen, jim, no offense,
but when push comes to shove,
what I want is more important
than what you want.
- I disagree.
- What do you guys think?
- ???
- ????
Great. Guys, can I just have
a moment alone with michael?
No, no, no, you don't need
to go anywhere.
Anything that jim
has to say to me,
he can say in front
of these types of people.
That is not what I said,
and, also, I am co-manager, meaning you
are not the only manager anymore.
I am also a co-manager.
That is not
what wallace told us.
That's exactly
That is not the way
I heard it.
I love rivalries...
Michael or jim,
paris or nicole, heidi or I.c.
It's so much fun.
But I guess if i'm really thinking about it
and answering your question honestly,
i'd have to go with I.c.
Heidi's a bad friend,
and her skin is terrible.
It is one thing, me giving you
the co-manager title.
It is another thing,
you bossing me around.
I'm not bossing you around. I'm trying
to do my job, which is sharing your job,
so maybe we should just call
david wallace.
No, no, no. No, we will
not call david wallace.
I will call david wallace.
David wallace is on line two
for you guys.
Or david wallace will call us
on line two. Why don't we just...
- Hey, david. You got jim here.
- This is michael, senior co-manager.
Hey, guys, um, I'm calling,
because, unfortunately,
we will not be able to give out
cost of living raises this year,
and I know people expect it.
However, there just is only a small
amount of money for each branch,
so we're leaving it up to the managers
to decide how to distribute it.
Got it, dave. Sounds like your
classic big-picture decision.
Which will clearly affect the day-to-day
well-being of our employees.
It's probably a little of both.
- Which is it more of?
- Excuse me?
David, I know
that I'm very new at this,
but I have a very good
perspective on how things work.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Michael, are you...
Are you texting me?
I thought maybe we could talk
after this is over.
Look, I need you both
to take care of this.
This is not going
to be a problem, is it?
- Nope, not at all.
- No, it will not be.
- I am on top of it.
- Very good.
- Thanks a lot, david.
- Talk to you later... Okay,
you didn't let me say good-bye.
All right,
I am looking forward to this.
- You don't have to lie.
- I hate the fact that
we have to do this together.
I think we work much better
separately.
When I am irritated
and I look at you,
- I don't see you anymore.
- alright
All I can see is how big and
gross the pores on your nose are.
All right. Let's get started.
Hey, why haven't we ever, um...
We have.
You know, there's no easy way
to do this.
I say we add 1.5%
to their paychecks
and don't say anything about it.
Do you mean, like break in
in the middle of the night
and change the numbers
on payroll?
No, we can do it
during the day.
It doesn't have to be
that dramatic, jim.
Okay.
You know what would help is
a pros and cons list
for our options.
Jim, don't take this
the wrong way.
Are you gonna
take this the wrong way?
It's hard to tell so far.
You use your brain
too much.
Are you advocating
that I use it less?
Sometimes the smartest people
don't think at all.
- You just came up with that.
- As I was saying it.
Okay, so for the 1.5% increase, pro...
Everyone gets a little bit.
Con... You look like a nerd.
Con... No one gets as much
as they did last year.
Pro... You get to share your pros
and cons list with the other nerds.
Pro... No favoritism.
Con... You unzip your pants,
and you find that there's
a calculator down there.
I've been studying michael
for years,
and I've condensed what
I've learned into this chart...
How michael spends his time.
As you can see, we have procrastinating
and distracting others,
and this tiny sliver here
is critical thinking.
I made it bigger,
so that you could see it.
Hey, pam,
I heard that you were registered,
but I didn't hear where.
I don't think
we registered anywhere.
We just want cash.
Like money?
Like you...
You want my money?
Mm-hmm.
Will you take a check?
Yeah.
Cool.
In the memo line,
i'm gonna write,
"to love's eternal glory. "
Okay.
Wait till monday.
Is this what I've become?
Materialistic?
Shallow?
I feel horrible.
Oh, look!
"mrs. Pam halpert!"
that's the first time
I've seen it in writing.
You know, the more
I think about it,
the more I think we should
give it to the salesmen.
That will not go over well.
I know. I just think it seems smart
to keep the salesmen happy right now.
Course I know that this
might come off as biased,
so you know what? Let us...
Oh, my god, are you gonna make another
pro and con list? I'm gonna kill myself.
I'm not gonna let you
stop me from thinking.
No, I could not do that, jim.
I can see it
in your crusty little eyes
that you are going
to make everything perfect.
If I can just think
this through,
if I could just think it
exactly right,
I can make this perfect,
and then I can go down
every avenue,
and every avenue
off of that avenue,
- and then another avenue.
And then another...
- Michael.
- You have a lot of strengths.
- Oh, I do? Tell me what they are.
I think that you are able to take
constructive criticism very well.
Ha! That...
I am not known for that.
But there is
a reason why I'm here.
Yes, you went over my head
to wallace.
No, it's because you also have
a lot of weaknesses, michael.
Okay. Well, why don't you
tell me what those are, jim?
Why don't you enliven me?
I don't think you're good
at making tough decisions.
- Ah.
- At thinking out the options,
and then stating that
decision very clearly,
especially when it's
an unpopular decision.
Okay, here's
a tough decision for you.
- You suck. You suck.
Is that clear enough for you?
- wait, but...
maybe I'm here for a reason,
because I might have
some good ideas, too.
I've been sitting out there,
and I've been learning a lot,
and maybe I can just bring
something different to the table.
Okay, skippy, here we go.
Why don't you run yourself
out there and tell them?
You call it.
This had better be terrible.
Could I have everyone's attention,
please? I have some tough news, so
I'm just gonna
give it to you straight.
Truth is, we only have so much
money for raises this year,
so the simple fact is some people will
get raises and some people won't.
Now, what we've decided is,
we are gonna give those
raises to the sales staff.
Wait. Seriously?
Look, you guys are smart,
so I'm just leveling with you.
I'm just trying to
treat you like adults.
Thank you, jim, for thinking
that we're smart people.
But I do not understand.
If we're such smart adults,
then why don't we get raises?
Excellent question, genius.
It's because jim wants to give
the raises to his friends
and the people he sleeps with.
- Ooh, easy. That's not it at all.
- ???
- Really what it is is about the money
the sales staff brings into the office.
- What's going on?
Jim is only giving raises
to the salesmen.
What the hell? Why are you
being such a jerk?
Hold on, kelly.
Would it help you to know
that jim thinks you're smart?
No. How is that
gonna repair ryan's car?
This is ridiculous!
How could he do this to us?
Okay, dwight, you know what?
You'd be getting the raise so...
What about all these people, huh?
How is it fair to them?
- Exactly.
- Totally.
We work just as hard as the sales
people. We deserve raises.
- Yes.
- Yes. They don't get 'em
if we don't get 'em.
My kid needs shoes!
- You want to tell him
he doesn't get shoes?
- yeah
Her kid needs shoes, jim!
- What the hell?
- ???
- ????
wow. I'm just gonna rewind
and back off a bit, so...
???
That was good.
Okay, all right.
Well, we all know
it's hard to be a boss, right?
You know what?
Look around you.
These are your best friends.
These are the people who will
open their hearts to you.
They all have heart-ons
for you,
and that is a gift.
So in terms of gifts,
we should be giving
each other gifts.
Angela, yes, lend oscar
a cup of sugar.
- What are you talking about? Michael!
- We just need to hear your plan for our raise.
My plan...
A man... Panama.
That's not how that goes.
You're not saying anything.
At least jim
was being direct.
Thank you, meredith. When he
was telling us his dumbass plan.
We would just like to know
what's happening.
Are we getting a raise,
yes or no?
All right, let me get this clear.
Does everybody want a raise?
yes!
All right, everyone
wants a raise,
so what we're going to do
is go into here,
and we will not come out
until we do.
Again, that gives us
no information.
This isn't a game, you know?
It's our livelihood!
What about a raise
based on merit?
- Rank each person individually.
- Mm-hmm.
Piece of cake.
Ryan, obviously the best.
Well, obviously.
Too bad he's a temp and
doesn't count, so let's get started.
- Are you making a...
- Nope. I'm numbering the paper.
- Just...
- Yeah, I don't understand
how they can even consider
giving money to some people
and not the rest of us.
It's not like we're
not gonna see the checks.
- We're in accounting.
- I am so pissed at this company.
- And jim.
- Yeah.
Who said that?
- I think it was creed.
- Yep.
It's going really well,
actually.
Each boston baked bean
represents half a percent raise,
we each got 24 beans,
so the idea is,
you place the bean on the picture
of who you think deserv... Who's that?
Toby.
He's not a part of this.
You know that.
Just wanted to draw
a picture of him.
Okay, your move.
All right, who to pick?
- Who to pick?
- Here we go.
I will skip a turn.
Okay, you're gonna still have
to play that bean. You know that.
I need more time.
Wallace sent an e-mail
about a meeting next week.
He wants you both to respond.
People are starting to notice
how terrible jim is.
It's great.
Eventually,
they'll rise up and revolt.
My only hope is that they do it
sooner rather than later.
If the people here
were our founding fathers,
the revolutionary war would
have been delayed ten years,
because stanley washington
was napping,
and phyllis hancock was still
signing the declaration,
and kevin jefferson
was distracted by a butterfly.
Come on in.
That's right.
Come in, feast your eyes.
They determine our worth
by putting beans upon our faces.
What the hell?
Things were not this bad
when just michael was manager.
Hey, what are you guys
doing in here?
What does a bean mean?
on this very old,
frizzy-haired picture of me?
Michael,
what does a bean mean?
Jim?
I was just trying
to be unbiased.
What does a bean mean?
Someone please explain it
to kevin.
Why can't you? My time
is just as valuable as yours.
Not according to the beans.
This is how you make
this important decision?
There's no way that stanley gets
more beans than me. That is ridiculous.
This is how it works.
It's not so much that I might not
get a raise. It's just demeaning.
Thank you.
That is exactly...
By the way,
I would also like a raise.
Yeah, I would, too.
Are we idiots?
What right does jim have
to claim authority, hmm?
Is he as good a salesman as i?
Is he as matronly as phyllis?
There are moments
where we can affect change.
For a few seconds
every decade, we exist,
and these are those seconds.
Let us storm his castle.
Come on.
Tick... Let's get him.
Tick... And drag jim
out of his office.
Tock... Take his keys
away from him.
Tick... That's a clock.
The time is getting very close.
It's now or never.
What say you?
I say no.
No, I mean, what do you
say to my plan?
- ???
okay.
- ????
- ???
what does a bean mean?
How you doing?
Uh, on a scale of one to ten,
i'd say I'm about a four.
Oh, what are you usually?
Six. You?
Usually a ten,
but I'm feeling like a zero.
I mean, a performance-based raise
sounded like a good idea, right?
I know, I know.
We tried to find
the fairest way to do it.
- Yes, we did.
- I just...
What?
Um, nothing. I just...
I used to have
to do this part alone,
and it was the worst.
I have something
I would like to give you.
- michael! come on
- ????
Michael's my only friend
left in the office.
Except pam...
I think.
Is she still upset?
- Michael!
- Michael, you cannot
just keep avoiding us like this!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What's in here?
Gin.
Ooh.
Just pretend we're not here.
Heard you guys are looking
for cash for the wedding?
Yeah, I mean,
if it's all the same for you.
Question for you.
Would you guys rather have
$100 now
or $5,000 a year from now?
$100 now for sure.
Because you just give me
$50 to cover the broker fee,
I put in 100 of my
own money as the gift...
Yeah. No, no, I'll, um...
The hundred.
I'll just take the hundred.
Instead of $5,000
a year from now?
How sure is this?
The guy has an algorithm
to determine the winner
of any given
college basketball game.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
don't tell jim.
www.tvsubtitles.net