- Uh-oh.
Okay, okay,
nobody panic.
Listen up, listen up.
Everyone, follow me
to the shelter.
We've got enough food
for 14 days.
After that, we have
a difficult conversation.
- My bad.
Space Heater and Fan
were both on high,
plugged into
the same outlet, so...
- uh, it's saying the server
went down?
Does Anybody know that password?
'cause otherwise,
we can't do any work.
- Uh...try "password."
- Nope.
- Try zero, Zero, Zero,
Zero, zero, zero.
- No.
- Okay, now try Zero, Zero,
Zero, Zero, zero, one.
- Okay, I'm not doing
every number.
- Wait, um, does anyone remember
when it was set up?
- Uh...it was, like,
eight years ago?
- Lord of the rings stuff?
I don't know, I'm just trying
to think of things
that were happening
at the time.
- Um, everyone was getting
their driver's license.
- Why don't we just call the
I.T. Guy who set it up?
What's the name of the guy
in Glasses, again?
- Okay, moving backwards,
our I.T. Guys have been...
glasses, turban, ear hair,
fatty 3, shorts, fatty 2,
lozenge,
and fatso.
I think lozenge was the one
who installed it.
- I got it.
Try, um--
[coughs]
- you know what, it made me
laugh when I heard it,
but Pam got really offended.
- Big boobs.
- Drama queen?
- Nosy?
- You're typing "big boobs"?
- I'm trying everything.
- Try "big boobs" with a "z."
- That's--
[ding]
the password. We're in.
- All right.
- Wow.
- Yes.
- The important thing is...
this kept us secure, people.
[cheerful music]
♪ ♪
- Morning.
- How's it going?
- Hey, I'm wuphf.
- I'm facebook.
- What's up, facebook?
- I sent you a facebook message
yesterday,
I still haven't heard
anything back.
- You should've sent me a wuphf.
- A what?
- When you send a wuphf,
it goes to your home phone,
cell phone,
Email, Facebook, twitter,
and home screen.
All at the same time.
[phone rings]
[melodic tone]
[robotic voice]
Wuphf.
[together]
- Wuphf!
- Dot-com!
- Thanks, Erin.
- Sure.
Pam.
- Mm-hmm?
- I don't wanna be
a lousy snitch.
- Okay.
- Ryan has been using the color
printer for his business a lot,
and as office administrator--
- Oh, it's okay.
- But it's not for--
- let it go.
- Yes, I invested in wuphf.
It's actually
a really great idea,
and I can't believe
it didn't exist before.
And I know Ryan's kind of
a sketchy guy,
but Hey, I married Jim.
I've done my part
for the nice guy.
Now I want a bedroom set.
- I think an INVESTORS ski trip,
frankly,
is the best idea.
It will be a bonding experience.
- I love it.
- I was looking at a Trail map,
and I was thinking that We
should start on a Bunny hill,
because I've never
actually been skiing.
And then work our way up
to death drop.
- Great, so we got our first
offer to buy the company.
[slaps desk]
- You're kidding.
- We could sell,
but why think so small?
We can just get a couple
more people involved,
really do this thing
our way.
- You and me, baby.
- New Investors
are key, though.
That's actually
why I came in today.
- Don't you work here full time?
- [chuckles]
Today I was thinking
I would sit down
with a few of the people
who haven't invested yet.
- Mm-hmm.
- Or we could do that together.
If that sounds fun to you.
- That does sound fun to me.
- Awesome.
- Ah, this is good hay.
Yeah.
This is the good stuff.
Mattress quality.
Every fall, growing up,
my Uncle Eldred used to build us
a Maze out of hay Bales
for us kids to play in.
We called it hay place.
Eldred called it hay world.
Eventually, lawyers
were brought in.
But that's all behind us.
Hay place lives on.
Watch it, watch it.
Hello!
Welcome to hay place.
A place for hay.
- Don't forget to make a Broom.
- Oh, the petting zoo
closes at 2:00,
and the goat roast
is at 3:00.
Come on in, enjoy!
- Hey.
I'm kind of in the mood
for a roll in the hay.
- Roll in the hay,
five dollars.
- No, I meant...
- Oh, our contract.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes, why don't we meet
at the usual spot.
Uh...
I've got a half an hour
during lunch
in-between the historical
reenactment
of the dunmore farm slaughters
and the onion boil.
- Perfect.
- So, uh...
excuse me, get off of there.
Those are show Bales,
not play Bales.
- All right, Thank you, I will--
I will send the contracts over
right away.
All right.
Whoo!
I am on the first hot sale
streak of my life.
I think it all comes from
feeding cece,
because no matter
how much she resists,
I sell her those carrots.
Let's be honest--
if I can make mushed carrots
seem better than a boob...
I can pretty much
sell anything.
- Commission comes out to...
dunh-duh-na-dah!
Zero.
- Mm-Kay, Well,
it can't be zero, kev.
- I entered the sale,
and I hit enter,
and I said, "dunh-duh-na-dah!"
I'm pretty sure
I timesed it right.
- You met your commission cap
last week.
So from here until the end
of the fiscal year,
your commission will be zero.
- What are you talking about?
We--we have a commission cap?
- It's a new corporate policy.
- Dunh-duh-na-dah!
- Is this job really about
the money for you, Jim?
I mean, isn't this
where you fell in love?
- A commission cap takes away
my incentive to sell.
So you realize I now have
no reason to work, right?
- When you're dealing
with a large organization,
sometimes you have to put up
with policies you don't like.
I wish my gym didn't allow full
nudity in the locker room.
Okay, seeing these old guys
walking around naked
feels almost passive-aggressive.
But I deal with it.
'cause it's policy.
See what I mean?
- Nope.
- Nudity makes me uncomfortable.
- Okay.
- My gym allows it.
I wish they didn't,
but it's policy.
So I respect it,
and I just--
keep a low--you know,
I look away.
Think about your commission cap
as a naked old man
in a gym locker room.
- Excuse me, everyone.
Sex!
Now that I have
your attention...
- you don't have our attention.
- Money!
- I'm listening.
- You had me at "sex."
- Pervert.
- You have all of our attention
just by screaming anything.
- That's good to know.
[screams]
- What do you want
to say, Michael?
- Wuphf!
All right,
I've warmed them up for you.
You have the floor, Ryan.
- How's everybody doing?
- Whoo!
- Good!
Now, a lot of you have already
staked out
your corner of the wuphf empire.
Raise your hand
if I'm describing you.
Great.
- Yes, I have a dream.
And It's not some m.L.K. Dream
for equality.
I want to own
a decommissioned lighthouse.
And I want to live
at the top.
And nobody knows I live there.
And there's a button
that I can press,
and it'll launch that lighthouse
into space.
- For my current Investors,
things are going great.
- We already have a buyer.
- Really? Who?
- Washington university.
I don't even want
to think about selling
until our numbers
get into the billions.
- At least.
- So I've decided to open up
a second round of investment
to friends and family.
- Oh, god. Hold on to
your wallets, ladies.
- Did you ever think of wuphf
as an EMERGENCY notification
system,
like, for college campuses
with shooters or gas leaks?
- No, no--Oscar, it's not--
it's not a digital rape whistle.
Wuphf is about fun.
- That's right.
- Fun, communication,
connection.
- What's your money situation?
- Well, it's tight,
as with any start-up.
- Sure, how long can you sustain
this without a cash infusion?
- We have nine solid days.
I love these questions.
Keep 'em coming.
- I'm sorry,
nine days until what?
- Bankruptcy?
- Wait, Ryan, so this could be
over by the weekend?
- How long do you think
a week is?
- No, not this weekend;
next weekend.
We were gonna go
on the investors ski trip.
I bought poles.
- Well, since I have
no incentive to sell,
I've cleaned my car,
organized my desk,
and taken a multivitamin.
So...
what now?
Pam.
[sighs]
Okay, now I've tried everything.
- Did you prank Dwight?
- No.
- Well, you like that.
- Yeah, it's not as fun
if I'm not blowing off work.
- I love you,
but I'm kinda busy,
so I need you to figure this one
out on your own.
- [blows raspberry]
- [chuckling]
- Oscar said Wuphf only has
enough money for nine days.
- Check this out.
- All that color.
- Look at that.
Triple your investment
by January.
- Anyone can just throw numbers
up on a chart.
What are you doing
to make it happen?
- Well, earlier today,
I was emailing
someone by the name of
John legend.
- There you go.
- You have his email?
- A lot of these guys
are just Mac.Com,
@ their website whatever.
We get that guy wuphfing,
it's all over.
- I want my money back.
- Do not talk like that,
Stanley.
- Ryan, just tell us your plan.
- Okay, all right.
I know what you wanna see.
I'll be right back.
[smacking door]
Hey, kids, was that fun?
- [all] Yeah!
- All right.
- I wanna go on it again.
- Oh, I bet you do.
You know what?
When I was a little kid,
they couldn't get me
off the hayride.
But it's gonna cost you
three more bucks.
Wow!
This brings back memories.
[inhales deeply]
Hay stacking, hay throwing...
and at the end of it all,
one lucky boy would be crowned
hay king.
I always wanted
to be hay king.
The world shines on Mose.
- Where have you been?
I've been waiting.
- Uh, can we move this
to the end of the day?
- No, I--I think you should
make time for it.
- I found the needle
in the haystack!
- Hey, congratulations.
Do you know what your prize is?
- I don't know.
- Nothing. Life lesson?
Some tasks are not worth doing.
- Dwight?
- Wuphf T-shirts.
Who wants one?
Just imagine that you're
at spring break daytona beach.
- Here we go.
- Okay?
Everyone's like, "hey dude,
what's up with all the hotties
in the wuphf shirts?"
Or, Uh, "hey, what's up
with that helicopter?"
"It's ry from wuphf!"
- "It's Ryan the wuphf guy!"
- "Yo, ry from wuphf!"
- "He's up there."
- "What's he dropping?"
"Wow, what's falling on
us, man?"
Wuphf condoms!
50,000 condoms
out of the sky.
- Look at that!
He threw 'em on the ground!
- Look, this is
a marketing campaign.
You got nine days.
Let's say you do get the money.
What are you going
to do with it?
- The first lesson of silicon
valley, actually,
is that you only think
about the user, the experience.
You actually don't think
about the money.
Ever.
- That sounds weird.
- No, it's not weird, Andy,
and you know what else?
We have an offer
from Washington university.
So monetize that.
- Are you guys meeting
about wuphf?
You know that that
was my idea, right?
- [gasps]
- I said to Ryan,
"I try to call you,
"and you don't have your phone.
"I try to I.M. You,
and you're not online.
"I wish there was a way that I
could do everything all at once,
"and I could just be like this
little dog going,
'Ruff! Ruff! Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!'"
- baby, baby, baby--
- I think I'm gonna stay here.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- I do, I do.
This isn't right.
- I help you with your things,
and you help me with my things.
- But I--it's not right.
- [whIspering] I got this,
it's okay,
don't worry about this.
- Is it any particular branch
of Washington university?
- The Washington university
Public health fund.
- W.U.P.H.F.
- Oh, god.
- They only want it
for the initials.
- The domain name.
Yeah, they do.
- I move we sell.
- What?
- Yeah, sell.
- Sell.
- Get us out of this.
- Have some faith in this idea.
- If everybody wants to sell,
we sell, right?
- I won't sell.
And you know what?
Ryan and I have
the majority of shares.
Isn't that right?
- Yes.
You alone do, actually.
- I--yes.
We're not selling.
I will not sell.
[children laughing]
- Awesome.
- Do you mind if we
share this bale?
- Sure.
- There's no charge
to sit on the hay, is there?
- Probably.
- I mean, wouldn't you think
the Ten dollars
to build your own Broom
would include the hay
and not just the instructions?
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, I'm starting to think
this guy is just trying to make
money off the holiday.
- Yeah, instead of hay place
it should be pay place.
- [laughs]
- Don't laugh at me.
- No, no, no, I wasn't--
I was just laughing
at your joke.
- Oh.
- Pay place.
- Mm.
Yeah, so we can celebrate
Thanksgiving-me-your-money day.
- [laughs]
That's humorous.
- Thank you.
- You guys know how to get out?
[kids shouting]
- Hi, Michael.
- Can't talk, saving the planet.
- Oh, we don't recycle.
- We don't?
Well, why have I been
separating the trash
into Whites and colors?
- I'm sure no one
asked you to do that.
- Eight years.
- Listen, I know
you really like Ryan--
- no, I won't even consider it.
- Michael, I...
I hate to say this, but...
You know this special bond
that you've always felt
with Ryan,
where, like, you're best friends
or you're his mentor
or something?
- Right, Yes, yeah.
Best friend/mentor.
- Michael, I think that
that feeling only goes one way.
And I think
that Ryan knows that,
and he's taking advantage
of you.
- I think you are wrong.
- And there are a lot
of other people in This office
who have money at stake.
Other people you care about.
- You may be right.
I may be crazy.
- Don't.
- I'm just saying that I think
I agree with your point.
- Yeah, but in a jokey way where
you're gonna start singing.
- I thought it might make me
feel better.
- Okay.
Go ahead.
- ♪ But it just may be
a lunatic... ♪
no.
- Ooh, nice, wasting time,
here we go.
- Hey, back off.
It's solitaire.
- Hey, kid--
hear you're looking for work.
- Talk to me.
- How far can you reach
those Lovely long arms of yours?
Eh, put 'em down.
How long
can you hold that pretty little
breath of yours?
- [inhales]
- Good.
- Hey, Jim?
Are you distracting
these people?
- We're working.
- Can you at least
try to look busy?
- [exhales]
- The moment Darla put
the cupcake in her mouth,
her daddy pulled her aside
and said,
"you're too fat.
No one's gonna like you
if you're too fat."
The next time I saw David Geffen
was at the buffalo club.
"I love you, you gay bastard,"
I said.
"You gay bastard," I s--
"gay ba--"
"gay B--"
- Michael, how's it going, bro?
- Good, good, bro.
- Hey, thanks so much for having
my back out there.
- Always have your back.
So any ideas on how we can get
over this nine-day hump here?
- I have nothing but ideas.
The thing is,
they all require money.
- Nine days, though.
That's, like...
- look, I know I've tapped you
so hard.
- Yes, you have tapped this.
Hard.
- [laughs]
Oh, you are funny, Michael.
You--people--people don't give
you enough credit.
- Maybe I could take a second
mortgage on my condo.
- Well, a lot of people
are doing that.
And there don't seem to be
any consequences.
And they say the rates
have never been lower.
- So you would think
that's a good idea for me to do?
- Think about this:
You and me on a private plane
flown by our private pilot--
- Mm-hmm.
- Eating our private meal cooked
by our private chef.
- Yeah, well, we never even have
dinner now, so...
- we totally should.
- Tonight?
- I gotta work on this.
- Oh, right.
What am I saying?
Rain check.
- Yeah.
- And now, by show of applause,
we will crown this year's
hay king.
All in favor of purebred.
[applause]
Put your hands together
for...
mixed bread.
[applause]
And Let's hear it for...
purebred.
[applause]
Mm.
It would appear we have
a three-way tie.
I have no choice but to pick
the hay king myself.
I pick...
me!
I am your hay king!
All Hail your hay king!
Did I truck 300 Bales of hay
to a parking lot to rectify
some childhood disappointment?
Yes.
- So if I were
to call dunder Mifflin
and ask for miss Angela Martin,
would I get through to you?
- You would.
And if I were to call your House
and ask for your wife,
would I get through to you?
- My wife passed away
a few years ago.
- How tragic.
Very sorry to hear that.
- Thank you.
- Help!
Hello?
Oh!
Help!
- Consider it a wuphf
in person.
- You're doing the wrong thing.
You're gonna lose
Michael's investment,
you're gonna lose ours.
- You got this crazy opportunity
to get our money back.
Tell Mike to sell.
- If you tell Michael to sell,
he'll sell.
- I'm betting on myself.
- It's a bad bet.
- Hello.
- Hey.
It's an ambush here.
Nobody here believes
in this company.
Will you tell them
they're wrong?
- It's not that we don't believe
in the company.
We don't believe in you.
- All those in favor of selling,
say aye.
- Aye.
Do not agree to sell,
which is to say nay.
- What is wrong with you?
What happened to you
in high school?
- Michael, are you that blind?
- I'm not blind!
I know exactly who he is.
He is selfish and lazy
and image-obsessed,
and he is a bad friend.
And he's also clever.
And he shoots incredibly high.
And he may just make it.
But you know what,
even If he doesn't,
I would rather go broke
betting on my people
than get rich all by myself
on some island
like a castaway.
And there is no middle ground.
- You're gonna lose
all of our money.
- Only If he fails.
And you know what?
Ryan, I believe in you.
Just like I believe
in all of you.
You have nine days to save
Everybody's money.
- Oh...
that's a lot of pressure.
I--I'm gonna need
some more time.
- You can't have it.
- Okay.
I won't let you down.
- Angela?
Angela!
- The world sends people
your way...
Ryan came to me
through a temp agency.
Andy was transferred here.
No idea where Creed came from.
The point is
you just have to play with
the cards that you're dealt.
Jim, that guy is an ace.
Dwight is my king Up my sleeve.
Phyllis is my old maid.
Oscar is my queen.
That's easy.
Gimme a hard one.
That's what Oscar said.
Toby is the instruction card
you throw away.
Pam's a solid seven.
And Yeah, you know what?
Ryan is probably, like, a two.
But sometimes twos
can be wild.
So watch out.
And I am obviously the joker.
So...
[phone rings]
that's, uh--
[melodic tone]
[robotic voice]
- wuphf from Ryan Howard.
Decided to sell company.
Thanks, bro.
Hell of a ride.
- Thank god.
[phone rings]
- Gabe Lewis.
- Now, listen here, gabe,
you're too fat.
No one's gonna like you
if you're too fat.
I made some changes
to my book.
See if you like them.
- Well, jo--
- now, I love reading,
and I hate being interrupted.
Shut up and listen,
you gay bastard.
Chapter one.
I was born, not into luxury
Nor poverty,
but into adversity, and for
that, I thank the lord.
My father was a man.
That's all we can know.
After I learned to ride a bike,
there was no stopping me.
I would ride up Magnolia Street
and down azalea Lane.
Which would later become my--
- All right, good night, gabe.
Just wanted to say thanks again,
'cause I really think I made
good use of my day, oh!
Sorry.
- And fate has obliged me
with plenty of battles,
the first being a hard--
www.tvsubtitles.net