-Oh. Hi, mate.
-Oh, hi. Yeah. Morning.
Did you just have a shower?
No, no, no. Oh, yeah.
Jogged in from, home.
So nice to freshen up.
You jogged in from Woy Woy?
No, no, I, um...
park a few blocks away
and jog in from the car.
Oh. I thought I saw your car downstairs.
Yea maybe. Maybe.
Umm. [awkward pause]
Yeah, I love jogging. Do you train?
I sometimes catch the train. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Well, I'll see you around.
Yeah, you definitely will,
because I'll be at my desk all day.
[laughter]
Okay. Well, I'll see you there.
You will for the next nine hours.
[theme music playing]
Yeah, so with our stock size cardboard
cartons, we can do 500 to 1000 for $2.45.
And anything over that is $2.35.
-[Deborah] I handle the accounts…
-[Nick] 300 would fit on a pallet.
She did what?
Thank you.
Jesus freaking Christ.
[door closes]
Have you registered us as a religion?
Yes.
[Deborah] Hannah is a riddle.
Swallowed by an idiot,
and shat out by a moron.
Why would you do that?
[Hannah] Well, I was reading
about successful billionaires
and how they avoid paying tax.
And it's incredible how many ways
you can avoid paying it.
Yeah, it's called tax evasion.
It's illegal.
No, no, I mean, these are legitimate
exemptions that you can apply for.
Like, you look
at the criteria for religion.
It's freaky how similar we are
to a religion already.
We sell packaging.
"No idea is so outlandish
that it should not be considered."
I think.
I think that was Winston Churchill. If I--
I'm the person in charge of financials.
And I'm the person in charge of the person
in charge of financials, what's the...
problem?
So you wouldn't be worried
if the ATO sent someone in to investigate?
-Nope.
-Great.
Because someone from the tax department
is coming in at three.
Three today?
Yeah, but you've got nothing
to worry about, right?
No. I wish they were coming in
at two, actually.
-Why don't I change it to tw--
-No, I've got a meeting at two.
Let's leave it at three. It's good.
And then they they're checking to see
if we are a...
Religious organisation.
-Religious organisation. Thought so.
-Yep.
Religion. Okay.
What are we?
What do religions do?
[Hannah] I have undertaken the
responsibility of saving this office.
So it's no surprise that my staff
now look to me as a saviour.
A teacher...
a therapist, a healer.
And sometimes you just need
to remind people of that.
So that they remind other people.
People say from like the tax office.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Welcome.
[Hannah] Yes. Thank you.
Thank you so much
for attending this morning.
It's lovely to start
off the day like this.
Okay, everyone.
What would you say our
collective focus is?
-[Lizzie] Boxes.
-[Hannah] Think bigger.
-Big boxes.
-More creative, more abstract.
Like a box
with a tiny moustache and glasses?
Family. Yeah?
Love.
Unity. I mean, we could be selling juice.
-What kind of juice?
-It doesn't matter,
-I like pineapple.
-[exasperated] What?
I don't like green smoothies.
The juice is irrelevant.
Yeah, we could be selling anything,
but our collective focus would still be…?
Boxes.
Okay, item number two. Rituals.
God, we've got so many
great rituals here, don't we?
We've got meetings.
-[Lizzie] Recycling.
-[Hannah] Recycling.
Yes, Lizzie. Love that one, actually.
-Morning tea
-Morning tea.
[Deborah] Time wasting.
Okay, Deborah.
No need for that.
Three. A leader.
Uh Oh! Whose that? [chuckles]
Number 4. Followers.
My people.
And I look at this and I think,
God, that really sums us up, doesn't it?
But do you know what?
It's actually describing?
A religion.
How did you know that.
Item five is a prayer room.
Yes, it is. A prayer room.
So I was thinking, God,
we operate so much like a religion,
why don't we just register as one?
[Martin] No, we are not a religion,
Hannah.
Some of us already have a religion.
I'm Buddhist.
Oh, Namaste.
[Hannah] You know what? Doesn't matter.
This is not to replace anyone's religion.
It's to run adjacent.
You can't force someone
to join a religion.
Well you can.
But it doesn't end well.
-Is this a tax dodge?
-[Deborah] Yep.
The ATO are coming in today
to shut it down.
[Hannah] Not true.
We're going to be
operating business as usual.
Just a couple of little tweaks.
Tina, would you like to be in charge
of converting the storeroom
-into a prayer room?
-No.
[Lloyd] Oh, why?
Why would you want to use the storeroom?
What about the toilets?
The toilets?
Show a little respect, Lloyd.
Okay, we're not doing
the prayer room in the toilets.
Disgusting, actually. Any takers?
[Greta] Love to.
-We'll do it.
-[Hannah] Perfect.
It's like Hannah googled
how to start a religion.
It took a bit of deep diving,
but I think I found it.
How to start a religion
in eight easy steps.
It's literally the first thing
that comes up.
It says here that religious leaders
offer spiritual and moral guidance
whilst giving back to the community.
[Hannah] Okay, yep, was just about to
write that down.
Guidance. Don't even have to look.
It's so in my blood.
Oh, am I writing Hannah?
Am I writing my own name?
Oh, it's charity.
That's how natural it comes to me.
You know what, Marty?
As head of HR,
You're burdened
with a lot of people's problems.
It's not a burden.
And I'm thinking you need someone
to talk to.
To seek some guidance. Yeah?
I want you to think of me like, um,
like pastoral care.
[phones ringing]
Hey, can you send me an email?
[Lloyd] Yep.
What about?
Anything.
Okay. [keyboard clacks]
-And sent.
-[email notification pings]
-Did you get it?
-Nope.
Oh.
Okay. Hang on.
-[email notification pings]
-Get that one?
Nope. [chuckles]
Oh, wonder if it's a server thing
or something.
[email notification pings]
[Deborah] Seeing as Hannah is apparently
now head of financials.
I am forwarding her all of my emails.
And I will be making sure
she gets a lot of them.
It's a bit of a community service
what we do here, isn't it?
-[email notification pings]
-It's a, it's a job.
-This is a business.
-[email notification pings]
It's a family business.
-Like the...
-[email notification pings]
-Smith family or the Vinnies family
Or the Salvos family.
They're an army.
-[email notification pings twice]
-You gonna check your emails?
-Hmm.
-[email notification pings]
[Door opens]
[Hannah] Ah, Deb.
[Deborah] You're interrupting
my sacred ritual.
And it won't happen again.
Something kooky is going on.
I keep getting your emails.
Really?
And I got, like, 15 from Lloyd
that just say doggy doo doo.
Well, that is strange.
Okay, I can see that you're
going through something.
[Breathes deeply] Umm,
is everything all right at home?
-A bit tricky with the old ball and chain.
-Yeah.
That's it.
Ooh, sorry.
Good luck with your fraud.
Oh it's-- It's not fraud. Oh, no.
[door slams]
[knocks]
Yoo hoo.
Hey, do you want two new hole punches?
-Oh, put them on my desk, please.
-Got it.
[Greta] Would you like five old phones?
[Nick] Err, just give me four.
[exclaims]
Is someone sleeping in here?
Yeah, that would be Lloyd.
-Yeah, that checks out.
-Yep.
[Lloyd] The daily commute from Woy Woy is
killing me,
so I've spent a couple of nights
in the storeroom.
I don't want everyone knowing about it.
It's not a big deal.
It's been one, two, three...
Four-- yeah, four nights this week.
It's nothing.
[strains]
Eww. What the hell is that stain?
Oh, hopefully nothing to do with Lloyd.
[chuckles]
Actually, kind of looks like Hannah.
Oh, my God, it does eh?
[Greta laughs]
[Lizzie] Oi You two, this isn't a disco.
Get back to work.
Wait, Lizzie.
We think we may have found an apparition.
-[Nick] Oh, yes.
-It's just a stain.
No, no, no, it wasn't there when we
started.
It's like it just appeared out of nowhere.
And it kind of looks like Hannah,
don't you think?
I don't see it.
Oh. Try squinting.
You know the thing about apparitions?
You confess your deepest, darkest secrets
to them, and you get rewarded.
Yeah. Maybe I should try it.
You totally should.
-Mm-hmm.
-Stand back.
-Oh.
I once took three plates of nigiri off
a sushi train, and I didn't pay for it.
Thief!
Let's see what gift the gods bring,
shall we?
[Nick] We shall.
Oh, would you feel that?
[Greta shivers] Oh.
Idiots.
Hannah.
-[lift dings]
-Ding!
All right, everybody,
it is time for my regular
op shop drop off.
[Deborah] By regular, you mean first ever?
[bag rustles]
Lizzie, would you like to make a donation?
Err, I can donate some staples.
Chuck them in.
No such thing as a bad donation.
Lloyd, would you like to make a donation?
Oh, I could I could draw you a picture.
Right. There's an example of a bad
donation.
We're always learning. Thank you Lloyd.
Marty! Donation?
I think that might be a no. All right.
Hey, Tina. Tina Arena.
You know what I love about,
eastern spirituality?
-My sandwich.
-Huh?
You're sitting on my sandwich.
Oh. Oh. Oh. I'm sorry.
-Um…
-You can donate it.
I'll get another one.
[Hannah] Okay.
[bag rustles]
[Greta] Here she comes.
I'm sorry. How many corrugated mailer
boxes do you want?
[snaps, fingers]
[whispers ] Pen, pen.
10,000?
Whoa. No.
No. Thank you so much for your business.
I really appreciate it.
You have a lovely day. Thank you.
That was my best ever sale.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Wait, you didn't think
it was because of the...
Surely not.
I did confess, and then I got the sale.
[chair squeaks]
Oh, Sebastian, can you take this bag
and the bag next to Lloyd's desk
with his donations
and then just follow me?
-Sorry.
-Yeah, just grab those two bags.
Follow me.
-[lift dings]
-[Hannah] I love giving back.
Off we go.
It's just so great seeing the gratitude on
their faces, hearing them say thank you.
You saved our lives.
Not that that's why I do it, but.
Yeah, I'd be annoyed
if they didn't say anything.
[keyboards clacking]
Hey Deborah.
-Have you seen--
-No.
It's a light green plastic bag.
Have you seen that around at all?
Alright.
Knock, knock.
Who's there? Opportunity.
[woman] Finley who?
Flinley Craddick.
-Finley. Finn.
-Flin-- It's two L's. Flinley.
-Fin.
-Flin.
-Flinley.
-Finley.
It doesn't even matter.
Should we just drop them
like it's hot here?
As per yoozh?
Why not take them through
to the back to Malcolm?
[sarcastically]
He'll sort through them, as per yoozh.
Okay. Don't need, don't need that.
Well, this is a bit more like it,
isn't it?
Tea towels on the door.
You should have a look in there.
There's some very good stuff
in there, my friend.
Oh, belt, belt. Good accessories.
Oh, Swannies Beanie.
[sings Sydney Swans theme song]
Is that Martin's?
No, not, not Martin's.
I'm sorry, folks,
we can't take wet clothes.
Well, I don't think that they're wet.
[gags]
Umm, don't know
where we got this bag from.
Probably accidentally picked it up.
I think that's Lloyd's bag.
[Hannah] Let's put the underpants away.
God, it just…feels good
to give back to community, doesn't it?
Yeah. I don't really have a choice
in the matter.
What... was that?
Community service.
It's part of my parole deal.
Meaning the old slammer.
What for?
Sebastian.
Don't. We don't ask those questions.
That's not appropriate.
Now that he said it though, like out loud.
What--?
[Malcom] Don't worry. It wasn't murder.
[chuckles]
Nah. Tax evasion.
Oh.
So I got nine years for it.
That seems like a lot.
Ruined my life.
[chokes up] I lost everything.
-[Malcolm] If I could go back,
-Yeah.
I would do it all differently.
Would you?
Well, speaking of going back.
Ooh, sandwich.
What do you reckon
we hit the road Sebastian?
Malcolm. Great to meet you.
Good to see
that you came out of it unscathed.
Well, hardly unscathed.
I haven't told you
about my first night in the cell.
Three guards busted in on me.
Jesus Christ!
[footsteps recede hurriedly]
[Lizzie] Once when I was secretary
of my body corporate,
I had an elderly woman evicted
for hanging tea towels off her balcony.
She died a week later but...
rules are rules so...
[whispers] Thank you.
[office hubbub]
[Greta] The fish is on the hook.
[phones ring, printer whirrs]
[mutters under breath] No way.
-[package rustles]
-[Greta] Oh, what's that?
[Nick] I've got no idea.
[gasps]
[quietly] Shut up!
That’s, that's my hat.
[Nick] So that was a Moncler hat.
I bought with a voucher
my parents got me for my birthday.
It was stupidly expensive,
[incredulously]
and now Lizzie's wearing it.
[Hannah] Can you just Google something?
Can you just Google,
religion, tax fraud, jail?
Just pop that in.
What's umm, what's coming up?
Yeah, I mean, it's mostly stories
of people going to jail for fraud.
[Hannah] Oh my god.
Okay, let's Google something nice.
Kids auditioning for singing contests.
You see how they...you've seen them?
-[Hannah] Oh, my God, that's him.
-[Sebastian] Who?
That's the ATO guy.
It's got to be him, right?
It looks like he's got
that tax stank on him.
Maybe we should just drive to Canberra,
start a new life.
Tassie. Is that better?
Maybe we should just tell them
it was a mistake.
-[Hannah] Yeah, Ok
-I'm sure. They'll be understanding.
Actually...
How hard do you think it would be to,
I don't know, like change identity or...
-[Sebastian] Umm.
-Like, could I, could I be a Carmen?
Would I be a Patricia?
-Might be difficult.
-You think?
-Yeah.
-All right.
-Let's just.
-Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
You know what?
I think I'm going to go up the back way.
[keypad beeps, door closes]
[office chatter]
-[Nick] Hi, Hannah.
-[mutters]
-Hey, Hannah.
What is going on today?
Thank you so much for coming in.
I'm grateful.
Cheers. Thank you.
[footsteps]
Hey guys. Sorry to interrupt.
Has anyone seen my Swans beanie?
Was just hanging up in my office.
It means quite a lot to me.
My son gave it to me.
It's like a red and white woolly hat.
She's donated it, hasn't she?
[Greta] Hey, Lizzie. What's up?
Just went and had a little visit
with the apparition
to score myself some more stuff.
Yeah. About that. Umm...
I ordered that exact same hat
three days ago.
Your point?
It's mine. I ordered it online.
Sounds like a tall story, Nick.
Lizzie. The whole stain thing was a joke.
Apparitions are no joke. Nick.
You are the joke.
An apparition?
Oh, no, I think there might be some
soy sauce I spilt one night.
I tried to clean it up,
but I think I made it worse.
Karma?
If it is, yours is coming.
Cause you were in on it too.
[tinkly phone ringtone]
[feint dance music]
Hey, babe.
-Hey, baby girl. Guess what?
-What?
[Car horn blares]
[laughs] Did you hear that?
Yes, I can hear that.
All right. Here's the deal right?
So you know you said that you want
to spend more time together?
Shauny's organised a bowling night,
and then we're going to go back
to Tommy's after for pizzas.
[Greta] Oh, great, time together with
Shauny and Tommy, cool.
Yeah. Come down so pack up whatever you're
doing and let's go eh?
-Hurry up.
-Sure.
Yeah. Give me a couple of minutes okay?
Karma calling?
No comment.
Bye.
This could be bad Hannah.
[Hannah] How bad?
Jail bad?
Are we both going down?
Well, no, I'm off the hook.
Oh, my God. Damn it.
I mean, it's great. It's great for you.
Do you--
Did you tell him it was just a mistake?
But you don't make mistakes.
Well, that's not entirely true.
I make mistakes. On, on occasion.
Such as this occasion.
-He did give me a phone number.
-[Hannah] He did?
But do not hang up.
Doesn't matter how long it takes.
You need to talk to someone there today.
Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
[quietly] Oh god.
Thank you Deb.
[Hannah] Hey, Deb.
Bless you.
[Deborah] Total bullshit.
I explained the situation. He went away.
Phone number was bullshit too.
Some tech nerd legend created a line
that only leads to hold music.
[phone line ringing]
[hold muzak]
[Lloyd] Probably a good thing I got
evicted.
I might take off actually.
Traffic's going to be building up on the
motorway.
It's a long drive so might listen to a
true crime podcast or something.
Anyway. Have a good weekend.
[hold muzak]
[muzak stops]
Oh, Hel--
[hold muzak starts]
[automated voice]
Your call is important to us.
[theme music playing]