Man.
My delts are blasted.
I wish they had a chart
for how much protein powder to scoop.
- For a 180 pound man with no fat.
- Protein powder.
You cut it with water?
Why don't you just take estrogen?
There you go, boys.
See how papa takes care of you?
I remember when people
thought biceps were all that.
They'd flex them at the discotheque.
I bet you think it's all about core.
- Please.
- Core's critical.
There are four tenets of pilates
that I live my life by.
One: lengthen.
Two: elongate.
I think we all want
to know the same thing.
Who's stronger?
There's only one way to solve that.
Flat curl contest.
Here we go, everybody.
May the manliest man win.
Go.
Feast on this, Lewis.
- I love the burn.
- The burn is where I live.
Come on, Gabe,
you can't handle his hamstrings.
- You're getting hypno-thigh-zed.
- Speed set. One.
- Here, this is for your elbows.
- Thank you.
Five, six...
Phone call from you.
Keep going.
Eight, nine, ten.
Ten.
We got it?
Very funny.
Yeah, Jim.
Way to mock us
for perfecting our bodies.
Everyone.
Conference room, now.
All right, easy there, grandpa.
I don't need your help.
- You don't need my help?
- Here. Just...
- Feygnasse Team -
.: La Fabrique :.
8x23: Turf War
Morning.
Somebody left
in such a hurry this morning
that she forgot...
These.
The only thing
more delicious than your feet
is the feast that I am going
to prepare for everyone.
If you're gonna hang out
for a while...
What's this?
This dumb rule Robert made.
He just wants visitors to sign in.
Is this an attempt to embarrass me?
No, of course not.
I think it's, like,
if we make an exception for you,
then we have to make
an exception for the water guy.
And then, where does it end?
Why is it when other people
spend time at the office,
they're rewarded for it,
and when I do it,
I am told it's a little much?
Is it because I'm not an employee?
Because that's what it feels like.
- Enjoy the alumni game.
- We have a deal?
Thanks so much, Earl.
Wow, simultaneous sale.
They said it couldn't be done.
Lot going on, guys.
What's happening?
Binghamton branch closed last night
and all their clients are for grabs.
That was a fine branch.
Things are really bad
under Robert California.
It's like a festival of poo.
Come on, language.
And we're not interested
in your sour grapes.
- Tell him where he can stick them.
- In the fridge.
The butt, in his butt.
Sorry, I can't focus on zingers.
There's too many potential clients.
You better watch yourselves.
The Syracuse branch can't be happy
you're taking New York clients.
Why did Binghamton close?
Can everyone just please...
I had a one-man
saturnalia last night.
In celebration of
the finalization of my divorce,
I got into a case of Australian reds.
And... How should I say this...
Columbian whites.
What is this about Binghamton?
The branch closed.
Forever.
Closing the Binghamton branch
never occurred to me before today.
Or, I guess, last night.
But in vino veritas, as they say.
I'm not gonna start
doubting my drunken self now.
I got your voicemail.
From last night.
Wonderful.
And the answer...
is yes, yes, yes, yes, and...
never.
When's the last time
you lived so intensely
that your brain
literally couldn't hold the memories in?
- This summer...
- Apparently,
I left a phone message
for Nellie last night.
I need you to find out what I said.
I am a little busy.
'Course.
Why don't you list the things
that would keep you from helping me.
- I can make you a list.
- Let's do it now.
What's number one?
Why don't I help you now?
There we go.
Who the hell are Jim Halpert
and Dwight Schrute?
Jim, Dwight, your last names?
And you are?
Harry Jannerone,
Dunder Mifflin Syracuse.
What the hell's all this?
Cherries jubilee
over homemade gelato.
You live well down here in PA.
I want to talk to you guys right now.
And Lloyd Gross too.
Which one's that guy?
The salesmen have a commission cap
but we figured out a way around it.
Lloyd Gross is a fictional salesman
we invented to...
How do I put this?
Steal from the company.
Embezzle.
To commit fraud.
It sounds sketchy,
but it helps us get more money.
Pam made a drawing of Lloyd.
He is a blend of all the salesmen.
There he is.
- That's Lloyd.
- Me?
Yeah, you.
Where do you get off
crossing State lines?
Now, we're actually closer
to Binghamton than you are.
Kimosabe.
I like to think Lloyd Gross
is a no-nonsense guy
who doesn't back down from anybody.
And he calls people "kimosabe."
They're New York.
We're New York.
State line is the dividing line.
That's the way it's always been.
There's no rule that says that.
That's true.
There's no rule.
You can check the employee handbook.
Can I check the employee handbook?
Does it say anything
about choking a man with my bare hands?
Wait, no?
Are you kidding me?
You told me there was.
I could've choked
so many people by now.
Stay out of my State.
It's in your best interest.
I've seen guys like you.
Big guys who like
to push the little guys around.
Lloyd Gross eats bullies like you
for breakfast.
Just stay out of New York.
Text from the old wife.
Gonna take that.
Why don't we just ask Robert?
Can we all agree
that the CEO should decide this?
Robert's here?
Look at us.
Bickering like schoolgirls,
looking around the room
for things to hit each other with.
I don't think we were doing that.
Chair, lamp, plant,
table leg, Jim's leg.
Where's the Advil?
I think I've hit my limit
on the Tylenol.
Sorry, not Jim.
What must we do to get rid of you?
Hire you back
and send Erin back to Florida?
Message received loud and clear.
Just have to get
the caramelized sugar
- off the pan before it dries.
- For God...
What a surprise you're here.
Why would you close Binghamton
without a transition plan?
- How do you mean?
- I forgot a pan...
Stay there, do your dishes, go ahead.
There is a time for every decision,
predetermined many years ago.
There's no benefit in questioning
why this particular decision seems...
So poorly timed.
What are you deciding?
We get a say.
Listen, Robert, I don't have time.
There's a big client in play.
- Prestige Direct Mail Solutions.
- Don't listen.
Used to be Binghamton's.
I want it, it's mine.
Prestige is ours. They do
half of the junk mail on the seaboard.
We get them.
We already put a call into them.
We need you to make a decision.
- Make a decision.
- I did.
Neither of you
are to have any contact
with either Prestige or any
other Binghamton client
until I have figured out
how to divide things up.
As Solomon once said...
Some bizarre energy
in this place today.
Robert is going off the rails,
making some funky decisions.
Why is nobody gonna call on Prestige?
It's a huge client.
They could give their business
to the first person at the door.
Could be any idiot.
Any idiot at all.
Shaping a company is in a sense
similar to training a geisha.
You have to mold
not merely the physical form,
but also the character.
The two must harmonize.
Are they still there?
They want a decision
on who gets the big client.
They can wait.
I'll still be talking about geishas
long past their bedtime.
You know, I trained as one.
Is it just me
or is our boss a freakin' weirdo?
I'm gonna get some air.
You know
what would be really dastardly?
If we snuck out of here
and got to the client first.
He's running!
Damn it!
Damn it.
- What is this supposed to be?
- It's a monkey.
Get real.
This is not a monkey.
It's got a hula skirt and a blue nose.
Hold on.
Is this him?
- What?
- Is that him?
- It's him! Do something!
- What am I gonna do?
Go slash his tires!
Go dent his hood.
That's it?
Great.
That's like a five-second delay.
Go!
Does this thing have turbo?
Nitrous?
- Hit the Nos.
- Nos?
Like in Fast And Furious?
Yeah, definitely.
- Hit the Nos.
- Are you sure?
- Brace yourself. 3... 2... 1.
- We got it. Go!
Here we go!
Hello.
Andy Bernard to see the CEO.
- Do you have an appointment?
- No, I do not.
I can squeeze you in.
Seriously?
'Cause I could just be anyone.
I thought I was gonna have
to convince you.
- He's really not that busy.
- Is there someone here to see me?
Yes, this man.
Come on in.
So... What do you make
of this Robert California guy?
What does a guy like that do
on an average weeknight?
I'll tell you what he does.
Hello!
Hello, my clucking hens.
Got room for another in the roost?
Don't worry, I won't lay an egg.
Robert sent me to take over
if Pam fails.
If?
I have been crunching numbers
all day.
Math is for boys.
I need girl talk.
Did someone say girl talk?
Sometimes I wonder
if I have ovaries in my scrotum,
because I am great at girl talk.
Have you guys been watching
any good Korean soap operas?
I'm pretty deep into
Hee-Jungcinderella Girl.
Although, I definitely fast-forward
ugh the young-Tae storylines.
Do you think I'd like that,
or do I have to have an Asian fetish?
I think you're gonna need
to have an Asian fetish.
It'll be upsetting if you don't.
I'm a former paper executive.
I know the product and the margins.
I can save you 25% on your costs.
Why haven't I heard of you?
You got any references?
I'm a rogue.
Which is the best part.
That means you will be
my first customer
and your business
will get 100% of my attention.
I have written down
my personal phone number.
You call this anytime.
Every salesman I've met has given me
his personal phone number.
Of course they have.
Which is why I'm giving you
a key to my house.
Whatever you need.
Anytime, night or day.
You just stop on by.
You want me to drive
to your house if I need paper.
Maybe you want someone to talk to
or a place to crash for a couple of days
My wireless password
is "eat, pray, love."
Easy to remember.
Ready?
Go, go!
You all right?
Dwight, what are you doing?
Go, go!
Take the stairs! Now!
I don't even know where their are.
- I'll stall him. Go!
- God!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna activate
the seismic failsafe.
We'll be stuck between floors
for hours.
- My pants fell down.
- What?
My pants fell down!
I don't have a belt!
Hello, sir.
Dwight K Schrute. Dunder Mifflin, Scranton.
Forgive my pants, they fell down.
An appointment with Mr. Ramish.
Right now is fine.
I was here first. Dwight K Schrute.
Dunder Mifflin, Scranton.
What's going on?
Harry Jannerone.
Dunder Mifflin, Syracuse.
I already made an appointment
with your secretary.
Let me stop you all. I've already picked
a new paper supplier.
It's not DM Utica, is it?
No, no, it's not
Dunder Mifflin at all actually.
- It's... Big Red Paper Company.
- Big Red Paper Company?
- Give me a cup of coffee.
- Me too.
Or do you also
have a monopoly on thirst?
All right.
It didn't work out for any of us.
So... We're still on the same team.
Let me get these.
Let him get his own.
He's got Syracuse money.
You know, your partner's got
a lotta attitude.
But I like that.
How long you guys been dating?
Jim couldn't land me
in a thousand years.
- But you're saying there's a chance.
- Shut up.
I stole Nellie's phone.
Excellent. Excellent.
Though troubling that your
first instinct is thievery.
- What do you want from me?
- Now we get to the bottom of Nellie's
"yes, yes, yes, yes. Never."
Hello, Nell, it's mom.
You'll keep your chin up.
It can't possibly be as bad
as you described.
Oh, yes, it can.
This is MasterCard.
You are over the limit.
Send the minimum payment
of $448 by Monday
or we will be forced
to send it to collections.
Shopaholic.
Sounds like it.
Hi, sis. Is your boss
still hitting on you?
This is Annie from Second Nests.
I'm sorry but the Romanian
orphanage felt more comfortable
with a two-person nuclear family
than a single mother.
- We're gonna hold out for that.
- Stop.
We need to get to the bottom of this.
Come on.
Okay, oops! I deleted them all.
They're all deleted.
Pam, Pam.
You've completely bungled this!
Can I do it, Pam?
Can I pull off a gold Arabian sandal?
Yes. Definitely.
With your hair.
Certainly.
- You dropped your cell phone.
- Oh! Gosh.
Thank you.
I'm so stupid.
No. My goodness.
You have a lot going on.
With Robert and everything.
Oh, God, Pam.
Don't get me started.
- No, I will not.
- You've just got me started.
Robert...
is...
a filthy beast.
I mean, don't you get the feeling,
every time he looks at you,
he's just thinking
of 15 different ways to do you?
I mean, the man talks
of nothing but sex.
But sometimes he talks about flesh...
and bacchanals.
I cannot even tell you what
he left on my phone last night.
No... Don't.
Just put it out of your mind.
Pam, what is your address?
I'm gonna send you a pair
of these gold harem shoes.
- No. You don't...
- Oh, yes.
Come on, a little
gold Arabian slipper.
Things are looking up.
I might be a mother soon.
I have MasterCard
right where I want them.
And...
I have a new friend.
A friend.
At work.
There's a call for you on line one.
Who is it?
He says Salvation.
No last name.
You once put me on a list
of the losers in the office.
Well, this loser just got
your biggest client
to give him all their business.
So hire me back,
that business is yours.
Don't, and I will find another buyer.
You're blackmailing me.
It's just business.
Ah, well.
I will not be blackmailed by
some ineffectual, privileged,
effete, soft-penised debutante.
You wanna start a street fight with me,
bring it on.
You'll be surprised
by how ugly it gets.
You don't even know my real name.
I'm the fucking Lizard King.
Well, I gave him a chance.
- Andy Bernard.
- You got a minute?
I'm in the middle of a piano lesson.
I wanted to see if I could
interest you in an investment.
Dunder Mifflin.
Now... Why would I want that?
It's worth half what it was 3 years ago.
Exactly.
And you know
that with the right management,
it could be worth twice
what you would pay for it today.
Why don't you come in?
So what would you do
if you weren't selling paper?
Oh, man, I'd have to sell beets.
- Probably submit them for competitions.
- What?
It sounds stupid, but nationals has
always kinda been a dream of mine.
How have we never talked
about this before?
Wait.
You don't even care about nationals.
Nothing?
I've always wanted
to own a bike shop, but...
What about you?
I'd like to sell one
big thing, you know?
Like... a plane.
One sale, I'm out.
That sounds lovely.
Anyway, Robert is gonna run this
company to the ground...
So...
We won't be doing this in six months.
www.tvsubtitles.net