-And the page is now live.
-Yes.
Let the donations fa-low.
[Hannah] Today is pyjama day.
Seeing as though people love working from
home so much, I thought,
oh, why don't we bring home
into the office.
Roll out of bed, grab your
favourite thing.
Rock up. Why not?
I brought two of my favourite movies.
[in accent] My wife. She rather nice.
Borat two.
[screams]
But most importantly,
the Pyjama Day foundation is
Oh, such a great cause.
-[notification bleeps]
-Yes.
You are going to make
so much money for the office.
For the office Pyjama day.
Raising money
for the Pyjama Day foundation.
Yeah.
[Lizzie] We are using the donations
to hit our financial targets
so that we can keep the office open.
That was my idea.
-[in Borat accent] High five.
-Yeah. [giggles]
-No, high five.
[in accent] My wife, she rather nice.
-My wife!
-No, don't.
[theme music plays]
[Lizzie] Okay. Let's see.
Boyd signed in. Tina signed in.
Nick has not signed in,
so we shall assume he is absent today.
Nick. Absent. Done.
[laughs] What the hell?
Not the only one
that made an effort today.
What is that?
-It's my pyjamas.
-That is my face.
I think it'd be a bit weird if I slept
in something with your face on it, Lizzie.
-[Lizzie] Not funny.
-[bird caws]
-Has your friend signed in yet?
-He is a visitor.
Yeah, but shouldn't have
one of those visitor stickers?
-What's his name?
-My crows name is Russell.
-[Lizzie] What?
-Nothing.
That's a good name.
-[Nick] Hello, Rusty. How are you, mate?
-Nick, no!
Russell is my roommate, my BFF,
and my an unemotional support animal.
He is extremely well trained.
[Deborah] No I'm looking for the accrued
expenses. Yeah. [coughs]
No, I'll just, sorry,
can you hang on for a minute?
-Will you fuck off with the sandalwood?
-I like sandalwood.
[banging]
Oi! You break it, you pay for it.
[Deborah] Sorry about that.
Hannah wanted us to bring something fun
from home, so I brought my fun kids.
Deb looking toasty in the corner. Snuggy.
Tina. Sure.
We enjoying the work
from home at work vibes?
What,
what did you bring in from home, Greta?
-I brought in my book.
-[Hannah] Book nerd. [laughs]
Yeah, I read too. Love reading.
Bit of a reader.
Yep. Lloyd's peeking out of his Trackies,
which is… [groans]
Now everyone remember to send
out those donation links to your friends,
your families, your pimps.
[Martin] We have a guest speaker coming in
today,
and I have told Hannah
about it multiple times,
and I will double
my donation if she has remembered it.
And no, I'm not wearing pyjamas because
I am an adult.
[Greta] Wow. Baking.
-How do you not have a girlfriend?
-Don't you have work to do?
Like a book to read?
-Okay.
-What's going on?
[camera clicks]
Pics for your new dating profile.
-Greta, no. No.
-Just act natural.
Natural?
What you surprise me with your camera?
-What am I supposed to be like?
-The exact opposite of what you're doing.
-I don't know how to…
-[Greta] Ahh, cute.
Looking forward to those biccies Nico.
Thanks, Lloyd. Yeah, me too.
Man. Should be good.
[coffee machine whirs]
And we won't be using that one.
Nope.
[Nick] Yeah. I'll bring dates home.
It's great.
They walk through the lounge
and see my dad in his undies.
Then they see my mum in the kitchen
who asks
when they're going to make babies with me.
And that's usually when the date ends.
-Can I have my phone back, please?
-Don't you trust me?
No. Like, not at all.
Okay. Profile interests.
I dunno. Food.
Great. Foodie. What else?
That's it.
-You ever been to Paris?
-No.
But you surf, right?
You know I don't.
Okay, well, I'm going to make your profile
look like a guy
someone would actually want to date.
And I'm setting up a 5K radius
to keep it local.
Thank you.
[trumpet sound]
Slumber party meeting in the lounge room.
Last one in's a loser.
Yeah, I just I'm just kidding.
Could everyone just come
into the meeting room, please?
-[Nick] Now?
-Yep.
Okay, just to let you know,
we have raised $280 so far,
but we're getting a lot of piddly $20, $30
donations.
So I emailed all the donors
saying that the amount is offensive
and it is time to step up their game.
Sure.
[Lizzie] I used to be in charge of troop
fundraising when I was in the Scouts,
and I have often found that a public
shaming is the most effective tactic.
[Hannah] Okay everyone, grab a bean bag.
Make yourself at home.
[Greta] Ah, interested now are we?
Any hotties?
So many Aperol Spritzes.
[Hannah] Now to get in the spirit of
pyjama day,
I thought we could kick things off,
a little bit of fun,
with a little game of [singing]
truth, dare, double dare,
-touch or kiss or promise?
-Dare.
Look, you're-- Not your turn Lizzie.
I dare someone to pass me the nuts.
I dare Nick to pat Russell.
I dare Lizzie
to use a toaster in the bath.
I don't eat toast, I eat jaffles.
[Hannah] Okay, okay.
All right, I'll start. Truth.
Ask me anything.
[Greta] Oh, is it true pyjama day is just
a sad attempt to make work more fun.
[lift dings]
Change it. Dare!
Who dares me to kiss Tina?
[laughs awkwardly]
All right, we'll get the fun
started with a pillow fight then.
-Ow!
-Come on. It's good fun.
[grunts and groans]
[Hannah] Martin!
Come on. Not now.
-I'm busy.
-Georgia's here.
Who's Georgia?
Georgia is a workplace consultant
who will be leading a workshop
in workplace behaviour.
With a specific focus on,
boundaries and consent.
Look, I've got a jammy packed day.
Let's put a pin in this.
Reschedule. Circle back.
-Hannah, can I see you in my office?
-[Hannah groans]
-[Hannah] When?
Six months ago. A year ago?
-[Martin] Yesterday. The day before that.
-[Russell caws]
She has nothing to say that I couldn't say
in a way more fun way.
Look. Oh, no.
It's just that I, you know, like, today
is more being, like,
fun and loosey goosey, you know?
So what I'm thinking,
to start your presentation...
You're gonna start in the box. Yeah?
And then you're crouched in like this
and then start the music.
[Hannah sings] Dah dah!
-[Greta] What is she doing?
-[Hannah] …Hot in...
-No idea.
[Hannah singing] Dah dah! So hot in here!
[Nick] oh no, no, no.
-[Hannah] Ow!
-[Greta] What?
[Hannah] And then, I like, when you do it.
Oh, no no no. [giggles]
-We've already matched.
-Oh, exciting.
The Pyjama Day Foundation is about raising
money for foster kids, not
it's not about being fun and hot and
loosey goosey.
Umm, I think it's about all of it.
-I might get started.
-[Martin] Sure.
Cool.
[Martin] All right. Hi, everyone.
This is Georgia.
She's a workplace consultant--
And she's going to get the party started.
She's got a 90 minute set.
Let's see if she can do a tight 30.
Oh, can we get this turned off, please?
Oh, no no, no,
This is the period blood dance bit!
Have you seen this?
-[Martin] No.
-It's hilarious.
Honestly. Look at it.
She's got blood dripping down her legs.
-Do we think this is appropriate?
-For a slumber party?
-Umm, Yeah.
-No, for the children.
[Deborah] Hey, kids, grab some snacks.
Go and play hide and seek.
Yes, a nice one.
-[Martin] I'll just turn it off.
-Yeah, we can just Borat it up later!
Do you reckon she's seen my profile?
-100%.
-She's pretty cute.
[Georgia] The workplace has been going
through some significant changes
in the past few years.
No more printing.
-Still some printing. Yeah,
-Well, there's less printing.
I was talking about behavioural
changes and what is and isn't appropriate
in the workplace.
Drugs.
Unless they're prescription.
Deborah needs her xannies.
Isn't that right, Deb?
See, that's actually an example
of what isn't appropriate.
It's not our place to discuss
people's personal lives.
We'd need to discuss registered offenders.
She's got you there.
Could I get a volunteer, please?
Great. Thank you. Come on up.
-[Georgia] It's Nick, right?
-Yeah.
Great round of applause for Nick.
[polite applause]
Nick, could I get you to hold this
around your waist, please?
-Yeah, sure.
-So just holding that up
around your waist.
So this represents Nick's personal space.
Now, sometimes we have to remind ourselves
not to enter someone's personal space
without their consent first.
So we're going to do
a little role play now.
Hi, Nick. Happy birthday.
-May I give you a birthday hug?
-Yeah, totally.
Okay, so only now can I enter
Nick's personal space to embrace him.
[Greta] Mason and I met pre Hinge,
pre Tinder, pre everything really.
We met in high school actually.
He came back to repeat his final year
and the rest is history.
[phones ring]
[general office murmuring]
Hey Lloyd mate. Yeah um...
You're kind of hanging loose.
Your whole...
We can see the whole barbecue mate. Yeah.
Have you got any other shorts
or pants or anything?
[Lloyd] Hang on, hang on.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Okay. Just easy, easy.
All right. Yeah, just.
-Ow.
-You okay?
Cool, good thanks. Thanks.
Biscotti?
[Russell caws]
Dude, you're going to break people's
teeth?
Yeah but are they good, though?
-They're good.
-Really?
-They're delicious.
-Cool.
-How are you finding the workshop?
-It is interesting.
-Uh Huh.
-Mmm.
-Biscotti?
-Oh I...
Apparently, they're tough
and delicious, just like the baker.
Oh, no. I'm fine.
I'm not really a biscuit person.
Ouch!
Hey, just a little bit of feedback
thus far.
I think you might be
losing the crowd a little bit.
Well, my job isn't really
to entertain the crowd.
Oh, no, obviously, that's my job.
[Georgia] We should probably
get back to it.
Yeah. Probably should.
[Hannah] Some people might feel threatened
by the new girl coming in,
get worried that
their staff will like her more,
and start
to overcompensate and fight for attention.
Not me.
I'm secure
knowing how my staff feel about me.
Don't even have to try.
[Georgia] Physical boundaries are
reasonably straightforward
and we'll just wait.
Oof!
Thank you Hannah.
But what about some other boundaries?
You may come in on a Monday morning,
someone might be telling you about
their weekend,
and it may be something
you don't want to hear.
[Deborah pretend coughs] Lloyd.
[Georgia] So I want you to find a partner,
and then I want you to practice
conversations
where you establish boundaries.
Ask each other a couple of questions,
but if at any point you don't feel
comfortable answering those questions,
just say, I'd rather not answer that.
-Okay, can I hear an okay?
-[all] Okay.
[Georgia] Okay all right, great.
The moment has arrived.
Up on our feet. We'll find those partners.
[Hannah] Gretty! Greta partner!
[indistinct chatter]
Can you ask me if I'm part
of the Mile High club?
Okay. Are you part of the Mile High club?
Am I part of the Mile High club?
I don't know, You'll have
to ask the staff at Lufthansa Air.
-Yeoww!
-[Lizzie laughs] That's very good.
You okay?
I think I'll stapled my thing to my--
I'd rather not answer that question.
[Georgia] Looks like we have an odd
number.
-Are you happy to be my partner?
-Oh, buy me a drink first.
-For the exercise.
-Oh. Of course. Yeah.
[Georgia] Look, why don't we just take a
moment to acknowledge that we obviously
have connected online, but we'll just put
that aside for the workshop.
Yeah. On the...
-Why don't I just ask the questions?
-Okay, yeah.
Paris, you grew up in Paris.
What was that like?
I did grow there.
But I prefer not to answer that question.
-Oh, that's. Yep. That's fine. Umm...
-Yep.
I saw you like surfing.
Where do you like to surf?
Oh, I love to surf. I, er, I the, Bondi.
The Bondi.
-I'd rather not answer that question.
-Okay.
-I like food.
-You like food?
Why don't we leave it there for a second?
So let's go back to our spots.
Okay, everyone. So that was great work.
Why don't we take this as a as a moment
to take a super quick
two minute bathroom break?
[Lloyd] Yeah.
-Guys, guys, guys, guys. Okay, okay.
Huddle in, huddle in.
Deb, Deb, Deb.
-I'll huddle from here.
-Okay.
[Martin] A pyjama day in the wrong hands
is a proper HR nightmare.
["Hot In Herre" by Nelly Playing]
♪ So hot in herre ♪
♪ So hot in ♪
[in time with music] Oh!
Sorry Georgia,
Bit of confusion.
It seems another guest speaker
has arrived.
♪ Give a little bit a ah, ah
And a little bit a ah, ah ♪
-♪ Yeah I was like… ♪
-[music stops]
It was just Tina. Just a little joke.
Yeah. Tina doesn't seem to be laughing.
She laughs internally.
Tina, did you consent
to getting in the box?
I don't mind.
-But did Hannah ask for your consent?
-Of course I asked.
-And did she respond?
-Yes. She got in the box.
Hannah, this is a prime example
of unacceptable behaviour
and I'm going to have to ask you
to step out of the workshop.
Yeah. I don't think anyone here wants me
Actually, it would be my pleasure, because
I've got a hell of a lot of work to do.
Excuse me.
Thanks, guys.
Enjoy your jerk shop.
-[Lizzie] Hannah, I didn't--
-Nah.
[Sebastian] What am I hoping to get out of
my internship at Flinley Craddick?
Umm, I guess a reality check
about what will happen if I don't get my
shit together and pass my exams.
[mouse clicks]
[woman screams on TV]
-Boundaries.
-Popcorn.
-Inclusion.
-[Georgia] Great work.
Cardboard.
Psst.
-[Tina] Sharing.
-[Georgia] Great.
-[Nick] Kindness.
-[Hannah whispers indistinctly]
[Tina] Permission.
-[Hannah whispers]
-[Deborah] Fanta.
[Georgia] Let's try and stick to our
feelings.
-Courage.
-Consent.
-Focus.
-[Russell caws loudly]
-[people gasp]
-[Georgia] Oh my goodness.
-[Nick] Lizzie, go get your bird.
-[loud thud]
-[loud hubbub]
-[Greta] Oh my God!
-[Nick] Greta, Greta, Greta.
No, no, no, no, no.
[Martin] Stay calm everyone.
So should I call the RSPCA
or the pest control?
[Lizzie] Come to me.
Come back in this room.
-[confused shouting]
-[Martin] Don't. Just.
Just don't stand on the chair.
-[Russell caws]
-[Lizzie] Russell! Come here.
Come, come.
Russell, come. Come.
Deborah! No!
[Lizzie] Deborah popped outside for a
smoke,
and Russell saw an opening and he took it.
I'm not concerned, though.
If there is one crow
that knows what it takes to survive
out there in the urban jungle.
It's Russell.
And Nick better watch out.
[Martin] So again, I'm just really sorry,
but, but anyway, thanks so much
for your patience today.
-I really appreciate it.
-Best of luck, Martin.
Hey, sorry about today.
-Umm, I just want to say goodbye.
-It's nice to meet you, Nick.
Maybe I'll catch you
around the Bondi sometime.
-Oh, no, I don't surf.
-No, I figured.
Oh, right.
Permission to give you an awkward hug.
I'm going to exercise the right
to say no on that.
Yeah. Nice.
-So do you know how to use the--
-It's press the button.
Yeah. G,
because we're on one. So, yep.
That's how you that's
how you use the lift.
-[computer game noises]
-Hannah?
Oh, yeah. Martin.
Terrible timing. I've just…
-[keyboard clacks]
-Ping this.
-[Martin Clears throat] Lizzie.
Hannah, today was meant to be about
raising money
for the Pyjama Foundation.
Yeah, raising money for pyjama day.
Yeah, for foster children,
not the Flinley Craddick Foundation.
Well,
if we don't meet our financial targets,
Martin,
we too will be foster children
lost to the system of remote work--
[Martin frustrated]
Donate the money to the foundation now,
and shut down the link.
$3,000! How did we do that?
Okay, I get it. I'll donate half now.
-All of it. Now.
And we will need to discuss
your behaviour today.
[in Borat accent] I like you.
[Hannah] I think we all learned something
today,
both about ourselves and each other.
When people are at home,
they're at their worst.
Surrounded by sick kids,
predatory birds, everyone walking around
with their wangs hanging out.
But the workplace is somewhere we can go.
And for eight hours,
pretend we aren't those awful people.
You wanna walk down with me?
Oh, Mason's picking me up.
I thought you liked catching the bus,
people watching and that.
Yeah, I do like that.
But he's on a job in Parramatta this week
and thinks we should save the bus fare.
What, $4.28?
[chuckles]
-Oh, Lizzy asked me to give you this.
-Oh, wow.
-Are you scared?
-I'm so scared.
I'll see you later.
Hey, I'm sorry about
the whole Georgia thing.
Oh, no. Whatever.
I was never going to work.
You know, she's not a, biscuit person, so.
You are so shallow.
Yeah, if you can add that to my profile
before surfer, I'd appreciate that.
Au revoir!
-[Crow caws]
-[Nick] Fu--
[sighs heavily]
[theme music plays]