Good morning, Flinley Craddick.
Yes, yeah. I'll try her line.
One moment.
-[Lizzie knocks]
-Yeah.
Alisha called again.
Should I say that you're not here?
I told you, I don't want a call
from that woman until 5:00 p.m.
Then I shall tell her to back off.
No, don't tell her to back off.
Just tell her I'm not here.
[Lizzie] Yeah.
Oh my God. When did the agents get here?
-[Lizzie] 20 minutes ago.
-Why didn't you wake me up?
You looked so peaceful.
I wasn't sure if you--
Lizzie, this building is not for lease.
Not yet, okay?
So, I want them gone. Is that clear?
Yes, Captain.
Don't… "Captain" is very strange.
Please don't say that.
[Hannah] Today is the day
the final sales report is due.
If we don't hit our financial target,
the office will close
and we will be forced to work remotely
from the brutal isolation…
-[fire alarm rings]
-…of our own home.
[alarm keeps beeping shrilly]
[Sebastian] Please, this way, I'm sorry.
[automated fire warning]
Emergency. Evacuate now.
[theme music playing]
Okay, let's talk numbers.
They're shithouse.
Well, that's not the attitude
I need right now, Deb.
-Just being honest.
-Well, be less honest.
But also, give it to me straight,
but in a positive and encouraging way.
Okay.
You're on the right track.
Love it.
But you're still 220 grand short.
You're the productivity manager.
What have you got for me?
Funny you should ask
because I have started
an Act4Change petition
to keep the office open,
and it's already got one signature.
Yeah. It's yours.
I don't think the lazy activist route
is going to save us, Lizzie.
It saved Karol Wilcox's dog in 2014
from getting executed for killing a duck.
636,000 signatures.
[phone ringing]
Good morning, Flinley Craddick…
Yeah. Yeah. One moment.
[whispering] Um, Hannah?
Hannah, it's Alisha.
Are you here yet, or…?
Okay, got it.
I'm sorry. She sliced her neck open.
Can I take a message?
-Hey.
-Hey, Martin.
Um, have you heard from Nick?
[Martin] Yeah.
Like… like, heard his actual voice?
Yeah, we chatted on the phone.
And did he sound sick?
Nah, not really.
Could be a sprained ankle, I guess.
[Martin] He said it was laryngitis.
Oh, cool.
[Greta] No, Nick didn't ask me out.
Not like out-out.
No, he just suggested grabbing dinner
and then Mason called and I had to go.
It's no big deal.
He's just been sick
every day
since then.
[bell ringing]
Okay, people!
Today is D-day,
and "D" stands for, "Let's do it!"
And that is why on this day,
I'm putting you all on sales.
Every one of you.
We've got until 5:00 p.m. to make 220K,
so let's go!
Whoo!
[Deborah] 220K by 5:00 p.m.?
Is a joke.
[Hannah groans]
We need to mobilise, people.
Okay? We gotta hit the phones.
We gotta share our clients.
We gotta, I don't know, sell your body.
Find a sugar daddy.
Where is Nick?
He's sick.
[Hannah] Today?
Okay, well, let's think global, all right?
Um, ah, what's… what's the time?
-What countries are still trading?
-It's 10:32.
It's 10:32. Yeah, it is. Yeah, it is.
So, America is closed. London is closed.
Japan's open. The Solomon Islands.
-[Hannah] Yes! Yes!
-South Korea.
-North Korea. Russia.
-North Korea's probably out.
-But Russia! Holy moly.
-[Lizzie] They're open.
-[Lizzie] Yeah.
-Whatever it takes, let's get a-sellin'!
[jingles bell loudly]
[Hannah] Whoo!
[Lizzie] Do I want to go remote?
Not relevant.
Do I want to support the vision
of my branch manager?
At all costs.
[Greta] What are you doing?
I am in sales now,
and seeing as a certain sales rep
didn't show up,
I shall be taking his spot.
If I had to finish my work placement
from home, I think I'd be okay.
Lizzie, pull up Nick's client list.
With pleasure.
-Okay.
-[computer beeps]
Ooh. It's password-protected.
Uh, try Nickiscool69.
Nickiscool…
-[PC beeps]
-Nope.
Ooh, how about "Nickisnotcool68"?
-[PC beeps]
-Greta, what's Nick's password?
Can't say.
Yeah, you know what? You're right.
No one likes a snitch.
Lloyd? What's Nick's password?
Um, "Lizzie is my bestie,"
and all the i's are exclamation marks.
Lizzie is my bestie…
-[PC chimes]
-Oh, right. Print that out for me.
Will do.
-For the record, Nick is not my bestie.
-[phone line rings]
Hi, David, this is Hannah Howard
from Flinley Craddick Packaging.
How are you going?
Nick Fletcher, yes,
but he's away at the moment,
so I just thought
I'd give you a little nudge.
[elevator dings]
[Hannah] Yeah. Okay.
No, that is no worries at all.
Um, you sure I couldn't convince you?
No. All right.
-Well, if you do…
-[door opens]
…change your mind, just give me a call.
But the offer is only available
till 4:59 p.m. today.
Okay, bye.
Yeah.
G'day, Hannah. You right if we borrow
some of your fridge space?
We just have a barbie downstairs
and ours is chockers.
[Hannah] A barbecue?
It's actually quite a busy day for us.
Oh, no, it's just a warehouse thing.
For Jonny's birthday.
It's just my birthday, so.
Oh, actually…
[mutters indistinctly]
Uh, hey, everyone!
It's Jonny's birthday.
Having a barbecue in the warehouse.
So, whoever makes the most sales
gets all you can eat sausages!
-All you can eat?
-[Hannah] Yeah.
So, yeah, chuck 'em in the fridge.
We'll catch you.
[Lloyd] Who uses packaging? Question.
Uh, I'd like to speak
to your manager, please.
Yeah, certainly. It is about a big sale.
Yeah, yeah. Happy to hold.
[bright on hold music playing]
Got a big fish on the line.
Just got to reel 'em in.
More of a shark, actually.
What would you say if I told you
that that shark was Tetra Pak?
I'd say Tetra Pak is a packaging company.
Why bother with them?
Well, who does their packaging? Huh?
Mm, okay. Good luck with that.
[Lizzie] Yeah.
[elevator dings]
That's my desk.
You snooze, you lose.
[Hannah] Yeah, I know that Nick
usually looks after you, but he's sick.
I'll call you back.
Nickelodeon!
Um, ah…
Better late than never.
Um, I had a client call me
saying that you'd been
hassling them on the phone.
Hassling? More like hustling.
Yeah, we're under a lot
of pressure today, so, yeah,
I've been picking up the slack.
Right. So you just open up my computer
and just help yourself
to my personal contact list.
Personal and professional.
Now, Sean Atwood at Bigger is Better.
Who is that?
Yeah. Sean renewed his order last month.
Okay. Nellie at Georgio.
Is that as in Armani?
No, as in my hairdresser.
-Okay. Is she a client?
-No, as in, my actual hairdresser.
-Can I have my contact list back?
-Gregor Best.
-He's a major player, right?
-Yes.
Yes, and his order's up
for renewal this week.
-Okay, let's give him a call.
-No, don't call him.
He told me he didn't want
to be disturbed today
because he's dealing with
personal matters.
-So, I'll just call him tomorrow.
-Tomorrow's too late.
Yeah? I think he'd appreciate a call
from the top diggity dog.
-No, Hannah, you don't understand.
-Hang on, shh! Voicemail.
Hi, this is Hannah Howard
from Flinley Craddick Packaging.
I'm the MD here, just calling you
to check up on a little order
that Nick mentioned to me…
Um, if anyone needs me, I'll be in there
writing my resignation letter, so.
[mumbled disbelief]
No one cares, Nick.
[Nick exhales]
[Tina] Is he joking?
[Lloyd] Yeah, it's a box.
It's a good box.
Yeah, a cardboard box.
So, do you want to buy it?
Oh, okay.
Okay. Bye.
[sighs]
Hey, Debs.
How do you sell boxes?
Is there like a script or something?
Are you serious?
I just really love sausages.
Favourite sausage?
Pork and fennel.
[sighs]
[Deborah] Yeah,
I'll survive working remotely.
Actually be quite nice to look up
and not have Lloyd staring at me.
[keyboard clacking]
[keeps typing]
[stops typing]
[approaching footsteps]
-[Greta] Hey.
-Oh, hey.
-Tea?
-Oh, yes, please.
Yep.
Um, I messaged you a few times.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry, I was a bit slack
on the old replies, you know,
just, um, a bit of a fuzzy brain, so.
Laryngitis, right?
[clears throat] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just knocked me around
for a couple of days.
Um… how are you? You good?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
Um… are you serious about quitting?
Yeah.
[Greta] Oh, okay.
[stammering]
Is that because…?
[Lloyd laughs]
Oh, here they are! Dynamic duo.
Sales sharks.
Hey, I was wondering, could I please
run my sales script past you?
Do you know what?
Greta's more of the shark than I am,
so I'm gonna leave you
in her capable hands.
Or jaw, depending on how… 'Cause…
-[Nick] Depending on…
-[laughs] Jaw.
Okay, so, ah, I've written this poem.
Um…
Oh, do we have like a Boombox
or a UE Boom?
-'Cause I could rap it.
-I think just do it acapella.
Oh, okay. Um, so…
"Knock, knock, Knox
What's in the box?"
"A cat called Socks
Also wearing my jocks"
"What a cute kitty"
What do you think?
Yeah, that's really deadly, brother.
Yes!
[clears throat]
[Hannah] Gregor!
Hannah Howard here. Again. Just…
-[phone ringing]
Oh, not now, Alisha. Come on.
[Alisha] Hello? Hannah?
Um… ah, yeah.
Just… I didn't say,
but we are going to throw in
some free bubble wrap.
[laughs]
So, yeah, give me a call.
[mutters] Oh, God.
[sighs softly]
[Lizzie] Psst!
[softly] I have landed the eagle.
What are you talking about?
I have a very sizeable offer on the table.
-Who's the client?
-Their username is XPRZylon#2833.
And let's just say, Zylon is willing
to go to 150K in Bitcoin
for 500 "bespoke" boxes.
150K?
Yes.
[Lizzie] If someone wants a supply of 500
adult-sized boxes
with built-in ventilation,
who am I to question it?
Deb, can we put Bitcoin
through the accounts?
No. Flinley Craddick
does not deal in crypto.
[Hannah] But…
[Hannah] Okay.
-Ask him if he can do Aussie dollars.
-[knock at door]
-Hey, Hannah, just going for a…
-Not now, Martin. We're busy.
[Lizzie] Shut the door.
Come on, Zylon. Come on.
-What are you doing?
-Our job, Martin.
I'm sorry, is this the dark web?
No, it's not the dark web. Is it, Lizzie?
I can confirm it is the dark web
and… boom!
150K Aussie dollars.
-Oh my God. Close the deal.
-[Lizzie] Yeah.
Do not. No,
we're not gonna close the deal.
Zylon's offering $150,000.
Okay, well, Zylon is possibly a criminal
and probably a human trafficker.
Well, I appreciate your opinion,
but I'm gonna give Zylon
the benefit of the doubt.
-Close the deal.
-Yeah.
Martin!
Okay, Hannah,
I think you just need to calm down.
I think you need to calm down,
that's what I think.
-Okay, well, I'm pretty calm.
-Well, I'm also pretty calm.
-I'm a meditation app.
-[Martin] Okay.
I'm… I'm wind in a wheat field.
I'm raindrops on a tin roof,
that's what I am.
-I'm not sure what's going on.
-[phone ringing]
-[Lizzie] It's Gregor Best.
-[Hannah laughs]
Well, well, well.
Looks like someone's luck
is about to turn around.
Hello, Gregor.
[Gregor] I do not appreciate
being harassed
after making it perfectly clear
I'm not available to be contacted today.
-[line disconnects]
-I'm a big fan of yours too!
[Hannah] You want to make
a big purchase? Great.
-[engaged tone on phone line]
-A business lunch? Yes, please.
Okay. See you there.
Exciting.
Well, everyone,
I'm off to land a pretty big deal.
Power lunch. Major player.
Wish me luck. Not that I'll need it.
Power lunch.
-[sighs heavily]
-[Hannah] Major player.
[Hannah's footsteps receding]
Gotta hand it to Hannah. I mean,
she… she never gives up.
Ever.
Does anyone feel like a game of ping pong?
[crossing beeps]
[Hannah] Um, yeah.
So, I would like to remortgage
my house today, please.
Okay, let's have a look.
Thank you.
You want a cash lump sum of $220,000.
Mm-hmm! And I'd like that today, please.
I see.
[Lloyd] "Knock, knock, Knox
What's in the box?"
"A cat wearing socks
Also wearing my jocks…"
Foul. Out.
Hey, Greta? Can I just…?
[indistinct office chatter]
-[Nick grunts] Hey. Um…
-[Greta] Hey.
I just wanted to address
the elephant in the room.
[Greta laughs]
-Did you find it purely for that joke?
-Yeah. Searched everywhere.
It's amazing what you can find
in the storeroom.
Look, about the other day,
it was never my intention to go anywhere.
Yeah, no, I get it.
I, hey, I'm… I'm sorry.
-I… forget it. I shouldn't have…
-Oh, no!
-You don't have to…
-Yeah, it's cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Were you planning on avoiding me
for the rest of your life?
That was the plan, yeah, but I failed, so.
-Miserably.
-Mm-hmm.
-Nah.
-Look, let's just go back to, you know…
just being what we've always been.
-What do you mean?
-You know, just friends.
Like, like… But fun friends!
-Butt fun friends?
-But…
-Fun friends only.
-Fun friends.
It'd be my honour to be
your butt fun friend.
[laughs]
-Okay, I'm gonna leave.
-[Nick] Okay.
-Just make sure you take the elephant.
-Oh, no, please.
You have that, Nick Fletcher.
-Greta King, um…
-It's all yours.
[Nick] Okay.
[moans]
[impassioned cheering and jeering]
[overlapping shouting]
[cheering]
[Hannah] What's going on?
[Lizzie] Oh, I mean,
you left and… and chaos ensued,
and I've been trying to shut it down,
but they wouldn't listen to me.
[paper scrunching]
[paper thuds]
All right, I'm going to the barbecue
to eat some meat.
[footsteps leaving]
I hope you're all happy with yourselves.
I, for one, am not.
[Greta] Oh, shit.
[Deborah] What is it?
Hannah just tried to remortgage her house.
[Lloyd] Well, that is wonderful news.
Have a lovely day.
Great doing business with you.
Guess who just made a sale?
Lloyd did.
[dead silence]
What did I miss?
Who remortgages their house
just so they can come into work?
I guess Hannah.
[barbecue sizzles]
-What's up with Hannah?
-Dunno.
Hey, Hannah?
Can I help you with anything?
Can you grab me the barbecue sauce?
Chuck us the barbecue.
Thanks, mate.
Thanks, ma'am.
Good on ya. Yeah.
[many footsteps approaching]
[Deborah] Emotional eater.
[Lizzie] Let me do the talking, okay?
[Tina] Should we get her a napkin?
15 signatures.
Everybody signed it.
Elizabeth Moyle.
Lloyd Kneath.
Tina Kwong.
And even Nick Fletcher.
Yeah.
Thought I might stick around for a while.
Wow, guys.
Wow.
Thank you very much. It means a lot.
And it proves what I've known all along.
That you love the office
and you want to stay here.
Oh, nah, I think it was more that,
um, we wanted to…
-We felt sorry for you.
-We're still happy to go remote.
But it says "save our office".
It's got all your signatures.
They're all there.
And as your trusted leader, I will not
let these cries fall on deaf ears.
-We will march to the Capitol.
-Whoo! Yes!
By the Capitol you mean Head Office,
that's in the city
and about a five-hour walk.
Okay, Martin, well,
we'll march to the train station
and then we'll march to the Capitol.
Sorry, Hannah, I actually made a sale,
so could I get my sausages now?
I… yeah.
Okay, everyone, grab a sausage
and then we'll get going.
Ah, excuse me. Sorry, mate.
Sorry, I'll just take that.
By rights, I should be first.
Um, hi.
-Ah, yep. Everyone, help yourselves.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Hey, happy birthday, mate.
-Yeah, cheers, Lloyd.
Thanks, man.
[Lloyd] Oh, look,
there's lots I'll miss if we go remote.
The chinwags. Communal cheese.
Toaster. Top toaster, four slice.
We vote no remote.
We vote no remote!
-Everybody now! We vote no remote.
-[Lizzie] Everybody, yeah!
We vote no remote!
-[Hannah] Hey! Oh my God.
-[Lizzie] We vote no remote.
-I mean, obsessed much?
-[Lizzie] Yeah.
[Hannah] Let's see
what she has to say for herself.
Hannah, I've been trying
to reach you all day.
Well, we were just coming to see you.
Well, I'm here now, so can we chat?
Sure.
-I meant in the office.
[Alisha] Hannah,
we had a board meeting yesterday.
Well, that's interesting because that's
what our meetings have become, Alisha.
Bored meetings.
You come in, you tell me
how to do my job, and I'm bored.
We had a board meeting yesterday,
and after reviewing the sales
and productivity of the last quarter,
it's become clear that
since we've gone remote,
there's been considerable downturn.
[laughs]
So, the offices will be reopening
and attendance will be mandatory
four days a week
with flexible start and finish hours.
So, what you're telling me is that
I was right?
Something like that, yes.
[indistinct chatter]
[elevator dings]
[slow clapping continues]
Well, I did it.
I convinced Alisha
to keep the office open.
Mandatory attendance four days a week
with flexible start and finish times.
-Wait, really?
-[Hannah] Yeah.
-So, we get a day at home?
-Yes.
-You convinced Alisha?
-Yeah, I did, Martin.
-Did the petition help?
-Didn't even need it, actually.
So, I shall see you all on the morrow.
Oh, I might work from home tomorrow.
Okay, I shall see the rest of you then.
-I'm gonna take my remote day too.
-Yeah, me too.
Yeah, same.
I might be sick tomorrow.
Okay, well, the day after. Whatever.
[grunts]
Yay!
-So, are you gonna come in tomorrow?
-Yeah. I think I will. You?
Yeah, I'll think about it.
[Hannah] Am I surprised by
today's victory? Not really.
I set a goal,
and I worked my butt off to achieve it.
Sometimes people ask me,
"Oh, how can I become a great boss?"
How can I do what you do?
And the simple answer is,
you can't.
It's just a quality you're born with.
You either got it or you don't.
We're just a little more charismatic,
a little sharper, and a little bit…
better.
-Well, Hannah.
-Martin.
It's certainly been
a challenging few weeks, and…
I single-handedly turned it around? Yeah.
That's why I get paid the big bucks,
I guess.
Yeah.
And I heard all the other branches
are reopening too.
Huh. Really?
I heard it was actually a directive
from Head Office.
Well, don't think we need to get
caught up in the nitty-gritty, Martin.
-Nah.
But that is what happened, so,
you didn't actually save the--
Okay. Thank you, Martin.
-I look forward to seeing you tomorrow.
-No one's coming in tomorrow Hannah.
[Hannah] We'll see.
[elevator dings]
[theme music playing]