Hey Jim. Stanley's back from
the hospital today.
- Can you sign his card?
- Oh, great.
"Glad they didn't mix up
your tonsillectomy
with a moustachectomy."
Oh, that's not good.
Oh, because your jokes
are all hilarious.
It's nice.
It's funny.
It mentions his tonsillectomy
and makes a funny little joke
about his moustache.
Stanley doesn't have
a moustache.
Yeah, he does.
Pam, hit the brakes.
Stanley does not have
a moustache.
I misspoke
I'm-- not sure...
I think he has one,
now that--
I think he has a moustache.
Okay. Phyllis sits
across from him every day.
Phyllis, does he have
a moustache or not?
Ooh, I don't know.
Now I think he doesn't.
Phyllis, what are you talking--
The whole card depends on this!
Okay. The man's worked here
for 25 years.
How can none of us
picture his face?
'Cause we come here
to do our jobs.
We don't stick our noses
in other people's business.
Okay. Which one of these
looks more right?
Neither of those
looks like any person
that has ever existed
or been dreamt of
in the history
of human insanity.
That said, the one on the left.
Guys, that's the elevator.
- What if it's him?
- Okay, quick.
Who says moustache?
Yep.
Who says no moustache?
Ah! Ha ha ha!
- Oh, man!
- Hey!
- He does have one.
- Yes!
Welcome back, Stanley.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
"Good morning, Robert,"
says no one,
because our receptionist
is in Florida.
Pam!
Oh!
Is this a video conference
you're having with...
"Drake, featuring Swizz Beatz"?
Um, no, I was just, um,
just having a cup of coffee,
kind of warming up for the day.
People, you should
come to work already warm.
9:00 to 10:00 AM
is the most productive
potential that a human being--
Sorry, sorry, everyone,
I'm late!
But you are all here,
so no harm done at all
by my lateness.
Nellie, really, 9:50?
Oh, here's what happened.
7:46,
my alarm clock goes off.
I hear it.
Whack the snooze.
- Ah.
- Nine minutes.
Bzzz!
Off it goes again.
Whack!
Seven more times I did that.
Bzzz-- Whack.
Bzzz-- Whack!
By the time I got up,
it was ten minutes to go.
No willpower.
That is my curse!
I've never believed willpower
was very important in a woman.
Ah ha!
I don't think
you would have shown up to work
nearly an hour late
for no reason.
Oh, I assure you,
I would have done.
I did,
and I will keep doing it.
No, no, no, no.
There's something going on.
Some stress in your life.
Well, yes, uh...
There is the whole
moving to Scranton nonsense.
30 boxes arrived yesterday
from england,
and two trunks from Florida.
Then I have to move
into my apartment
in this dreadful,
God knows where it is
backwater suburb of a suburb,
and I mean, no offense,
but are there a lot of
Irish people living around here?
- Yes.
Ugh! I hate that!
No offense.
- None taken.
- Actually, Nellie,
this monologue you're delivering
is very offensive.
Oh! Ay, caramba!
The natives
are getting restless!
- Who's a native?
- Uh, excuse me.
The tone here
is getting quite hostile.
I would appreciate it
if you would keep that stuff
on the basketball court.
- Oh...
- Okay. Okay.
If you'd let me finish--
or the squash court,
or the supreme court.
- Hmm?
- Nellie.
Yes, Robert!
You're clearly
under a lot of... Stress
with the moving
and the work situation
- you've found yourself in.
- Yes.
Let's help her out, shall we?
Go above and beyond today
to show her some of that warm
Scranton hospitality.
Jim, Dwight.
Take the day.
Help Nellie
move those boxes
into her new place.
Why Jim?
The rest of you,
let's throw a party
at the end of the day
to welcome the newest member
of our little community.
I'm sorry.
We're throwing a party
for someone
because they're being horrible?
I'm sorry.
We're taking work time
to move someone's
personal belongings
into their new apartment.
I'm still not sure why
this woman is even here.
Why is she here?
♪ two crazy kids
on the journey of life ♪
♪ going to Pennsylvania ♪
On the road
with my new girlfriend.
But first, a small pit stop
to break up with
my current girlfriend
who is at her parents' cabin
in Southern Pennsylvania.
Oh. That must be nice.
Mm-hmm.
It's a beautiful place.
Great place
to let her down easy.
Oh, no, no, I mean that
must be nice to have parents.
Oh.
Hmm.
♪ time to have a little kiss ♪
- No.
- Mm. Sorry.
Right. No kisses
till the breakup is official.
- Yes.
- I believe in that.
- Yes. So do I.
- I think that's important.
That is important.
Bummer... But important.
- Important.
- Mm-hmm.
I can't believe he's making us
throw a party for her.
- I know, right?
- She's always late.
She's always rude.
It kinda makes me want
to throw a really bad party.
- Yeah.
- On purpose.
Phyllis!
We should do it
right here in the break room.
Order carrot cake.
And Jessica, just so you know,
this is way more
about my love for Erin
than anything wrong with you.
Well, Andy, I'm upset, but...
You did this
in the best way possible,
and I knew you as a lover...
And I'll remember you
as a gentleman.
Okay. That was one minute
and ten seconds.
Consider it nailed.
I think we should try it again.
This time,
worst-case scenario.
Okay, here we go.
Jessica,
I'm really sorry.
I just need you to know--
- What?
What is it?
I didn't sleep well last night.
Ugh!
- Ow.
- Nellie, that reminds me.
Do you want this chair
in the bedroom?
'Cause to be honest,
I don't think
it's gonna
fit through the door.
Don't listen to Jim.
Have you ever seen him
play Tetris?
"Oh, I think I'll just use
this line horizontally.
Oh, I had no idea what a gift
this line is."
- The one time--
- I will get the chair in.
Watch the great Schrutini
work his magic.
Oh, no.
Really? Magic?
No, no, no.
Let's not go there.
No, nothing is more repellant
than magicians.
Bunch of grown men
waving wands,
pulling bunnies
out of body crevices.
Magicians are repulsive.
Next topic.
Excuse me, one second.
- Hi.
- Hey, what's up?
Ah, nothing, just hauling
some cube with Dwight.
Haulin' cube!
That's moving boxes.
We just came up with the term
to make it sound cooler.
So we're planning
this party for Nellie,
and we're gonna make it
really bad.
Sounds like every other party.
No. We're gonna make it
like a prank.
Like order bad food, give her
this passive-aggressive card.
Oh! Hire a magician.
- What?
- Trust me.
Okay.
Oh.
Wow. There's a lot
of cars here.
This is just weird.
Andy!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Hey, Lauren.
Look at you.
Well, I know.
Look at me.
I was just on my way back
from this business trip,
thought I'd stop
and say hi to Jessica.
Aww!
Why is Erin with me?
That's a great question.
She is my coworker,
and she needed a ride
because she totaled her car.
Oh.
God.
So I'm Erin.
Hi.
- Yep. This is Erin.
- Nice to meet you.
Well, Jess went out for a run,
but she'll be back soon.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, ladies.
Andy's here.
Okay, Andy,
that is a bachelorette party,
this is Jessica's friends,
an they've been drinking
during the daytime.
Should we go?
You know, we had such a quick
window to make this work,
I think we should
probably just--
Oh, Jess!
Look who stopped by
after his business trip.
Andy!
Hey!
I wonder if king-sized
sheets
are called presidential-sized
in england.
I really should have
a tweeter account.
Yes, you should.
Ooh!
"Nellie, don't open, stupid.
Love, Nellie."
- I have to see these shoes.
- I doubt that they're sh--
Whoa.
Who's this guy?
Here's the two of them
taking a hike.
I'm guessing
he's some kind of friend.
Boyfriend.
Here's the two of them
kissing at a beach
and kissing
at the Eiffel Tower.
I'm guessing he's some kind
of close romantic friend.
Like a boyfriend?
- You read my mind.
- Yeah.
Whoa. Here's one with
his face whited out.
Hmm. Maybe someone
threw a pie in his face.
New theory-- He's a hated
Italian politician.
Better theory--
This is her ex-boyfriend,
and they went through
some kind of painful breakup.
- Oh, Nellie.
- Oh.
I'm so sorry.
We were just...
I see you've discovered
Benjamin.
That's what I call my box
full of photos of Henry.
- Why not call...
- Shh!
God. We owned a flat together.
Then one morning,
just like that, he was gone.
He ran off with the waitress
at our favorite restaurant.
That's awful.
What kind of restaurant?
Dwight.
I couldn't afford
the flat myself.
So I sold it at a loss.
Ah, but what's ten years
of bliss down the drain
compared with the thrill
of starting over
with nothing and no one?
I'm so sorry.
These must be
very painful memories.
If it would help you to forget,
I could hit you in the brain
stem with this candle stick.
Thank you.
No.
Jim, Dwight, please...
Don't tell anyone about this.
No, no.
Of course.
Just one quick question.
Was this, um, Halloween or...
No.
That's the most embarrassing
thing of all of this.
What kind of fool
gets her heart broken
by a bloody stage magician?
Hey, you know what, Pam?
I was thinking maybe
we should change course here.
Let's give up
on all this mean stuff.
What? No!
No, I just had
this brilliant idea--
Everyone loved it.
You don't have a copyright
on pranks.
I might be better
at this than you.
- No, that's not what I--
- Jim, could you give us a hand?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Call it off, Pam.
Call it off, okay?
It's way more complicated
than you think.
Cancel the magician.
Trust me.
Oh. O-okay.
Okay, I will.
- Pam, we have a great idea.
- Listen to this.
We're gonna have the
fluorescent lights flickering.
It's gonna make everyone sick.
- Or what if...
- Okay.
We discuss...
The idea of doing the party
totally normal?
Like... Not mean.
Just a regular party.
Not mean.
I knew she'd crack!
I wanted to leave you out,
you know.
We're in far too deep.
We can't change course
at this point.
What are you talking about?
Of course we can.
What I mean to say is
we don't want to.
Toots, we're not stopping
this train,
so get off the tracks.
Suck it!
- Andy--
- It'll be fine.
Just act natural.
Do you want a gummy penis?
No, I'll just have
some gummy bears.
- These are delicious.
- But... they're penises.
And we come to Matthew,
the guy who was with
his old girlfriend
basically the whole time
we were together.
- Oh!
- Eew!
Eew! Aw!
That seems gross...
At first blush, right?
But relationships are always
more complicated than you think.
I mean, we don't know Matthew's
history with this other woman.
Maybe she saved his life.
I don't know.
I just-- I don't think
we should rush to judgment
about Matthew.
Maybe we don't pop that one.
- No, pop Matthew.
- Pop it!
Pop it!
- Hey.
Sorry.
It's kind of a madhouse.
- Aah!
- Oh!
Ha ha ha! Megan!
You are one of the good ones,
nard dog.
- Aw...
- No, really.
Where's my Andy?
- I dunno.
- Oh, he's out there.
Are you gonna sing for us?
Well, you guys are doing
a pretty good job
with the scary yelling, so...
That's not like you.
Come on, sing!
Sing!
♪ beyond Bonnie Banks ♪
♪ and beyond Bonnie Brae's ♪
Okay, they're almost here.
What?
Come on!
If you guys are gonna be mean,
can you at least be subtle?
Oh, in the warehouse
we use code names
for people
we want to talk about.
Andy was Jelly Roll.
Mike was Dennis The Menace.
Ryan was douche bag.
Hey, that's not a code name.
That's just an insult.
Plus, everyone would know
who you meant.
- Yeah.
- No. That's a great idea.
Yes, let's have a code name.
How 'bout mondays?
I hate mondays?
Mondays are the worst?
Nobody's named Monday.
Hey, how 'bout we go with Pam?
Simple, easy to remember.
'Cause there's someone
already here named Pam.
Hey!
Welcome to your party.
Everybody get comfy now.
This first song's
over a half hour long.
Best gig ever.
They asked me
to play only originals.
I said, "Have you heard
my originals?
They're terrible."
They said, "Even better."
I said, "I get it.
It's an ironic party
for Nellie."
Maybe we should just go.
No. I gotta do this.
Hey, Jessica,
can I talk to you?
Uh, yeah, sure.
What's up?
Maybe we could talk in private.
Uh... yeah.
What is it?
Well, first let me just say
that I hope when I'm done
with the sort of ugly bits
that we can stay friends.
You're breaking up with me?
Uh... No.
No.
You always do this.
You twist my words around.
Part of me thinks we should
just end this right now.
Oh, my God.
Are you leaving me for Erin?
You said she wasn't
relationship material,
and she wasn't as good as me,
but it's her, isn't it?
Whoa!
That-- No.
Okay.
You want honesty?
Super-honesty time.
I'm gay.
What?
I am gay, and I prefer men.
- I knew it!
- You did not, Kenny!
You invited me to go
shopping with you.
I like hanging out with you.
You're a cool guy.
Which proves my point.
That I'm gay.
Andy, you're not gay.
I mean, we were... together.
And you seemed
pretty excitable.
Well, I was faking it.
I had to fake it every time.
I had to imagine
that I was in a steam room
with John Stamos.
I can't say
it doesn't make sense...
- Well...
- Look, it's--
I mean, I was good
at hiding it, but--
It's fine, Andy.
I didn't think we were
gonna get married or anything.
I just...
I'm just upset for now.
Understandable.
And I'm really sorry.
I really am.
So... we should probably...
go.
This humble but sincere effort
is all for our
valued new colleague.
Excellent.
To Nellie Bertram.
You are a most welcome
and friendly presence
at our company.
- Cheers.
- Why, thank you.
Pam, on the other hand,
is a most unwelcome,
entitled, unfriendly presence
in our company.
Cheers.
Nellie is terrific,
but to be honest,
every day I imagine
how happy I'd be
if Pam died.
Oh. Well.
I feel that as someone
who knows Pam
only a little bit...
Enough.
A good amount.
Not the most, though.
I would say
that she is misunderstood
and that maybe there's
some stuff in her past
that you guys don't know about
that's a little messed up,
and probably makes her
such a torture to work with.
We hate Pam.
We hate Pam!
- We hate pa--
- So we've established...
- No. No.
- That you guys hate Pam.
Do you ever wish she would
just... Disappear?
Oh!
That was a really rough scene.
- Right? Rough scene.
- Yeah.
Oh... At least
we can kiss now.
Oh, yeah.
You know, that stuff
that I said about you to her...
I did-- That's just--
I had to say it.
You know, I was dating her
at the time.
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
- Ah... I feel really tired.
- Yeah.
Probably from seeing
that turkey.
- Oh, yeah.
- When we drove by the farm.
Ohh.
Always does it.
Are you Nellie?
Oh, I think you're my volunteer.
Come on over here, huh?
Oh, I'll do it.
I will volunteer.
- No, Nell-- She--
- I'll do it.
Oh! Big guy, huh?
How's the air up there?
Watch out for... birds.
All right, let's, uh--
Let's do some card magic.
Now, what I want you
to do is...
I want you to pick a card
just by looking at it.
Do not say what it is.
It's the 4 of hearts.
Oh, no, you--
Looks like we got a guy
from another country here, huh?
No hablo el cardo, señor?
Hmm? Ha.
All right, the card is picked.
Now, sir, will you please
shuffle the deck?
You didn't just do that
on... Purpose, did ya?
Why is Jim treating
the magician poorly?
Little known fact
about me--
Before I was a magician,
I used to work...
- at a rope factory.
- Not true.
'Cause that's not a real place.
But I never could seem
to figure out those knots.
That's not a real knot.
When you pull on it,
it disappears.
What the hell?
All right, where's Phyllis?
Who's Phyllis?
Look!
This is really uncool, okay?
I put on
a clean show here--
- Okay, scram, wizard.
- What?
- You heard me!
- Ho oh!
Well, Nellie, I'm sorry.
If I'd known Jim and Pam
would use this party
as an excuse
to abuse a magician--
Well, I thought
it was quite fun.
In fact, I think
they're brilliant employees
in their own way.
Don't you see what I see?
Interesting.
Yes.
No, yes, I see that.
Great work, team.
Great party.
You think this is
a great party?
This cake has vegetables in it.
Like a salad bar, Robert.
How do I get this taste
out of my mouth?
What?
Why are we--
- I just gotta do one thing.
Oh. Hello.
Hey, everybody,
look who's here.
What are you doing here?
Hi.
Super-duper honesty time.
I'm not gay.
In fact, I'm so not gay
that I'm in love with a girl.
Her name is Erin Hannon,
and she's right there.
She's sweet, funny,
and beautiful,
and total relationship
material.
Why the hell
did you come back here?
- Go away.
- Get lost.
- Get out!
- Okay.
- You're done!
- Bye, guys.
Get out.
You ruined my party!
Who does that?
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, run away, Andy.
- Run away!
- You're disgusting!
I can't believe you're not gay!
- Yeah, get outta here.
- Don't come back.
Uh-oh.
- You don't even know how to drive!
- Bye, Andy!
- Loser!
- Nice car!
Have fun!
- Hey, Hank.
- Yes, ma'am.
I thought I was very specific about
not letting up a magician?
Yes, ma'am.
I got my eyes open.
Oh, turns out that he
actually made it up there.
What? That ain't right.
Yeah, he came and went.
Wait a minute!
You said he was a magician, right?
You don't think he could have used...
It couldn't have been...
Just let's go...
Night, night.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net