Parkour!
Extreme!
- Parkour!
This is parkour.
Internet sensation of 2004.
And it was in one of the Bond films.
It's pretty impressive.
The goal is to get from point A...
...to point B as creatively as possible.
So technically they are doing parkour...
...as long as point A is delusion...
...and point B is the hospital.
Okay, here we go!
- Andy, leapfrog!
Do me! Do me!
Get off! Get off!
Jump over it.
Jump over the camera.
Okay, we all go together
or we go one at a time.
Here it is.
Truck to refrigerators,
to dumpster,
360 spin onto the pallets,
backflip gainer into the trash can.
Hardcore parkour!
- Hardcore parkour!
I'm right behind you! Come on!
- Let's do it!
Parkour.
Good.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Is there anything else I can do?
See those files behind Kevin's desk?
Go put them all in random order.
Then come back here
for your next assignment...
...concerning their order.
This is the last day
of our summer interns.
It's been nice.
We haven't had interns in a while...
...ever since Michael's
Monica Lewinsky incident.
He didn't do anything sexual.
He just made far, far too many
Monica Lewinsky jokes.
It was just easier for corporate...
...to shutdown the program.
Think she did him?
- There's something there.
I was in the kitchen yesterday...
...and they were too happy...
...to be cleaning the freezer.
If they get married before I do,
I'm gonna kill myself.
Who's getting married?
- Nobody.
I'm gonna start screaming.
Eric and Megan.
I hired them.
Matchmaker.
This place is like Spaniard fly.
They're not getting married.
It's just talk.
Everybody knows about this but me?
There's nothing to know.
It's gossip.
We haven't told anyone that I'm pregnant.
What with her being unmarried.
Knocked up by some guy.
The yakkity-yaks in this office...
...would have a field day.
We don't want them...
...at the wedding thinking...
...Jim's being marched down the aisle...
...by my dad with a shotgun.
Wait,
there's not gonna be a shotgun?
No shotgun?
'Cause that changes everything.
- Can't back out now, Halpert.
What are you gonna do about it?
There's no shotgun, so...
Free at last. Free at last.
No, keep it up.
You'll never guess what I know.
Let me finish this thought.
Eric likes Megan.
He most definitely does.
He's been asking her out for weeks.
She finally said yes.
They went out the other night.
Apparently it went very well.
How do you know this?
- People tell me things.
I guess I have a face you can trust.
I think
it's because of my low cheekbones.
And...
Okay, what is it?
What can't I guess?
I hate, hate, hate being left out.
Whether it's not being
picked for a team...
...or being picked for a team
and then showing up...
...and realizing that
the team doesn't exist...
...or that the sport doesn't exist.
I should have known. Poopball?
Man, I know how you feel.
Third wheel.
I have been the third wheel
so many times in my life.
My mom told me something once...
...that made me feel better. She said...
...the third wheel
is what makes it a tricycle.
What are you talking about?
Your group date with Megan and Eric.
At Tink's?
How'd you know about that?
Did Stanley tell you?
Stanley was on your group date?
No, Stanley was with his wife.
I waved at him but he didn't wave back.
Does anybody else know about this?
There he goes.
So what is the scuttlebutt?
Anybody hear anything?
Nothing?
I got a little something-something.
I don't know if I should say.
- So just keep it to yourself then.
Stanley is having a midlife crisis.
Stanley is way past
the middle of his life,
considering his height to weight ratio.
Apparently he and his wife...
...were out dancing
at a club for young people.
Teri's out of town.
Who?
- Stanley's wife, Teri.
She's at an interior decorating expo
in Philly.
And Stanley hates crowds,
kids, and music.
I think you should check your facts.
You stupid son of a bitch.
You set me up.
What are you talking about?
- Stanley's wife is out of town.
He was with somebody.
- Definitely.
Was he? Who, his sister?
I don't get it!
If that was his sister,
then what they were doing was illegal.
Drugs?
Making out.
No, it's okay.
Never mind. Carry on.
Stanley is having an affair.
What?
- I know.
I am very happy right now,
thrilled perhaps,
to be a part of the office,
to be a part of the conversation.
When you have somebody's attention
and their eyes are lighting up...
...because they are very interested
in what you have to say,
that is a great feeling
and I experienced that firsthand today.
It is wonderful
to be the center of attention.
That and that are the same letter.
'Q'.
He's holding a pencil.
He could be doing a crossword puzzle
with that pencil.
What's that letter right there?
Same letter here and here.
What haven't you guessed?
- 'T'.
'T', yes!
That is a 't'
and there's another one right there.
Just sound that out.
You're almost there.
Where you going, big guy?
Up to no good?
I'm meeting a client.
Do you have a problem?
I just had a quick question for you.
I'm casting...
...a movie and I'm looking
for a woman who can dance.
Beautiful woman.
Do you know anybody?
Good-bye.
Pays $5 million.
Nudity required.
You have to stop this.
Did you hear?
Stanley's having an affair.
I did from you.
You got to stop telling people.
Okay, I get it.
You feel out of the loop
and sorry for yourself...
...and it's really sad,
everybody thinks you're a loser.
Do you even know if it's true?
Do you have any idea? Because...
...you might be ruining his life.
Hold up! Hold up!
Time to stop being polite and get real.
You having an affair?
That is ridiculous. Of course not.
Why would you think that?
So it's not true.
Those interns. They told me
they saw you at the club...
...and they all said it was you.
It was clearly just...
...racial profiling gossip.
The little...
- Damn!
Told her it was a stupid idea.
That's so stupid.
It's just that...
Teri's been traveling a lot lately.
- I know.
It's been lonely.
- I bet.
Cynthia's been keeping me company.
She was my nurse...
...when I was in rehabilitation.
We used to go on these long walks
on the treadmill.
I didn't intend...
Wait, wait, wait.
So it is true?
But I'm going to go break it off.
That's where I'm headed right now,
I swear.
Wait a second.
Do people often say they're going...
...on sales calls
and then go someplace else?
That's not cool.
I just need you to promise
not to say a word about this to anyone.
Michael, please.
I'm not saying a damn thing.
- I'm counting on you, Michael.
You can count on me.
That smells good.
I might have extra.
It just depends on how many I eat.
Did you hear about Angela?
That's weird.
What do you mean exactly?
The fact that she apparently is dating...
...an 81-year-old billionaire...
...who owns a Quiznos on the turnpike.
Really?
Right?
How do you untell something?
You can't.
You can't put words back in your mouth.
What you can do...
...is spread false gossip...
...so that people think that everything
that's been said is untrue,
including Stanley is having an affair.
It's like the end of Spartacus.
I've seen that movie half a dozen times...
...and I still don't know
who the real Spartacus is.
And that is what makes
that movie a classic whodunit.
Kelly has an eating disorder.
She always eats my lunch.
Anorexia. She's ana...
She's an 'anorexitec.'
We should do something.
- Nothing can be done.
Just have to tell everybody
and hope for the best, I guess.
I'm worried about Erin...
...because she's not a very good worker.
I don't know how long she's gonna last.
Really?
So...
And Andy...
...is gay.
Did you hear Pam is pregnant?
Really?
She's gonna hate being a mom.
What?
Tea.
So?
- You would.
I like tea.
I bet you like it.
I like it a lot.
I love tea.
Do you like it as much
as you like men's butts?
What?
'Cause you're gay.
Who told you that?
Was it Broccoli Rob?
Someone from Chi Psi?
Did you run
in someone from my high school?
This is not the first time...
...rumors about me being gay have come up.
Twice before, actually.
Just a weird coincidence.
It's a little too weird.
Almost makes you wonder
if it's not a coincidence at all.
Which it is, of course.
But it makes you wonder.
Did you hear the rumor about me?
That I'm gay?
I did.
And?
What?
Do you think it's true?
Do you think that I'm...
...gay?
Are you attracted to other men?
Let me kick you a scenario.
I'm at, like, a beach cabana...
...and Brad Pitt approaches,
tries to lean in and kiss me.
I would definitely resist,
like, at first.
But if he was persistent,
I might...
...give in a little bit
to just really see what it felt like.
Would I push him away?
How hard?
Like, what if he's,
like, really aggressive?
If you resisted Brad Pitt a little bit,
he would still...
...need to get to you?
- This is not real Brad Pitt.
This is, like, in my...
This is my fantasy.
Or it's, like, not fantasy.
It's, like, what I'm...
It's a scenario.
I wish I could help you. I don't...
You might be gay.
What exactly is my responsibility here?
To comfort insecure heterosexual men?
That can't possibly fall to me.
How far is Pam?
- A few months.
That's why they're rushing the wedding.
You can't believe everything you hear.
Like Stanley having an affair.
That is crazy.
Just there's no stock in it.
It's a weird day for false facts.
Let it go.
OK, everybody.
Big day. Last day for our interns.
Lot of other stuff.
Who knows what to believe?
Dwight, the honors.
Present these to the dean for credit.
And as a gift,
I've attached my card.
Call me anytime of the day or night.
Why would we call you at night?
Now you can't call me at all,
so problem solved.
You will regret when you find yourself...
...between a moose and her cubs.
Look to the intern on your left.
Now to your right.
One of you will do
exceedingly well in business.
Just unlimited potential.
One of you will make a living
and nothing more.
And one of you...
...will make a great mother.
It's up to you
to choose which you want to be.
I am so happy you're eating again.
Me too.
Dude, how come you never try
to set me up?
I don't really do that.
Pam might have some friends though.
Women friends?
Not guy friends?
Are you interested in her guy friends?
For the record, I prefer women.
But off the record,
I'm kind of confused.
Really?
The evidence is stacked against me,
I feel like.
You got to figure this out.
- Yeah, right? How?
You got to have sex with a woman.
Right-o.
- And then a man and then compare.
All right.
Congratulations to you.
- On what?
Come on.
Little baby tuna.
Little junior toro.
A baby conceived out of wedlock
is still a bastard.
What?
Want me to say it again?
Why did that come into your brain?
- Can I talk to you?
So they know.
Who did you tell?
- I didn't tell anyone. And you?
Nobody.
Did one of you tell Stanley
that I have asthma, 'cause I don't.
If it gets out,
they won't let me scuba.
If I can't scuba,
then what's this all been about?
What am I working toward?
What?
You think I'm the voice
of the Taco Bell Dog?
What are you talking about?
I have a daughter.
How could I be a virgin?
Has everyone heard
a crazy rumor about themselves today?
You know what?
Let's discredit these rumors.
Sure, but who's been saying
all that stuff?
That's not important,
We shouldn't listen to this crap.
We should get to the bottom of this.
Let's pick a rumor and trace it back.
I need to do mine first.
Who's been saying that
there's another person inside of me...
...working me with controls?
I heard that from Andy.
I heard it from Erin.
I heard it from Michael.
He's over here!
Where you going?
- Nowhere.
You told people
that I use store-bought manure...
...when I showed you
where my manure comes from.
Don't get on it.
- Michael, don't.
Don't get on.
Do not.
Stay, Michael.
- Step away.
Come on, boss.
Okay, I made it all up.
What?
Even the fact that I'm gay?
But, guys, I'm a victim here too.
People have been saying
that I am a J. Crew model.
No, we heard that about Jim.
I spread the rumor
that somebody was a J. Crew model...
...and I was referring to myself.
How is that a bad rumor?
- 'Cause people think that models,
even though they're very attractive
are somewhat vapid.
It set our industry back quite a bit.
Michael, why?
Why say all these things?
Why make up an eating disorder,
Stanley's affair,
me being a spokes dog?
You told everyone I was having an affair?
Here's the thing.
There was one true rumor out there today.
I didn't want everybody
to know what it was,
so all of you are off the hook
except for this one person.
Well, then what's the one true rumor?
We have a right to know.
Am I gay?
The one true rumor...
This is gonna ruin
this person's life, is...
That Pam's pregnant.
I knew it.
- I knew it.
Her breasts were a tiny bit bigger.
At first I thought,
she has a new bra with padding.
But then I thought,
Pam doesn't need padding.
It just didn't add up, Jim.
Congratulations.
- That's really great.
Don't vaccinate it.
- Who's the father?
How far along?
- Four months.
Who's the ob-gyn?
- Stop.
All right, you know...
This is not the truth...
...and you can't fall on a sword this way.
The real thing is that Stanley Hudson...
...had an affair.
Thank you to defend us, but actually,
Pam is pregnant and we can prove it.
If you would like to see proof.
Just gonna wait for her?
- What's the 'proof' mean?
There it is!
- It's true!
Look at that!
That is the inside of your vagina.
That's not how it works, but...
It's clear
why we were trying not to tell people.
That's clear now.
How long have you known
about the pregnancy?
A week? Month?
A year?
We only told our parents last week.
Did you pee on a stick?
- I did.
But it was inconclusive.
You should have told me.
You're right.
We should have realized
that you are an equal part of this.
Michael, Teri Hudson returning your call.
You called Stanley's wife?
A long time ago.
Just to make sure she was out of town.
God.
- Don't take it.
I have to take it
or it'll seem suspicious.
If you talk to her,
you're gonna tell her...
...and that's gonna seem more suspicious.
- I can do this.
You can't do this.
- I can. I am going to tell her...
...that I need to redecorate my condo
and I need her help.
We will haggle about money
and I will back down...
...and then I won't talk to her
until this Cynthia thing's blown over.
Sounds terrible.
- Please don't.
What up, Cynthia?
Just hang on a second, Cynthia.
It turns out
that Teri was already suspicious...
...because she had caught Stanley...
...and Cynthia a few months ago.
So Stanley promised...
...that he would stop and he did.
End of story. Well...
...not exactly.
Cynthia kept calling him.
She would not stop calling him
and she was in love with him.
And get this.
Cynthia? Also married.
So...
...you can't stop love, I guess.
And quite frankly,
I don't think you should ever even try.
I learned that a company
can describe an internship...
...as full of exciting experiences,
even if that's a lie.
There's no regulation.
I learned that half
these people's email password...
...is 'password.'
I learned that a ream of paper...
...is 300 sheets.
I thought it was 500.
I guess I didn't learn anything.
I learned that if you look
even the tiniest bit like Jet Li...
...Michael will call you
Jet Li all summer.
Julia Stiles.
- Alan Thicke.
www.tvsubtitles.net